[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2010-11-01 23:53:27
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:CASO_Tsubasa
Original Script:CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwen,方正隶变_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H004080FF,&H00000000,&H3C000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,0,3,1,2,30,30,15,134
Style: jinggao,方正水柱_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,8,5,5,13,134
Style: op,MS Gothic,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H80000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,1,8,10,10,13,128
Style: opzw,方正黑体_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H80000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,1,2,10,10,12,134
Style: ed,MS Gothic,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H80000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,1,8,10,10,13,128
Style: edzw,方正黑体_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H80000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,1,2,10,10,12,134
Style: yingwen,Monotype Corsiva,31,&H00FFFFFF,&H004080FF,&H00000000,&H3C000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,0,2,2,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.35,0:00:18.02,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已无法再回到　往昔的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.29,0:00:26.02,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在立誓　将曾经的悲伤统统战胜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.94,0:00:29.84,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若没有伤痕　便无法超越
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.20,0:00:34.74,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了能与你再次相会
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.09,0:00:38.77,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅途的足迹遍布了大地
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.94,0:00:44.33,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就在这无形之中教会了我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.75,0:00:50.68,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心又应该如何跳动
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.84,0:00:56.15,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未来并未被他人夺去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.47,0:01:01.31,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我相信我们能继续前行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.51,0:01:05.21,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Just go on　我只要能有你的微笑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.45,0:01:09.16,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只要能有你的歌声
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.43,0:01:13.57,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全会变成我期望中的情形
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.37,0:01:17.29,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你给了我那勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.32,0:01:20.83,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你给了我那温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.19,0:01:27.59,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为了我旅途中　能够前进下去的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.35,0:00:18.02,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう戻らないあの日々に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.29,0:00:26.02,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今誓う悲しみに打ち勝つこと
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.94,0:00:29.84,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無傷のまま越えれらない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.20,0:00:34.74,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君にまた出合うための旅は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.09,0:00:38.77,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足跡も燃え尽きて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.94,0:00:44.33,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君がいつか教えてくれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.75,0:00:50.68,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心の躍動が駆り立てる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.84,0:00:56.15,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未来までは奪われてない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.47,0:01:01.31,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それも知いてるから行ける
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.51,0:01:05.21,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Just go on　君が微笑むなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.45,0:01:09.16,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君が歌えるのなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.43,0:01:13.57,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おれが望むすべてに変える
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.37,0:01:17.29,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君がくれだ勇気
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.32,0:01:20.83,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君がくれだ優しさ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.19,0:01:27.59,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前を見つめて　歩く力になる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.57,0:23:15.98,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}気が付いてない　君はまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.30,0:23:27.53,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}昨日さえ帰る力が二人にあるってこと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.98,0:23:32.12,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}訳もないのに　lonely　lonely
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.51,0:23:36.80,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙がはらはらと落ちて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.07,0:23:40.77,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あいたいのはひとり　ひとり
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.82,0:23:48.04,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}空に描く人　君のことだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.09,0:23:52.37,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}この手を手を取って
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.46,0:23:54.30,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}一緒に行こうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.35,0:23:56.69,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手を手を伸ばし
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.72,0:23:58.73,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}風掴むんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.77,0:24:01.05,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手を手を取って
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.09,0:24:03.21,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}怖がらないで
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.23,0:24:05.45,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手を手を繋ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.50,0:24:15.87,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そして飛べに　君とな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.57,0:23:15.98,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}或许你仍没有发现
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.30,0:23:27.53,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你们两人拥有的力量连过去也可以改变
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.98,0:23:32.12,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无法去解释的　lonely　lonely
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.51,0:23:36.80,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}让我的泪水不禁滴落　如雨下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.07,0:23:40.77,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我想要见的只有你　只有你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.82,0:23:48.04,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在这天空中描绘的　正是你的身影
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.09,0:23:52.37,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想要这样　拉着你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.46,0:23:54.30,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}一起向前方行进
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.35,0:23:56.69,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}伸手　伸出你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.72,0:23:58.73,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}抓住那一阵风
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.77,0:24:01.05,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}拉手　拉着你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.09,0:24:03.21,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我已经不再害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.23,0:24:05.45,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}牵手　牵着你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.50,0:24:15.87,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,500)}并且和你一起　飞上青空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.20,0:01:34.10,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}本字幕仅限试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版，\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，华盟字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.20,0:01:38.10,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}翻译：美宝Anglea、七海·拓；校对：七海·拓、zipwinmax；时间：vipzhang；\N后期：vipzhang、Chris.R、zipwinmax；繁化：翊凌。
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.07,0:02:23.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2}少年的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.29,0:01:45.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗～到达下一个世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.59,0:01:47.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你噗什么噗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.09,0:01:49.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是一直都在强调让你降落在一个好点的地方么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.77,0:01:51.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是幸好在海里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.90,0:01:53.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开心地说什么傻话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.99,0:01:56.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主  有没有受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.33,0:01:59.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有点吓到了  没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.10,0:02:03.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说是陆地了  连个岛都没看到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.86,0:02:06.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去我们四个人都要去见上帝了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.30,0:02:09.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  看那个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.34,0:02:49.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.60,0:02:50.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.61,0:02:54.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.37,0:03:04.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了  坏人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.75,0:03:06.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.01,0:03:15.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把我称作坏人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.26,0:03:19.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着这张脸这么想也不奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.38,0:03:20.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不生气么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.15,0:03:24.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海上的男人怎么会在意那么小的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.62,0:03:28.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是这艘Lagosta的船长唐巴尔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.36,0:03:31.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是摩可拿  大家的偶像
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.31,0:03:32.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么是么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.00,0:03:34.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  偶像是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.22,0:03:38.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界的领主好像是个好人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.67,0:03:40.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以信他么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.52,0:03:41.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵魂不是一样的么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.29,0:03:45.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵魂那种东西不是没有善恶之分的么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.79,0:03:47.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.40,0:03:49.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啊  不是很清楚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.97,0:03:52.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.72,0:03:57.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事情商量一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.66,0:04:01.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的船上人手不太够呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.56,0:04:05.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你们几个来做饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.03,0:04:07.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常乐意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.70,0:04:09.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小摩可  加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.47,0:04:10.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会尽快完成的哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.39,0:04:19.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  新来的  快点打扫甲板
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.67,0:04:22.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是新来的  我是黑钢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.34,0:04:23.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.50,0:04:24.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报上名来  是想打架么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.84,0:04:26.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.85,0:04:31.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要打么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.76,0:04:36.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  机关长在么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.42,0:04:37.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.07,0:04:41.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么小的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.00,0:04:43.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很聪明的孩子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.88,0:04:46.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操作引擎方面可比大人都强哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.61,0:05:04.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.75,0:05:05.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.83,0:05:07.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.24,0:05:08.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.37,0:05:11.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我似乎在哪里见过你吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.71,0:05:14.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得没有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.87,0:05:16.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.66,0:05:18.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我说了奇怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.01,0:05:24.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫小狼  让他来帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.80,0:05:25.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.20,0:05:33.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是机关长  藤隆
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.71,0:05:35.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸  爸爸…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.37,0:05:38.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.46,0:05:41.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.98,0:05:43.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.92,0:06:00.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以摸的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.79,0:06:15.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要试试看么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.32,0:06:19.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要试试看么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.63,0:06:25.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我刚才在想事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.35,0:06:28.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我再做一次给你看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.62,0:06:45.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.37,0:06:47.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.76,0:06:49.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再轻柔一点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.32,0:06:52.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.33,0:06:56.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次要去发掘现场看看么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.04,0:06:59.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对考古有兴趣了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.91,0:07:02.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.69,0:07:11.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甲板扫除完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.31,0:07:13.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.35,0:07:15.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.54,0:07:20.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请尝尝味道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.84,0:07:21.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.45,0:07:23.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.12,0:07:27.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和小摩可一起做的  叫做司寿的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.96,0:07:29.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是司寿  是寿司
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.36,0:07:31.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.17,0:07:34.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好酸的味道啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.41,0:07:36.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还放着生的鱼～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.64,0:07:39.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法伊不喜欢寿司啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.04,0:07:41.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.62,0:07:50.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.45,0:07:58.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛有点酸酸的  但很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.33,0:08:02.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在和爸爸居住的国家里曾经吃过类似的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.05,0:08:06.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼爸爸是什么样的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.22,0:08:12.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸很早就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.41,0:08:14.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.10,0:08:15.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.57,0:08:22.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…没什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.15,0:08:25.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子是小狼的爸爸么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.79,0:08:26.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,严格的说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.20,0:08:32.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是和小狼的爸爸有着同一个灵魂的另外一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.37,0:08:33.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.79,0:08:35.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么爸爸会比你还年轻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.16,0:08:38.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在异世界拥有同一灵魂的不同的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.16,0:08:43.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自身的年龄也未必相同啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.42,0:08:49.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定在哪个世界有个小黑磷哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.47,0:08:50.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.86,0:08:53.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  这个国家有羽毛么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.75,0:08:56.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…完全没有这个感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.93,0:08:58.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次又落空了么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.09,0:09:01.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  摩可拿还在这个世界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.34,0:09:06.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是小狼这样想的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.40,0:09:07.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.18,0:09:11.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿感觉到了小狼的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.61,0:09:16.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼想和那个孩子再待一下  哪怕一小会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.35,0:09:19.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以摩可拿会再待一下的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.45,0:09:22.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  摩可拿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.79,0:09:46.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.73,0:09:47.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我小狼就行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.78,0:09:52.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼在我这么大的时候做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.54,0:09:56.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮爸爸的忙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.95,0:09:59.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸是考古学家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.71,0:10:00.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.84,0:10:04.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼也是为了调查遗迹而出来旅行的么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.59,0:10:09.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然对考古学有兴趣  但是这并不是旅行的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.25,0:10:14.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有不管怎样都一定要找到的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.30,0:10:18.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.95,0:10:24.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有目标的人很好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.17,0:10:28.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很想为什么而活着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.51,0:10:35.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是要为什么而活  现在还在寻找这个目标
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.74,0:10:42.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸也有这样的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.77,0:10:47.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那个老头在叫你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.36,0:10:50.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  船长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.78,0:10:53.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风的味道消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.06,0:10:55.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来暴风雨了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.67,0:10:56.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.72,0:11:38.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去是不行的  得关掉引擎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.72,0:11:40.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  必须要船长的命令才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.86,0:11:43.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去问一下  小狼请跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.44,0:11:52.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再稍微把船稳住  快点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.93,0:11:55.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船长  快点把引擎…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.32,0:11:59.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机关长
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.77,0:12:01.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼君  藤隆君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.21,0:12:03.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼  抓住
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.26,0:12:08.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.92,0:12:10.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机关长
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.80,0:12:13.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑声
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.83,0:12:14.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.06,0:12:23.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.69,0:12:35.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼君——
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.02,0:12:50.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  机关长  新来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.30,0:12:53.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.09,0:12:55.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.68,0:12:58.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样都找不到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.58,0:13:26.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.41,0:13:38.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.78,0:13:41.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像我们被冲到附近的岸上了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.25,0:13:43.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lagosta号呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.01,0:13:45.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道沉没了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.84,0:13:50.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那样的话  会有更多船体的碎片漂上来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.50,0:13:52.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么船没事的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.67,0:13:53.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.63,0:13:54.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.91,0:14:01.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先找到船  通知他们我们在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.24,0:14:05.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  好像沿着海走是不太可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.47,0:14:09.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我们就去那边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.98,0:14:18.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.22,0:14:24.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  这里是亡灵之岛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.32,0:14:29.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亡灵之岛…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.77,0:14:46.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.87,0:14:49.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在岛上的亡灵们的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.68,0:14:50.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亡灵？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.83,0:14:53.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从先祖那里流传下来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.43,0:14:57.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个岛上住着很恐怖的亡灵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.94,0:15:01.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们千万不能登陆那个岛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.32,0:15:05.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  小狼他们可能被冲到那个岛上了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.72,0:15:08.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使那样  我们也没有办法救他们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.77,0:15:10.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅行的人可能不能明白
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.26,0:15:13.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是在这个国家生存的我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.62,0:15:16.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须遵守先祖的叮嘱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.39,0:15:19.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  请原谅我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.74,0:15:20.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.50,0:15:33.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.96,0:15:35.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…啊  不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.89,0:15:36.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.83,0:15:40.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说敬语了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.20,0:15:42.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.40,0:15:44.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我的话没关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.53,0:15:46.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.04,0:15:49.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.95,0:15:51.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了  是亡灵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.35,0:16:00.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个岛上曾经住过人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.38,0:16:02.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.55,0:16:03.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是遗迹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.94,0:16:05.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是相当古老的了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.52,0:16:08.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是岛的地图？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.33,0:16:18.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不要惧怕神的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.58,0:16:21.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倾听神的歌声之时
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.49,0:16:23.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道路会变得光明」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.34,0:16:24.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能读懂吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.18,0:16:29.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经学过这种文字
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.16,0:16:33.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「真正可怕的是…长的东西」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.81,0:16:36.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这里就读不懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.72,0:16:41.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这条路看来是通向山顶的小路呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.67,0:16:46.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是看哪里都不像路
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.91,0:16:49.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  有路
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.45,0:16:55.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.31,0:16:59.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是爸爸教给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.73,0:17:14.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是「亡灵」的实体么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.82,0:17:15.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.83,0:17:20.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在听到的就是  刚才那遗迹上所写的神的歌声
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.07,0:17:25.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是亡灵的笑声
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.97,0:17:26.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.01,0:17:38.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是神的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.02,0:17:42.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是大家说的恐怖的亡灵的实体
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.59,0:17:47.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都相信的亡灵  原来是风的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.15,0:17:53.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是船还在的话  应该在岛的另一面
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.36,0:17:57.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要到那边的话就只能穿过这个遗迹了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.89,0:18:01.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  在遗迹里面要是遇到刚才那样的风怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.14,0:18:05.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不要惧怕神的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.84,0:18:08.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倾听神的歌声之时
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.82,0:18:10.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道路会变得光明」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.39,0:18:15.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  听见这种歌声的时候就是安全的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.58,0:18:30.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们真的去岛那边了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.93,0:18:34.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船舵修理完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.21,0:18:48.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.16,0:18:49.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.29,0:19:13.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.67,0:19:30.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风向变了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.26,0:19:58.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才真危险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.70,0:20:01.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  小狼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.19,0:20:11.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活着呢  两个人都活着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.57,0:20:13.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.29,0:20:18.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看快看  两个人都没事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.10,0:20:19.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.51,0:20:24.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  马上就过来  等一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.62,0:20:26.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.74,0:20:49.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「真正可怕的是…长的东西」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.27,0:20:53.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗迹上写的就是那个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.21,0:21:04.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许先祖是要借亡灵之说向我们传达  让我们小心那个怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.69,0:21:19.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许亡灵的实体的确是那风声
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.38,0:21:23.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我以为那里是禁地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.20,0:21:26.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大海还是很宽广的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.56,0:21:29.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使有上一件不可思议的事情也没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.95,0:21:30.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.98,0:21:33.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有及时去救你们真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.34,0:21:33.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.21,0:21:38.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了船长  我才找到了要找的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.92,0:21:39.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.57,0:21:44.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢诸位照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.28,0:21:46.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就在此分别吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.13,0:21:50.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  这里可是海上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.53,0:21:56.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿·摩多基正兴奋不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.59,0:22:04.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.65,0:22:09.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保重吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.26,0:22:12.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.65,0:22:17.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼  我找到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.81,0:22:21.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长大以后我要成为考古学家
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.50,0:22:28.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定能行的  绝对可以
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.24,0:22:34.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.66,0:24:33.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有不亮的夜
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.88,0:24:34.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的常识
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.12,0:24:37.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在下一个世界好像完全行不通
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.97,0:24:39.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有白天的这个国家里
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.69,0:24:42.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等待法伊的是孤零零的公主
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.71,0:24:46.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？对法伊来说  那是很怀念的女孩吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.56,0:24:49.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到法伊和那个女孩是怎样生活的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.64,0:24:51.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就请继续期待吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.28,0:24:52.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼·年代记
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.63,0:24:53.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与魔术师的约会
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.16,0:24:56.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回会为两位小女孩的登场而心动不已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.32,0:21:12.95,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Far in the night, I can see it in every scene of the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.20,0:21:15.79,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}A tiny feather of love.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.06,0:21:26.67,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}I gotta go destiny never finds the way for me,my love.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.94,0:21:36.37,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Even in the night I see your face, in the dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.85,0:21:42.81,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}So I never lose my way to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.99,0:21:45.65,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}I never close my heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.75,0:21:52.19,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}The light is always there.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.21,0:21:58.95,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Time goes by, we can never stay the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.16,0:22:04.30,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Now we come so far from love memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.50,0:22:09.82,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Though your smile has gone,we will never be apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.06,0:22:15.66,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}In our hearts we are one, for love melody.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.80,0:22:22.85,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}The future arrives with your love.


