[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-04-24 00:20:16
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Mushishi
Original Script:CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwen,方正细珊瑚简体,35,&H00CEE1D6,&H00000000,&H35000000,&H143F5A42,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,15,134
Style: biaoti,宋体,61,&H00F4F9EC,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: biaoti2,黑体,120,&H00B38A71,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,550,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: LOGO,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H60000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,134
Style: LOGO2,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&HFF676767,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,2,1,30,30,10,134
Style: OP English,Monotype Corsiva,37,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: OP Chinese,华文隶书,32,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,12,134
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,5,5,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.60,0:00:20.12,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I walked ten thousand miles,ten thousands miles to see you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.27,0:00:27.00,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And ever gasp to breath,I grabbed it just to find you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.02,0:00:33.82,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I climbed up every hill to get to you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:40.65,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I wandered ancient lands to hold just you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:48.76,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And every single step of the way,I paid
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:01:00.79,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Every single night and day I searched for you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.03,0:01:12.52,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Through sand storms and hazy dawns I reached for you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.60,0:00:20.12,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我步行万里  一万里只为见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.27,0:00:27.00,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}从不向瞬间喘息  紧扼住每一丝遇见的契机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.02,0:00:33.82,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我攀上每一座丘陵  寻找那邂逅的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:40.65,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}徘徊于远古的大陆  而我想占据的  仅仅是你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:48.76,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}一路上留下的每一个脚印  是我付出的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:01:00.79,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}每一个孤单的黑夜白天里  我寻找着你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.03,0:01:12.52,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}穿越肆虐的沙暴穿越迷雾的拂晓  而后  将是你我的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(466,246)\frz-90}{\fsp-1}www.CAMOE.cn
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx100}{\pos(100,530)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)}{\pos(100,225)}柔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)}{\pos(100,290)}软
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)}{\pos(100,355)}的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)}{\pos(100,420)}角
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)}{\pos(100,225)}柔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)}{\pos(100,290)}软
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)}{\pos(100,355)}的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.75,0:02:56.64,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)}{\pos(100,420)}角
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.00,0:03:01.00,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}本字幕仅供交流试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版。\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，华盟字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.10,0:03:05.10,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}翻译：馨；校对：X；时间：zipwinmax；\N特效、歌词：Noeru；后期：Noeru、zipwinmax；繁化：黑羽侖人。
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.15,0:02:17.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.48,0:02:27.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用双手把耳朵捂住的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.02,0:02:29.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额头就会突起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.85,0:02:31.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四个角就会露出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.15,0:02:36.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大雪纷飞的晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.92,0:02:38.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音都消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.16,0:02:40.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要和谁说话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.33,0:02:42.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要把耳朵捂住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.70,0:02:44.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不捂的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.70,0:02:47.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳朵就会…被吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.75,0:03:00.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎你的到来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.23,0:03:04.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是虫师银古先生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.68,0:03:06.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.01,0:03:09.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是村长白泽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.98,0:03:12.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代表村子请你来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.54,0:03:17.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你所见  村子地处山坳
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.07,0:03:21.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安静地连风声也听不到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.34,0:03:24.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别像现在这样的雪夜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.90,0:03:27.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万籁俱寂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.28,0:03:30.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时仿佛说话声都被寂静所吞食
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.93,0:03:33.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这种时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.81,0:03:36.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多人得了耳疾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.37,0:03:39.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是两只耳朵吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.16,0:03:42.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数的人是单耳
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.26,0:03:46.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山下的医生费尽心机都找不到病因
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.22,0:03:51.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想是否是鬼怪在作祟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.68,0:04:04.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  这种黏液
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.28,0:04:08.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原因是虫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.23,0:04:12.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一种叫「{\fnyouyuan}呍{\r}」的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.72,0:04:16.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是它们吃掉了声音
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.16,0:04:20.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常栖息在森林中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.90,0:04:23.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪把声音给吸收了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.25,0:04:27.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以虫才会到村子里来觅食声音
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.45,0:04:36.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.82,0:04:39.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像作了相当大的巢穴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.65,0:04:43.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是声音消失的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.60,0:04:50.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样离开巢穴后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.99,0:04:52.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄生在动物身上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.63,0:04:55.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去像蜗牛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.05,0:05:00.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.09,0:05:02.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是移动了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.99,0:05:07.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道耳朵里有个和蜗牛很像的器官吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.80,0:05:11.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饿了的「{\fnyouyuan}呍{\r}」抛弃外壳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.58,0:05:12.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里寄生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.33,0:05:15.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃掉了所有传进耳朵的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.81,0:05:19.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以器官并没有被破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.96,0:05:20.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.68,0:05:25.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要的这盆热水
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.46,0:05:26.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.89,0:05:34.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个流进耳朵里去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.08,0:05:49.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  就像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.18,0:05:52.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好咸  这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.00,0:05:54.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是盐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.87,0:05:55.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盐？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.72,0:05:57.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听得见了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.88,0:06:04.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来再在楼顶洒些  就没有问题了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.83,0:06:09.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人吃惊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.71,0:06:12.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次听说虫师这个职业
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.25,0:06:16.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的只有一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.29,0:06:19.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双耳都失聪的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.36,0:06:23.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的…外孙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.48,0:06:30.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和其他人的情况明显不同
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.45,0:06:32.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我外孙的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.15,0:06:36.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能麻烦你不要和村里的人提起可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.51,0:06:57.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.46,0:06:59.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我安静点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.66,0:07:09.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫真火
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.33,0:07:12.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从去年冬天开始就变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.89,0:07:16.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然从前面长出了角
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.38,0:07:22.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那开始就听不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.84,0:07:28.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他说听见了从没有听到过的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.72,0:07:32.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使像这样安静的晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.54,0:07:35.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还是会听见外面的声响
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.89,0:07:38.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窃窃私语或者嘈杂声
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.00,0:07:42.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使捂住耳朵  塞住缝隙也不会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.85,0:07:45.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音会从角里进去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.36,0:07:51.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个恐怕是「阿」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.61,0:07:52.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.51,0:07:54.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和「{\fnyouyuan}呍{\r}」一起行动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.24,0:07:57.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专吃「{\fnyouyuan}呍{\r}」产生的「无音」的虫子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.14,0:08:01.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这个寄生了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.71,0:08:03.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一个世界的声音会逐渐变大的同时
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.71,0:08:03.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fs25}（即野生动物能听到的声音）
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.98,0:08:07.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自身的声音会消失
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.80,0:08:12.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  和「{\fnyouyuan}呍{\r}」比起来是很少见的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.64,0:08:16.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流传下来治疗的记录只有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.08,0:08:22.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且像对付「{\fnyouyuan}呍{\r}」一样用盐水洗的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.54,0:08:24.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「阿」也不会从耳朵里出来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.43,0:08:28.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有人试过各种各样的药
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.30,0:08:31.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收效甚微
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.39,0:08:36.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,患者会在第二年冬季结束时发病
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.60,0:08:37.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是白天还是晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.75,0:08:40.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳朵充满洪水般的噪声
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.21,0:08:43.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,患者精神会崩溃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.32,0:08:46.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久后就衰弱而死
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.87,0:08:52.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个冬季结束之时…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.19,0:08:59.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  要知己知彼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.25,0:09:16.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的声音听的见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.60,0:09:23.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  周围稍微变安静了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.84,0:09:28.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥来了之后  声音变的越来越大
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.38,0:09:31.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头好像要炸开了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.13,0:09:34.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还真是不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.82,0:09:37.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的体质天生招虫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.01,0:09:40.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫在身边咔喳咔喳很烦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.00,0:09:43.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个烟可以赶走它
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.64,0:09:47.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫？这种声音吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.31,0:09:49.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数都是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.45,0:09:53.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动物中人的耳朵算是特别迟钝的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.20,0:09:57.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,许多动物都能听到更多的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.63,0:10:03.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但  也有野兽听不到的很大的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.53,0:10:07.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是虫的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.82,0:10:11.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫都是用那么大的声音在说话吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.81,0:10:12.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.38,0:10:16.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单个发出的声音很微小
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.03,0:10:21.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但虫不胜其数
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.91,0:10:25.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些东西一起发出声音的话会怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.99,0:10:27.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那将是惊人的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.83,0:10:31.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回荡着充斥整个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.20,0:10:36.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你耳朵里的是叫「阿」的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.12,0:10:38.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃掉了你的「寂静」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.49,0:10:41.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会长出这些角来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.49,0:10:44.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那里传入各种各样的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.10,0:10:47.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕就是这么回事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.74,0:10:51.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你耳朵看不出什么异常啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.83,0:10:54.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些角  是怎样出来的？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.09,0:11:02.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把耳朵捂住
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.35,0:11:05.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年冬天
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.46,0:11:08.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为妈妈去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.64,0:11:14.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈总是那样做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.65,0:11:17.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回忆起来也那样做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.47,0:11:24.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果  额头突起  角就出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.08,0:11:27.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捂住耳朵？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.73,0:11:31.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你妈妈要…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.32,0:11:35.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  我想不起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.32,0:11:40.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈和我一样  得了额头长角的病
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.50,0:11:44.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捂住耳朵应该也能听到声音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.06,0:11:50.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候妈妈好像说着什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.72,0:11:59.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用无力的手使劲捂住我的耳朵
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.10,0:12:04.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  那个时候到底说了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.55,0:12:07.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该记得的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.97,0:12:10.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是每当我回想的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.58,0:12:14.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会不断有声音流进耳朵里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.05,0:12:16.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本想不起来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.49,0:12:19.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.78,0:12:25.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  虽然不幸但运气还算好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.79,0:12:28.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有过类似的病…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.72,0:12:31.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该有可以治疗的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.33,0:12:42.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿去世时…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.84,0:12:46.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她当时很可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.99,0:12:50.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为声音的缘故  无法安心睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.12,0:12:54.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然在真火的面前绝对不提  但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.82,0:12:58.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她死前一直在说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.04,0:13:02.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想在一个什么声音都没有的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.80,0:13:04.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好的睡一觉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.88,0:13:07.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你刚才说的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.32,0:13:11.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发病后的第二年冬末就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.72,0:13:14.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了她一直想去的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.97,0:13:19.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后也是被痛苦折磨着吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.41,0:13:20.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.85,0:13:24.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.11,0:13:25.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.31,0:13:28.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天突然说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.03,0:13:32.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  声音消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.31,0:13:38.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「嘭」的一下  什么都听不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.20,0:13:45.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害怕  好怀念那样轰隆的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.49,0:13:49.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后不久
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.13,0:13:55.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像那声音消失了一样  去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.55,0:13:59.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是在死前什么声音都听不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.23,0:14:00.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.53,0:14:03.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有其它状况吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.95,0:14:04.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.12,0:14:08.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  恐怕真火刚才所说的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.56,0:14:10.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.77,0:14:13.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时也觉得很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.86,0:14:17.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子到底  因为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.34,0:14:22.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去世前的寂静
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.78,0:14:25.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,察觉到宿主死期将至
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.04,0:14:27.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「阿」离开了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.78,0:14:32.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能  那样应该会恢复听觉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.74,0:14:36.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都听不见了  到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.12,0:14:41.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有为什么要拼命捂住真火的耳朵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.26,0:14:46.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.81,0:14:48.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫了也听不到吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.24,0:14:51.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.70,0:14:57.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  只是稍微散步而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.66,0:15:00.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对外婆要保密
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.02,0:15:03.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直待在家里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.39,0:15:07.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就更显得奇怪…了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.61,0:15:09.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.46,0:15:18.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我总是想着妈妈死时的情景
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.80,0:15:26.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.29,0:15:30.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为妈妈和自己得了相同的病吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.27,0:15:42.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下雪了  还没有回来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.35,0:15:45.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真火  真火
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.17,0:15:49.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银古先生  真火不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.64,0:15:50.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.63,0:15:52.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看着他出去的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.67,0:15:53.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.81,0:15:55.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么让他出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.79,0:15:57.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找他去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.44,0:16:03.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好安静
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.33,0:16:10.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  并不是一点声音也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.36,0:16:16.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竖起耳朵  可以听见雪飘落的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.02,0:16:18.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果周围很安静的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.32,0:16:21.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能听到自己心跳的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.19,0:16:27.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  声音逐渐被吃掉后
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.75,0:16:30.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音就一点一点听不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.24,0:16:35.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是发展到极限的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.72,0:16:37.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.59,0:16:43.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许这就是声音消失的原因吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.58,0:16:47.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.87,0:16:59.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.43,0:17:05.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我本来打算马上回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.20,0:17:09.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中途下起了暴风雪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.55,0:17:13.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想在这里等着雪停
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.76,0:17:18.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  渐渐越下越大了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.72,0:17:20.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  声音…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.77,0:17:39.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.69,0:17:42.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们别着急
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.54,0:17:44.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「阿」是哪一只
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.05,0:17:47.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「{\fnyouyuan}呍{\r}」是向右转
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.84,0:17:50.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「阿」是向左转…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.95,0:17:51.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.21,0:18:12.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真火  把你的双手拿出来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.04,0:18:15.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你妈妈那样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.69,0:18:27.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.04,0:18:40.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,融化了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.75,0:18:45.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用双手捂住耳朵也不是没有任何声音
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.63,0:18:51.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在死前并不是无意识的捂住耳朵
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.27,0:18:56.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想那时她是想听真正的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.75,0:18:59.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听得见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.19,0:19:06.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微小的类似大地振动的轰鸣声
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.71,0:19:10.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是手腕肌肉运动的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.22,0:19:13.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说  「阿」的弱点是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.52,0:19:15.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其它生物发出的生理声音
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.25,0:19:21.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种声音会一直在生物体内回响
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.82,0:19:25.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对「阿」来说不是好的寄生场所
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.15,0:19:29.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以「阿」最终会消亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.18,0:19:31.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「阿」消亡的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.66,0:19:33.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宿主也会衰弱死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.46,0:19:39.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这大概需要一年的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.95,0:19:43.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你女儿应该意识到了这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.77,0:19:48.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那个时候已经很衰弱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.94,0:19:51.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连伸出手的力量都没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.81,0:19:53.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真火
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.75,0:19:56.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听得到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.63,0:19:59.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是妈妈的声音啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.28,0:20:04.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很早以前  妈妈看到过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.90,0:20:07.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和爸爸一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.28,0:20:10.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活火山
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.80,0:20:17.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音  和熔炎的声音很像
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.05,0:20:26.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  当妈妈相当不安的时候  就听这个声音
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.52,0:20:30.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像什么都能融化一样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.78,0:20:38.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安和难过  全都融化了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.51,0:20:42.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  你也试试
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.44,0:20:46.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听听你体内熔岩的…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.54,0:21:03.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熔岩…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.30,0:21:05.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真火
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.75,0:21:12.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火红的熔岩…在流动
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.13,0:21:20.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  这个就作为报酬
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.46,0:21:22.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.84,0:21:24.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的这样就行了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.02,0:21:25.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.03,0:21:28.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗  真火？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.45,0:21:30.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.25,0:21:49.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界变安静了吧  真火
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.72,0:21:52.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许还不习惯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.04,0:21:55.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还会怀念以前的世界吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.00,0:22:02.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  到了热闹的春天就会忘记的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.11,0:22:07.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…不会忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.60,0:22:14.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在听着的  和妈妈一样的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.37,0:22:21.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那震撼人心的…美妙的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.08,0:23:36.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)}「枕边小路」


