[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-05-06 15:53:22
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:虫师
Original Script:华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwen,方正细珊瑚简体,35,&H00CEE1D6,&H00000000,&H35000000,&H143F5A42,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,15,134
Style: biaoti,宋体,61,&H00F4F9EC,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: biaoti2,黑体,120,&H006791CA,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,550,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: LOGO,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H60000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,134
Style: LOGO2,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&HFF676767,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,2,1,30,30,10,134
Style: OP English,Monotype Corsiva,37,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: OP Chinese,华文隶书,32,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,12,134
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,5,5,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.60,0:00:20.12,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I walked ten thousand miles,ten thousands miles to see you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.27,0:00:27.00,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And ever gasp to breath,I grabbed it just to find you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.02,0:00:33.82,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I climbed up every hill to get to you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:40.65,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I wandered ancient lands to hold just you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:48.76,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And every single step of the way,I paid
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:01:00.79,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Every single night and day I searched for you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.03,0:01:12.52,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Through sand storms and hazy dawns I reached for you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.60,0:00:20.12,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我步行万里  一万里只为见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.27,0:00:27.00,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}从不向瞬间喘息  紧扼住每一丝遇见的契机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.02,0:00:33.82,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我攀上每一座丘陵  寻找那邂逅的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:40.65,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}徘徊于远古的大陆  而我想占据的  仅仅是你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:48.76,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}一路上留下的每一个脚印  是我付出的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:01:00.79,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}每一个孤单的黑夜白天里  我寻找着你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.03,0:01:12.52,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}穿越肆虐的沙暴穿越迷雾的拂晓  而后  将是你我的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(466,246)\frz-90}{\fsp-1}www.CAMOE.cn
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)\fscx100}{\pos(75,516)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(75,228)}沉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(75,288)}睡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)\fscx96}{\pos(76,348)}之
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(75,408)}山
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(75,228)}沉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(75,288)}睡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)\fscx96}{\pos(76,348)}之
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.26,0:02:10.15,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(75,408)}山
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.90,0:02:14.90,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}本字幕仅供交流试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版。\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，华盟字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.00,0:02:19.00,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}翻译、校对：X；时间：zipwinmax；特效、歌词：Noeru；\N后期：Noeru、zipwinmax；繁化：黑羽侖人。
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.48,0:01:40.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山上有个洞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.23,0:01:47.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是神山  好壮观啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.28,0:01:50.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘  来碗荞麦面
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.45,0:01:51.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  两份
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.26,0:01:53.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有酒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.98,0:01:55.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  让我放一下  小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.06,0:02:01.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.70,0:02:14.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是  要是没人去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.24,0:02:16.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.36,0:02:18.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算谁去了也只是重蹈覆辙而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.51,0:02:22.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然现在不能进山里去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.84,0:02:25.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无直大师不是也说了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.72,0:02:28.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可这正关系到他的安全啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.02,0:02:33.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山里发生什么事了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.30,0:02:36.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.01,0:02:38.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是虫师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.13,0:02:40.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里山的状况有点怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.17,0:02:43.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得自己帮得上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.23,0:02:45.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  虫师？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.40,0:02:47.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他是虫师呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.00,0:02:49.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.60,0:02:51.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长老
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.18,0:02:52.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.11,0:02:59.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  请一定要帮帮我们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.15,0:03:05.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请找找住在这深山里的虫师无直大师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.10,0:03:13.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这山里住着全能的山神
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.92,0:03:20.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无直大师是唯一知晓神意的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.60,0:03:25.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做任何事的时候我们都先请示大师的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.58,0:03:31.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在收割的季节我们不能进入深山
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.84,0:03:36.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是大师定下的规矩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.50,0:03:42.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是在无直大师突然消失后不久
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.56,0:03:47.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有几个人打破禁忌进入深山找他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.84,0:03:53.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果得了热病而丢了性命
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.88,0:04:01.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精气很重
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.28,0:04:04.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点甜又有点苦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.78,0:04:07.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛渗进皮肤一般的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.82,0:04:09.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.48,0:04:11.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光脉的主流
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.82,0:04:16.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命之河流淌的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.18,0:04:20.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且现在是收获的季节
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.29,0:04:23.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使普通的山上精气也会增加
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.28,0:04:27.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没准备的话一定会中毒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.35,0:04:35.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里应该有守护光脉主流的灵兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.29,0:04:38.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山的异变也许是因为灵兽的变化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.79,0:04:45.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话  那个虫师应该知道原因
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.43,0:04:56.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村里的小孩吗？喂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.52,0:05:01.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.67,0:05:06.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在找无直大师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.68,0:05:11.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是无直大师的弟子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.87,0:05:15.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连弟子也有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.62,0:05:18.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个含在嘴里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.58,0:05:24.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  好苦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.51,0:05:26.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头晕的时候就嚼一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.53,0:05:28.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是提神的药
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.31,0:05:31.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早…早说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.81,0:05:33.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  老实待在这里别动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.28,0:05:36.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始由我来找你的师父
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.75,0:05:40.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.22,0:05:45.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问「{\fnyouyuan}葎{\r}」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.94,0:05:50.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「{\fnyouyuan}葎{\r}」是一种宛如山的神经的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.62,0:05:55.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们的意识游走于草木之中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.96,0:06:02.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.95,0:06:13.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.44,0:06:14.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.95,0:06:15.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到别处看看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.76,0:06:17.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去山的另一边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.33,0:06:22.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.69,0:06:25.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边已经看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.40,0:06:30.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「{\fnyouyuan}葎{\r}」自动脱离了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.27,0:06:33.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.71,0:06:35.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.54,0:06:40.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  是这边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.12,0:06:41.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.91,0:06:50.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钟声？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.13,0:06:52.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在大概七点了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.24,0:06:56.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边有钟吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.91,0:07:02.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是在附近
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.38,0:07:04.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  看那个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.93,0:07:08.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.49,0:07:10.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无直大师
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.03,0:07:19.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说  是因为脚滑了而受伤咯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.42,0:07:22.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直吃周围的果实和草度日
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.64,0:07:25.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水我自己有带
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.65,0:07:33.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有我帮忙传达神意村里人一定很困惑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.55,0:07:40.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也真是的  竟然被同为虫师的人救了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.57,0:07:42.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫银古
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.85,0:07:43.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫无直
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.50,0:07:47.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乡下人不懂什么礼节
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.47,0:07:53.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这大山就像我自己的庭院一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.32,0:07:57.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过居然在那种地方滑了脚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.75,0:07:59.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我真是老了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.66,0:08:05.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是该卸任的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.35,0:08:09.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是指「山神」吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.94,0:08:13.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能将我这个入侵者控制的「{\fnyouyuan}葎{\r}」弹开
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.17,0:08:15.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是灵兽能办的到的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.39,0:08:18.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是人的法术吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.50,0:08:24.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先前山的异变是因为你在崖边无法动弹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.90,0:08:27.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法四处施法造成的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.04,0:08:35.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不过等明天我这脚好了我又能扮演「山神」了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.34,0:08:38.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山也会恢复原状
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.31,0:08:42.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但据说人来做灵兽的工作很辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.78,0:08:45.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道有什么苦衷吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.31,0:08:48.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.41,0:08:50.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有一条光脉的主流
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.82,0:08:58.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来有正统的灵兽来抑止山上的灵气
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.63,0:09:03.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过被村里的人误杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.84,0:09:08.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始是河水有酒的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.37,0:09:12.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着草木因为过度生长而几乎全部腐烂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.68,0:09:17.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前也是旅行的虫师
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.08,0:09:20.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常会在这村子里借宿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.42,0:09:24.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看到这里的状况
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.33,0:09:26.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决心留下来做这里的「山神」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.65,0:09:33.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子因为长期生活在精气迷漫的山上而过世了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.88,0:09:36.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  你想让这个孩子做下届的「山神」吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.57,0:09:38.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.98,0:09:41.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能在这山上行走  他资质还不错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.52,0:09:43.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那当然
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.83,0:09:49.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是大山抚养的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.86,0:09:53.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你注意到村里小孩的数量了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.07,0:09:56.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝了山上流下的水
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.71,0:10:00.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人们都会孕育很多小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.63,0:10:03.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,养不活的就被遗弃到山里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.88,0:10:10.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有被野兽吃掉而活下来的只有这个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.81,0:10:17.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是村里这孩子的兄弟都夭折了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.24,0:10:24.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年前这孩子的双亲把他领回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.41,0:10:26.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们真是自私呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.33,0:10:30.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  你说的没错  但是也没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.86,0:10:34.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他还是留在父母身边比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.05,0:10:38.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钟声？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.50,0:10:41.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么晚还有？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.92,0:10:48.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一直这么辗转流浪吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.16,0:10:50.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.57,0:10:54.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我体内寄生了很多虫子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.98,0:10:57.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一个地方住下的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.42,0:10:59.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不出半年就会出现虫的巢穴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.38,0:11:04.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是我使用虫的必然代价吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.55,0:11:08.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以只好四处漂泊吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.81,0:11:10.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里  其实我挺喜欢这种生活
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.97,0:11:12.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.99,0:11:14.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.94,0:11:20.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起我一步都不能踏出这座山还真是令人羡慕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.99,0:11:29.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样这山就是我的埋骨之地了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.60,0:11:40.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  我这就去村里把消息告诉大家
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.62,0:11:43.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到我回来之前  不要乱动哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.64,0:11:45.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.41,0:11:50.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你也要在解禁之后再进山里来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.86,0:11:55.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  你也要保重
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.83,0:11:57.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  保重
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.51,0:12:07.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无直大师
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.04,0:12:11.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在也还是无直大师的弟子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.07,0:12:14.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.62,0:12:17.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从村里到这里就是一种锻炼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.16,0:12:21.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在已经是很出色的虫师了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.04,0:12:23.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.48,0:12:29.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  他回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.28,0:12:31.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉和他在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.00,0:12:33.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无直大师没事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.53,0:12:50.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音越来越近了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.85,0:12:53.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是顺风的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.23,0:12:55.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底从哪里来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.07,0:12:56.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银古先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.48,0:12:59.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那声音很怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.83,0:13:01.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近又没有钟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.05,0:13:04.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲他们说什么都没有听到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.98,0:13:09.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为虫的原因吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.59,0:13:12.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问你个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.23,0:13:13.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.94,0:13:18.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经在学「山神」的法术了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.59,0:13:21.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「山神」？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.86,0:13:24.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使人成为「山神」的法术
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.25,0:13:28.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,术者在体内饲养「{\fnyouyuan}葎{\r}」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.69,0:13:31.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时常保持驾驱「{\fnyouyuan}葎{\r}」的状态
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.04,0:13:38.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使睡觉的时候  也能感知山上发生的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.87,0:13:42.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能操控「{\fnyouyuan}葎{\r}」的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.54,0:13:46.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能掌握抑止这山中异常的精气的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.77,0:13:49.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没有开始学习
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.46,0:13:51.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.87,0:13:58.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  钟声的原因并非什么特别让人担心的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.08,0:14:00.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家睡觉去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.28,0:14:02.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.88,0:14:04.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是去散步而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.76,0:14:06.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.58,0:14:17.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山又变得寂静了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.47,0:14:21.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它已经到这里来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.27,0:14:22.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那老头
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.35,0:14:25.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,招来不得了的家伙了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.76,0:14:37.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.10,0:14:42.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音是从那边传来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.19,0:14:45.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山顶吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.84,0:15:02.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  还有什么事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.91,0:15:05.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的脚根本没有受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.60,0:15:08.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是在那个一般人不会去的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.35,0:15:11.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,召唤「白蛇」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.11,0:15:13.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.55,0:15:16.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越近的钟声
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.73,0:15:20.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是白蛇的叫声
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.39,0:15:22.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专吃灵兽的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.79,0:15:26.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山的灵兽  沼泽的灵兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.11,0:15:30.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了它们之后取而代之
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.69,0:15:37.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换句话说  是能给这里带来安定的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.04,0:15:41.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么做也是我的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.93,0:15:43.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要阻碍我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.30,0:15:47.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里曾有一只很不错的灵兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.61,0:15:53.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一只有着巨大野猪外表的美丽灵兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.89,0:15:58.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我不好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.68,0:16:03.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了不该做的事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.51,0:16:04.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有话以后再说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.70,0:16:05.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快从这山里出去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.85,0:16:11.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经太迟了  白蛇已经找到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.09,0:16:16.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该由它来取代灵兽的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.42,0:16:17.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对普通人来说太辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.46,0:16:23.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对小玉我也只是教给他一些生存的知识
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.63,0:16:25.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.77,0:16:27.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把你身上的「{\fnyouyuan}葎{\r}」剥离
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.03,0:16:33.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白费力气  即使这样也没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.46,0:16:35.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样总比什么都不做强吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.69,0:16:38.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村里的人要怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.43,0:16:44.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可是十分崇拜  十分需要你的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.40,0:16:48.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过你有些羡慕我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.60,0:16:50.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我也有些羡慕你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.97,0:16:56.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  不要随便就决定去死！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.49,0:16:57.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别做傻事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.63,0:16:59.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也会被卷进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.39,0:17:16.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.68,0:17:18.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无直大师？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.56,0:17:22.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无直大师——！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.47,0:17:41.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  无直来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.72,0:17:43.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无直
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.79,0:17:44.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.59,0:17:46.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.86,0:17:47.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.92,0:17:53.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  各位  大山怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.79,0:17:57.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  今年也发生了几件奇怪的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.05,0:17:59.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.39,0:18:03.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  无直
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.94,0:18:06.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能住下来？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.44,0:18:09.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这村子需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.31,0:18:13.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.18,0:18:15.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.30,0:18:18.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有吸引虫的体质
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.87,0:18:21.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一个地方住下来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.29,0:18:24.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里就变成虫的巢穴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.71,0:18:27.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论无何都不行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.52,0:18:32.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妹妹朔可是一直等着你来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.74,0:18:37.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能在这里和她一起生活吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.30,0:18:43.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果一定要我住下来的话我有个不情之请
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.63,0:18:48.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须得杀死这山上的灵兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.30,0:18:50.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我吃它的肉  之后代替执行它的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.30,0:18:57.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话以我的意识就能让虫无法接近大山
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.42,0:19:01.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我也想住下来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.85,0:19:05.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这种事也必然是无法原谅的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.95,0:19:15.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵兽必经之地的地图和毒药都不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.22,0:19:17.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么时候？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.08,0:19:25.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朔  你去哪里了…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.11,0:19:30.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  牡丹姐给了我这些
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.90,0:19:40.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等一下  我这就拿去下锅
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.10,0:19:44.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会努力做的好吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.63,0:19:46.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朔…朔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.70,0:19:47.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.69,0:19:50.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.15,0:19:54.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定要住在这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.69,0:20:03.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这决不是我的记忆  我在做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.66,0:20:18.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到山顶的时候发现银古先生倒在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.10,0:20:22.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是到处都找不到无直大师
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.18,0:20:25.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然之后又仔细找了找
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.42,0:20:27.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是找不到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.50,0:20:30.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连原来的寺庙也不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.72,0:20:37.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且村里的人谁也记不起无直大师的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.23,0:20:42.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被白蛇吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.95,0:20:46.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵兽的交替就是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.03,0:20:52.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而只有那时在山里的人的记忆还保留着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.01,0:20:59.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  这种召唤虫的药是你调配的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.29,0:21:01.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.37,0:21:04.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  你还蛮厉害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.60,0:21:06.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这些我当然会做
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.54,0:21:09.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是无直大师的弟子嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.87,0:21:13.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.75,0:21:18.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一棵树怎么也砍不倒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.24,0:21:21.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能想个好办法？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.17,0:21:23.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这就去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.55,0:21:26.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.51,0:21:28.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不要在意
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.76,0:21:43.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵  好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.54,0:21:47.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.61,0:21:49.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样总比什么都不做强吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.68,0:21:54.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然没办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.34,0:21:56.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.42,0:22:08.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然壮观啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.22,0:22:12.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你是不会知道人们的心情的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.85,0:22:16.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  白蛇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.59,0:22:34.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是打哈欠一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.46,0:22:37.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白蛇叫了一声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.70,0:22:43.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后静静地陷入沉睡之中
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.66,0:23:37.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)}眇之鱼


