[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-04-24 10:19:06
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Mushishi
Original Script:CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwen,方正细珊瑚简体,35,&H00CEE1D6,&H00000000,&H35000000,&H143F5A42,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,15,134
Style: biaoti,宋体,61,&H00F4F9EC,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: biaoti2,黑体,120,&H000BB9D1,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,550,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: LOGO,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H60000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,134
Style: LOGO2,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&HFF676767,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,2,1,30,30,10,134
Style: OP English,Monotype Corsiva,37,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: OP Chinese,华文隶书,32,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,12,134
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,5,5,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.70,0:00:20.22,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I walked ten thousand miles,ten thousands miles to see you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.37,0:00:27.10,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And ever gasp to breath,I grabbed it just to find you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.12,0:00:33.92,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I climbed up every hill to get to you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.92,0:00:40.75,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I wandered ancient lands to hold just you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:48.86,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And every single step of the way,I paid
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.96,0:01:00.89,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Every single night and day I searched for you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.13,0:01:12.62,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Through sand storms and hazy dawns I reached for you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.70,0:00:20.22,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我步行万里  一万里只为见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.37,0:00:27.10,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}从不向瞬间喘息  紧扼住每一丝遇见的契机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.12,0:00:33.92,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我攀上每一座丘陵  寻找那邂逅的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.92,0:00:40.75,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}徘徊于远古的大陆  而我想占据的  仅仅是你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:48.86,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}一路上留下的每一个脚印  是我付出的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.96,0:01:00.89,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}每一个孤单的黑夜白天里  我寻找着你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.13,0:01:12.62,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}穿越肆虐的沙暴穿越迷雾的拂晓  而后  将是你我的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(466,246)\frz-90}{\fsp-1}www.CAMOE.cn
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.13,0:01:29.47,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.92,0:01:40.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫师？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.79,0:01:42.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鄙人叫银古
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.57,0:01:46.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说你经常做预知梦是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.14,0:01:49.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在附近似乎受到了好评呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.77,0:01:51.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.01,0:01:55.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个梦我想是不是稍微有点问题啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.70,0:01:57.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.56,0:02:00.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕是和虫子有关
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.01,0:02:03.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一种栖息在梦中的虫子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.85,0:02:06.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是它们让你有了预知力
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.78,0:02:09.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且会逐渐增殖
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.38,0:02:12.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是用这种药调整一下数量为好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.13,0:02:16.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在有多少的预知能实现？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.07,0:02:19.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十个中有一个或两个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.49,0:02:21.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再增多的话会有害的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.02,0:02:24.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时就可以喝药了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.01,0:02:28.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过多喝的话就会有毒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.58,0:02:32.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是放着不管的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.42,0:02:33.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可能沉浸于梦中醒不来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.14,0:02:36.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是适量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.76,0:02:39.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要喝哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.32,0:02:44.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快喝完的时候我会再来的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.16,0:02:48.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.00,0:02:51.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你好梦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.12,0:03:01.00,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2000,0)\fscx100}{\pos(535,530)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.12,0:03:01.00,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2000,0)}{\pos(535,225)}枕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.12,0:03:01.00,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2000,0)}{\pos(535,290)}边
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.12,0:03:01.00,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2000,0)}{\pos(535,355)}小
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.12,0:03:01.00,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2000,0)}{\pos(535,420)}径
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.40,0:03:05.40,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}本字幕仅供交流试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版。\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，华盟字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.50,0:03:09.50,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}翻译：馨；校对：X；时间：zipwinmax；\N特效、歌词：Noeru；后期：Noeru、zipwinmax；繁化：黑羽侖人。
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.79,0:03:07.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不能和梦中的人说话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.54,0:03:12.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是与黑暗的国度对话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.84,0:03:25.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那以后好像已经过去了一年了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.78,0:03:30.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里究竟是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.48,0:03:57.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.34,0:04:00.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫师
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.40,0:04:02.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在等你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.14,0:04:05.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事要问你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.75,0:04:09.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就一个人？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.72,0:04:11.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个村子的其他人呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.50,0:04:13.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.23,0:04:15.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.00,0:04:20.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会告诉你的  全部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.19,0:04:38.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉唉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.63,0:04:42.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.89,0:04:48.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.98,0:04:53.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是水脉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.56,0:04:58.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下田地就能灌溉了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.79,0:05:08.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.53,0:05:09.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.83,0:05:11.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金的梦又实现了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.50,0:05:13.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去通知村里的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.79,0:05:22.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村里大家的谢礼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.06,0:05:23.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.89,0:05:27.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.22,0:05:28.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.76,0:05:34.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  时不时送点东西来也不算坏嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.46,0:05:36.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是感谢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.03,0:05:38.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  杨梅
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.77,0:05:40.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  金
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.66,0:05:44.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预知实现的次数增加了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.73,0:05:48.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像那个虫师说的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.89,0:05:53.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信他吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.95,0:05:55.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是虫子让我看到的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.64,0:05:57.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.18,0:06:00.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  假如
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.13,0:06:03.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如那是真的的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.74,0:06:05.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.38,0:06:08.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些药我会喝的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.71,0:06:11.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.52,0:06:13.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.83,0:06:17.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西边的山崖塌方了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.58,0:06:23.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感谢您了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.32,0:06:26.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是没有预言的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.87,0:06:27.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.84,0:06:31.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是  不知道该怎样感谢您
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.70,0:06:39.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.37,0:06:42.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不时会感到害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.59,0:06:47.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当梦见的东西在现实中发生时
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.57,0:06:51.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像是按照我的想法实现的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.23,0:06:52.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.10,0:06:54.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.11,0:06:59.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是上次的谢礼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.18,0:07:00.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请收下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.15,0:07:07.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  也为我们做一个好梦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.09,0:07:10.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.20,0:07:12.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈…别说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.64,0:07:13.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是梦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.51,0:07:16.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再次期待着你的梦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.45,0:07:17.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.39,0:07:21.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  金
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.47,0:07:26.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是你为了帮助大家才有预知的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.41,0:07:30.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是因为托你的福大家才得到幸福吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.51,0:07:33.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么好害怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.77,0:07:38.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.15,0:07:43.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然妻子这样说…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.24,0:07:48.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我对预知的恐惧没有消失
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.61,0:07:50.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逐渐的就把药喝了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.44,0:07:54.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.35,0:07:58.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是海啸…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.97,0:08:12.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眉…眉她
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.53,0:08:13.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在海边
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.35,0:08:15.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.53,0:08:18.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种梦一次都没有梦到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.43,0:08:21.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.12,0:08:24.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的大灾难就一点也预测不到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.49,0:08:31.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眉…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.77,0:08:47.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为愚蠢地喝了药才…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.66,0:08:51.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才没能救到眉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.23,0:08:58.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我停止了喝药
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.85,0:09:04.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后  预知的次数在增加
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.59,0:09:07.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内容也越来越准确了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.71,0:09:09.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  金
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.21,0:09:12.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在门口发现的谢礼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.50,0:09:17.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要打起精神啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.96,0:09:20.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.38,0:09:22.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.99,0:09:30.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了梦吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.73,0:09:31.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多的汗…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.54,0:09:33.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好的梦吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.97,0:09:35.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.92,0:09:38.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是身体不舒服而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.87,0:09:41.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是梦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.34,0:09:47.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  第二天
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.83,0:10:09.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.73,0:10:15.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦中看到的那种病
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.09,0:10:16.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从指尖开始
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.53,0:10:18.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到胳膊都发青
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.60,0:10:20.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扩散到全身
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.37,0:10:22.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像泥块一样崩溃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.42,0:10:25.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.25,0:10:29.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镇上只有我一个人活了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.66,0:10:35.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过你叫银古吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.30,0:10:39.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那梦境成为现实的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.91,0:10:40.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.59,0:10:48.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候  你骗了我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.76,0:10:57.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我体内的不是带来预知梦的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.77,0:11:01.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是将我梦中所见到的东西转化成现实的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.41,0:11:04.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种青色的怪病
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.36,0:11:09.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从我身边的人开始发作的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.32,0:11:11.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妻子…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.22,0:11:13.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邻居…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.10,0:11:15.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直蔓延开去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.32,0:11:22.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那简直就是梦境的重现
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.05,0:11:29.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在为止我做的全部预言
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.66,0:11:33.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的梦境造成的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.10,0:11:36.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.86,0:11:38.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.64,0:11:41.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要骗我？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.68,0:11:50.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我无法根除这种虫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.47,0:11:52.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被寄生了要到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.58,0:11:57.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不伤害宿主的话只能让二者共生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.78,0:12:01.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.96,0:12:03.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果直接说出虫的真面目的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.11,0:12:07.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宿主可能会承受不了而崩溃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.04,0:12:11.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既…既然那样的话我死就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.33,0:12:12.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我那种谎言…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.32,0:12:15.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么让我活下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.09,0:12:16.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.40,0:12:25.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.36,0:12:27.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然已经变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.48,0:12:31.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何我都会找到对付这种虫的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.24,0:12:34.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.77,0:12:38.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦野间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.87,0:12:41.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,栖息在宿主梦中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.05,0:12:44.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候会从梦中出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.17,0:12:46.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.85,0:12:51.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们就成为可将梦转成现实的媒介
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.33,0:12:52.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.33,0:12:55.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些没成真的梦并非无法转为现实
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.97,0:12:58.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是随着它们的增多
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.33,0:13:00.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从梦中出来的次数就越来越多
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.54,0:13:06.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后被实现的范围和规模也越来越大
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.83,0:13:11.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  虫的实体晒到阳光就会消失
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.35,0:13:12.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很脆弱的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.00,0:13:17.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道它们是怎么到现实世界来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.35,0:13:18.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.28,0:13:22.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫子们一定隐藏在某个地方让梦不断延续
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.89,0:13:25.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当宿主醒来的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.14,0:13:28.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫子们又在那里沉睡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.37,0:13:31.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能找到这个地方的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.39,0:13:33.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定能做点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.23,0:13:39.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.31,0:13:43.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种规模的「梦现」先前也没有记录
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.93,0:13:45.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种药的话阻止不了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.53,0:13:48.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是增加药的用量…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.75,0:13:55.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.27,0:14:03.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部的药
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.59,0:14:04.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都喝了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.03,0:14:05.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.99,0:14:06.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿解毒剂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.76,0:14:07.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.26,0:14:17.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经够了  我不该活在这世上…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.50,0:14:37.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼球在动
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.94,0:14:40.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始做梦了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.01,0:14:43.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.64,0:14:44.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦话？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.28,0:14:48.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是你的过错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.37,0:14:52.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是虫的过错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.55,0:14:56.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双方都只是为了生存
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.47,0:15:00.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.02,0:15:03.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别死
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.69,0:15:06.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有做错什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.99,0:15:12.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.21,0:15:13.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大雁吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.00,0:15:14.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.72,0:15:19.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是梦话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.95,0:15:21.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点逻辑也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.16,0:15:23.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在到底在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.21,0:15:25.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点回来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.98,0:15:28.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一片芦苇塘中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.11,0:15:30.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.56,0:15:32.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.93,0:15:37.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.69,0:15:38.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种耳鸣？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.82,0:15:48.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.30,0:15:52.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为刚才的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.11,0:15:53.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙的梦转换成现实了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.96,0:15:55.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.41,0:15:57.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来像是大雁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.77,0:16:03.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些全部都是梦野间
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.78,0:16:32.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.95,0:16:35.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眉…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.63,0:16:37.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎您回来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.81,0:16:40.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.49,0:16:48.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.91,0:16:51.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对不起你们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.08,0:16:54.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定在恨我吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.29,0:16:58.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你们和大家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.81,0:17:00.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀死了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.04,0:17:03.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了  金
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.76,0:17:06.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.19,0:17:09.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有做错什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.61,0:17:18.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有谁在吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.86,0:17:26.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.78,0:17:32.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屏风上好象有什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.94,0:17:34.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.79,0:17:35.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.53,0:17:37.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁来…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.52,0:17:40.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显示着的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.22,0:17:42.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的梦吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.04,0:17:48.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦是从枕边出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.46,0:17:52.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.38,0:17:55.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.33,0:18:00.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快起来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.68,0:18:04.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去打水…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.74,0:18:14.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦是通过枕头出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.64,0:18:18.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫子们隐藏的某个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.24,0:18:20.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当宿主醒来的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.69,0:18:22.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫子们又在那里沉睡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.57,0:18:33.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.75,0:18:35.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.02,0:18:44.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的虫子们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.43,0:18:46.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.57,0:19:16.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.83,0:19:19.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.10,0:19:43.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏做了应急处理
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.51,0:19:46.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样好像已经得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.76,0:20:10.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成这样  你知道是怎么回事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.11,0:20:13.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明只是砍了枕头一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.29,0:20:18.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.66,0:20:22.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「枕头」这个词汇源自「魂居之处」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.93,0:20:24.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经有「魂居之处」之说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.63,0:20:30.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人活着有三分之一的时间要和枕头接触
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.93,0:20:33.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人认为那是人的魂魄所在的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.50,0:20:38.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以那里也就成了梦野间的巢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.69,0:20:41.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连接梦和现实的通道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.12,0:20:44.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毁坏枕头
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.21,0:20:46.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就等于伤害你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.62,0:20:56.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦和现实之间是魂居之所
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.11,0:21:00.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁能通过这个地方的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.10,0:21:03.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能梦见那个禁断的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.15,0:21:11.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那以后
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.36,0:21:14.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人又再次做起了磨刀师的老本行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.68,0:21:18.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们都说他手艺很好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.18,0:21:20.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.83,0:21:23.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他心里好像有什么事情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.44,0:21:27.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候突然来回挥舞着刀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.22,0:21:30.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后把刀锋刺向了自己…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.04,0:21:38.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.68,0:21:42.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人很惧怕睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.51,0:21:47.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕睡着的时候自己的灵魂不知道会去了哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.90,0:21:53.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从那个男人斩了枕头
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.19,0:21:57.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就再没有做过梦了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.72,0:23:37.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)}「游荡的沼泽」


