[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-04-24 20:20:13
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:虫师
Original Script:华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwen,方正细珊瑚简体,35,&H00CEE1D6,&H00000000,&H35000000,&H143F5A42,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,15,134
Style: biaoti,宋体,61,&H00F4F9EC,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: biaoti2,黑体,120,&H00673669,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,550,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: LOGO,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H60000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,134
Style: LOGO2,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&HFF676767,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,2,1,30,30,10,134
Style: OP English,Monotype Corsiva,37,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: OP Chinese,华文隶书,32,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,12,134
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,5,5,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.60,0:00:20.12,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I walked ten thousand miles,ten thousands miles to see you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.27,0:00:27.00,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And ever gasp to breath,I grabbed it just to find you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.02,0:00:33.82,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I climbed up every hill to get to you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:40.65,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I wandered ancient lands to hold just you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:48.76,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And every single step of the way,I paid
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:01:00.79,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Every single night and day I searched for you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.03,0:01:12.52,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Through sand storms and hazy dawns I reached for you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.60,0:00:20.12,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我步行万里  一万里只为见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.27,0:00:27.00,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}从不向瞬间喘息  紧扼住每一丝遇见的契机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.02,0:00:33.82,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我攀上每一座丘陵  寻找那邂逅的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:40.65,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}徘徊于远古的大陆  而我想占据的  仅仅是你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:48.76,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}一路上留下的每一个脚印  是我付出的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:01:00.79,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}每一个孤单的黑夜白天里  我寻找着你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.03,0:01:12.52,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}穿越肆虐的沙暴穿越迷雾的拂晓  而后  将是你我的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(466,246)\frz-90}{\fsp-1}www.CAMOE.cn
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx100}{\pos(550,545)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,130)}吸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,190)}露
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,250)}水
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,310)}的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,370)}种
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,430)}群
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,130)}吸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,190)}露
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,250)}水
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,310)}的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,370)}种
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.02,0:02:49.91,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(3000,0)\fscx95}{\pos(550,430)}群
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.50,0:02:54.50,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}本字幕仅供交流试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版。\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，华盟字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.60,0:02:58.60,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}翻译：馨；校对：X；时间：zipwinmax；\N特效、歌词：Noeru；后期：Noeru、zipwinmax；繁化：黑羽侖人。
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.56,0:01:41.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳升起  然后落下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.65,0:01:45.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花朵盛开  然后凋零
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.16,0:01:50.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳落下  然后升起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.74,0:01:54.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花朵重新盛开
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.95,0:01:59.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但和昨日相比又不同…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.23,0:02:10.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  还没到吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.87,0:02:13.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就到了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.83,0:02:19.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…既然是医生介绍的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.09,0:02:21.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您应该也是医生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.89,0:02:25.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是虫师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.18,0:02:28.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样不信任我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.97,0:02:30.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就如你刚才听到的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.54,0:02:32.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那确实是我的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.43,0:02:35.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  这个职业我第一次听说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.76,0:02:38.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  能看到岛了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.94,0:02:54.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋  你听说过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.59,0:02:56.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去到海的另一边的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.22,0:02:58.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一片广阔而美丽的土地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.35,0:03:01.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家可以在那里幸福地生活
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.33,0:03:05.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候我带你一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.81,0:03:09.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  别再苦着个脸了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.89,0:03:14.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.25,0:03:17.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就该这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.90,0:03:24.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  为什么只是远远的看着岛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.81,0:03:26.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上潮向就要改变了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.35,0:03:29.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是复杂的潮目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.35,0:03:29.58,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6}（潮目：暖流和寒流的分界线）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.07,0:03:31.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水流也很急
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.36,0:03:34.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入岛就只有大潮的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.18,0:03:36.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转眼的工夫就到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.90,0:03:40.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.83,0:03:42.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很简单的就进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.06,0:03:44.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请小心头
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.60,0:04:00.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是渔家的孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.64,0:04:03.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个岛里没有渔民
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.14,0:04:07.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为每个月安全进出岛的日子只有一天呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.00,0:04:15.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都是岩石呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.86,0:04:19.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这是个土地稀少的贫瘠岛屿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.11,0:04:22.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在想办法活着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.48,0:04:25.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有「活神仙」这个心灵支柱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.29,0:04:27.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「活神仙」？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.34,0:04:28.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  有人  快藏起来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.42,0:04:32.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  这个不能吃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.90,0:04:34.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是献给「活神仙」的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.19,0:04:37.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须先治好你的病
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.62,0:04:40.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  忍一忍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.70,0:04:42.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就会好起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.92,0:04:46.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  我们为什么必须藏起来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.94,0:04:52.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想见见那个「活神仙」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.29,0:04:54.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子只是个普通人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.75,0:04:57.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请帮帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.11,0:05:00.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都被骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.20,0:05:07.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.68,0:05:17.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旁边是她的父亲  这个岛的岛主
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.63,0:05:22.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的身上每天都有奇迹发生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.95,0:05:26.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是信徒参拜的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.23,0:06:00.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼吸完全停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.55,0:06:06.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个看到了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.30,0:06:08.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看不见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.26,0:06:12.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快吸了这些香气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.27,0:06:17.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心中的烦恼和病患都会一扫而空
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.99,0:06:22.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是不老不死之神的赐福
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.79,0:06:25.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后还会恢复原来的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.74,0:06:29.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上醒来后就像什么也没发生一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.27,0:06:34.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然和你说的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.81,0:06:36.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我也吃了一惊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.54,0:06:39.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样病就能治好？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.80,0:06:41.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那根本就是一派胡言！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.32,0:06:44.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈就是没有治好而死了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.76,0:06:49.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田里的收成几乎  全部献给了「活神仙」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.99,0:06:52.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信奉「活神仙」的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.75,0:06:55.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最早是由岛主一族的人提起的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.06,0:06:57.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掌握潮水的变化
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.21,0:07:01.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先进入岛屿的好像是岛主的先祖
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.37,0:07:03.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是从那之后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.71,0:07:07.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岛主一族代代都会出现「活神仙」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.38,0:07:10.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到这消息的人们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.16,0:07:12.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看作是这岛屿的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.06,0:07:15.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也越来越多的迁居到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.04,0:07:18.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个「活神仙」死了后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.11,0:07:21.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又出现新的「活神仙」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.84,0:07:23.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成这样不过半年时间
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.04,0:07:26.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就有谣言说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.91,0:07:28.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸入「活神仙」发出的香气
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.08,0:07:31.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使不治之症也能治好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.65,0:07:35.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本不相信
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.27,0:07:39.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.77,0:07:44.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.25,0:07:50.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又和外面的人一起玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.77,0:07:53.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  有重要的事和你说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.73,0:08:00.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候前代「活神仙」刚刚过世一个月
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.64,0:08:05.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天是起潮的日子  所以我记得很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.19,0:08:11.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我听到了他们的谈话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.21,0:08:13.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「昨天的事情我不记得了」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.22,0:08:16.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「又有人死了」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.67,0:08:22.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过了一段时间后我终于明白了事情真相
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.41,0:08:26.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  又有治好的人出现了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.56,0:08:27.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.45,0:08:30.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是自我暗示起的效果吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.44,0:08:34.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本就没指望的阿古屋
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.98,0:08:37.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也能起些作用就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.39,0:08:40.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能饶恕他们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.67,0:08:43.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以决定出岛寻找能治好阿古屋的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.20,0:08:46.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗他们说不再回来而出岛了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.99,0:08:50.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是岛主知道我回来了  一定会起疑的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.67,0:08:54.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  银古先生  你也很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.52,0:08:58.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了麻烦的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.74,0:08:59.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.94,0:09:01.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能这样再让大家被骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.54,0:09:03.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.46,0:09:09.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  我帮你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.72,0:09:11.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽快让我见一下本人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.88,0:09:25.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脉搏跳动的很快
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.11,0:09:29.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体温也比常人高
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.89,0:09:44.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.81,0:09:46.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜡烛就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.31,0:09:49.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.24,0:09:53.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了  是虫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.42,0:10:03.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,产子后成虫死掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.98,0:10:05.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.05,0:10:08.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,病因是寄生在鼻腔里的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.43,0:10:12.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道拿掉后会不会好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.96,0:10:15.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,患者只有这个孩子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.03,0:10:17.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他几个人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.62,0:10:21.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被藏在岛崖那边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.24,0:10:26.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们大家也和阿古屋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.81,0:10:30.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前就有零星的这种病人出现
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.93,0:10:37.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,历代的岛主发现有这样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.15,0:10:39.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把他们藏在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.54,0:10:43.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为接近「活神仙」的狂热信仰者
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.25,0:10:47.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的家人都会为他们祝福
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.07,0:10:53.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为自己家族出了脱离苦海的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.38,0:11:08.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果没有新的发现啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.20,0:11:12.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那个孩子发病的时候也是涨潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.53,0:11:17.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涨水的时候才能去的地方有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.92,0:11:21.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岛崖前面的洞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.85,0:11:25.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那附近
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.37,0:11:30.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在找什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.01,0:11:32.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.14,0:11:35.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  这家伙也被寄生了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.38,0:11:37.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该还有其它的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.23,0:11:39.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到附近到处找找
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.04,0:11:46.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又找到了两只
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.82,0:11:48.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  先放在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.09,0:11:56.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈岐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.86,0:12:02.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治疗的方法找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.35,0:12:09.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  阿古屋  安静点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.40,0:12:10.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.25,0:12:14.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.71,0:12:30.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.38,0:12:35.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈岐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.70,0:12:37.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.09,0:12:39.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.50,0:12:41.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.21,0:12:52.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？父亲为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.51,0:12:54.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋  离开小岛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.44,0:12:57.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有三天就是大潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.03,0:13:00.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间你先把病好了的消息瞒着岛主
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.87,0:13:06.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我喜欢这个小岛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.89,0:13:10.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲一定也不会放过我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.58,0:13:12.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.11,0:13:15.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定会有其他人代替的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.70,0:13:18.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那个原因治好了就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.96,0:13:21.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这个岛上根治这种由虫带来的病啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.66,0:13:25.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为「活神仙」时候的事  还记得吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.39,0:13:29.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天我被父亲叫去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.29,0:13:36.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋  这是为你准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.96,0:13:41.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.90,0:13:45.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很香吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.16,0:13:46.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.44,0:13:55.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外表像牵牛花  香味很浓的花
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.18,0:13:57.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在悬崖的那个洞里见过
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.09,0:14:00.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面很暗  但确实有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.54,0:14:02.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是原因
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.12,0:14:05.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天后吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.57,0:14:09.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  总之一定不要让岛主发现才行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.96,0:14:10.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.41,0:14:13.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前先扮演好「活神仙」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.32,0:14:31.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.34,0:14:32.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有以前的感觉了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.63,0:14:40.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得非常不安
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.85,0:14:42.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为「活神仙」的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.37,0:14:46.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始衰弱着  睡着度过每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.66,0:14:49.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却总是觉得生活很充实
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.34,0:14:50.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明只是闭着眼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.26,0:14:54.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却感到很害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.37,0:15:00.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使醒来也只是继续昨天的现实而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.29,0:15:06.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对眼前虚无飘渺的时间洪流束手无策
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.91,0:15:12.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像是按照虫的时间来生活的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.95,0:15:18.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种虫会使宿主体内的时间和自己同步
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.60,0:15:22.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生物的寿命根据种类不同而各异
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.52,0:15:25.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是一生中脉搏跳动的次数据说是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.24,0:15:29.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不同的只是体内时间流逝的密度
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.76,0:15:32.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种虫的寿命大约是一天
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.41,0:15:36.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你每天都经历着这些
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.05,0:15:40.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.64,0:15:53.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一天  每一刻  对我都是新的开始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.81,0:15:59.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有烦恼  没有忧愁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.13,0:16:12.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里  总是很充实
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.69,0:16:20.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再过半个时辰就能进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.57,0:16:27.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.32,0:16:30.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.41,0:16:33.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个时候你应该很衰弱才对
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.87,0:16:38.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父…父亲  我的病不知道为何已经好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.00,0:16:39.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.23,0:16:43.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈岐好像回来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.65,0:16:46.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像知道他去了哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.46,0:16:51.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  今天是大潮的日子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.93,0:17:06.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长在黑暗中的牵牛花  好浓的气味啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.23,0:17:09.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个部分就是虫的巢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.74,0:17:14.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄生在生物上的虫就是把卵产在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.42,0:17:17.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银古先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.03,0:17:24.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「活神仙」大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.21,0:17:25.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.43,0:17:30.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  请告诉我岛崖的洞在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.51,0:17:35.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  「活神仙」大人会说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.33,0:17:36.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.28,0:17:38.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后会都告诉你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.47,0:17:39.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你们
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.59,0:17:42.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救奈岐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.88,0:17:48.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈岐  你在这里做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.84,0:17:50.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这混蛋  居然还这么悠闲…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.78,0:17:51.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.46,0:17:52.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别激动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.90,0:17:55.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管他  这种人不会有好下场
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.82,0:18:01.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉迷于利用虫而不能自拔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.62,0:18:04.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终究会自我毁灭的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.99,0:18:07.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用虫的结果就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.62,0:18:12.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在挑衅  是不是有什么想法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.55,0:18:13.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来  奈岐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.03,0:18:14.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.97,0:18:17.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.70,0:18:18.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.18,0:18:20.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便把他们的尸体扔到海里喂鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.55,0:18:27.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.45,0:18:36.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他手里拿着花
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.92,0:18:37.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.70,0:18:39.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和阿古屋说的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.11,0:18:41.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.13,0:18:49.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像没人追来  但是好像涨潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.78,0:18:52.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  最多支撑半个时辰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.93,0:18:58.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人  找到了  是奈岐他们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.67,0:19:02.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  让开点  我们把缝隙砸开
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.06,0:19:19.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.48,0:19:24.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲  父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.36,0:19:29.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为你准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.35,0:19:30.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再苦着个脸了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.81,0:19:39.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很香吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.64,0:19:41.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.18,0:19:48.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.29,0:19:51.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.49,0:19:53.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.32,0:19:58.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…呢  奈岐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.76,0:20:03.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就能…活着到…那个世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.82,0:20:07.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比以前寄生的更严重了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.18,0:20:09.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要取出来的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.70,0:20:15.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经够了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.96,0:20:32.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿古屋真正开心的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.18,0:20:35.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在身为「活神仙」的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.93,0:20:47.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳升起  然后落下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.19,0:20:51.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花朵盛开  然后凋零
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.95,0:20:56.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳落下  然后升起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.21,0:21:00.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花朵重新盛开
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.34,0:21:04.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽和昨日相比又不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.70,0:21:08.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但花朵今日依然美丽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.59,0:21:17.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时  逃过了涨潮的银古先生在岛上又待了一个月
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.14,0:21:22.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此期间把岛崖那里得这种病的人都治好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.53,0:21:27.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  在下次涨潮岛崖下的洞穴再次打开的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.12,0:21:30.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定又有人会成为「活神仙」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.43,0:21:35.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕有人并不会感谢我的治疗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.39,0:21:38.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总会再闻那些花吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.28,0:21:40.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像阿古屋那样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.25,0:21:42.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.82,0:21:48.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对眼前虚无飘渺的时间洪流  束手无策
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.20,0:21:52.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有这样的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.19,0:21:57.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今往后  不知道该怎样活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.59,0:22:00.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像普通人一样活就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.47,0:22:04.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能捕到鱼的话就好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.57,0:22:07.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时间就乘船出海
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.28,0:22:09.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫大家一起把那个洞填了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.05,0:22:11.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是什么容易的事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.55,0:22:17.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  对于你来说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.77,0:22:25.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很漫长的时间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.72,0:23:37.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)}「雨后彩虹」


