[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-05-06 14:57:17
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:虫师
Original Script:华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwen,方正细珊瑚简体,35,&H00CEE1D6,&H00000000,&H35000000,&H143F5A42,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,15,134
Style: biaoti,宋体,61,&H00F4F9EC,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: biaoti2,黑体,120,&H00353969,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,550,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,0,134
Style: LOGO,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H60000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,3,1,30,30,10,134
Style: LOGO2,方正粗宋_GBK,26,&H00F5F8F8,&H00000000,&H00000000,&HFF676767,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,2,1,30,30,10,134
Style: OP English,Monotype Corsiva,37,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: OP Chinese,华文隶书,32,&H00CCCCCC,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,12,134
Style: jinggao,方正准圆_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,5,5,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.60,0:00:20.12,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I walked ten thousand miles,ten thousands miles to see you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.27,0:00:27.00,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And ever gasp to breath,I grabbed it just to find you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.02,0:00:33.82,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I climbed up every hill to get to you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:40.65,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}I wandered ancient lands to hold just you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:48.76,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}And every single step of the way,I paid
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:01:00.79,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Every single night and day I searched for you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.03,0:01:12.52,OP English,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}Through sand storms and hazy dawns I reached for you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.60,0:00:20.12,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我步行万里  一万里只为见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.27,0:00:27.00,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}从不向瞬间喘息  紧扼住每一丝遇见的契机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.02,0:00:33.82,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}我攀上每一座丘陵  寻找那邂逅的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:40.65,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}徘徊于远古的大陆  而我想占据的  仅仅是你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:48.76,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}一路上留下的每一个脚印  是我付出的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.86,0:01:00.79,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}每一个孤单的黑夜白天里  我寻找着你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.03,0:01:12.52,OP Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}穿越肆虐的沙暴穿越迷雾的拂晓  而后  将是你我的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(466,246)\frz-90}{\fsp-1}www.CAMOE.cn
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,100)}{\fsp0}┼─
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,145)}{\fsp0}华
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,185)}{\fsp0}盟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,228)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,263)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,298)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,333)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,368)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,403)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(230,425)}{\fsp0\fscy50}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(344,425)}{\fsp3}─字幕社{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(160,425)}{\fsp0}─────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,228)}{\fsp3}CASO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(380,248)}{\fsp0}────
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,218)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.03,0:01:29.37,LOGO2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs42\fad(4000,5000)}{\pos(458,248)}{\fsp0}│
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)\fscx100}{\pos(535,516)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(535,228)}栖
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(535,288)}砚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)\fscx96}{\pos(536,348)}之
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(535,408)}白
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(535,228)}栖
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(535,288)}砚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)\fscx96}{\pos(536,348)}之
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.99,0:02:23.92,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2200,0)}{\pos(535,408)}白
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.30,0:02:28.30,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}本字幕仅供交流试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版。\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，华盟字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.40,0:02:32.40,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)}翻译、校对：X；时间、特效、歌词：Noeru；\N后期：Noeru、zipwinmax；繁化：黑羽侖人。
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.65,0:01:44.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.09,0:01:47.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生现在在给我奶奶看病呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.19,0:01:52.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  到处都是稀有的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.34,0:01:56.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.31,0:01:59.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.85,0:02:14.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  好漂亮的砚台
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.45,0:02:32.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.32,0:02:37.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生  帮帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.51,0:02:39.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生  医生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.73,0:02:41.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家的孩子…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.11,0:02:51.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了晚上就突然说「冷」啊「冷」的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.87,0:02:55.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天和他一起玩的邻家的孩子也出现了同样的状况
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.32,0:02:58.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.80,0:03:00.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体温很低
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.55,0:03:04.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.21,0:03:06.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再拿一床被子来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.00,0:03:07.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就去拿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.25,0:03:09.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连呼出的气都是冷的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.97,0:03:14.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.46,0:03:20.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.60,0:03:22.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.24,0:03:26.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天  在医生的仓库里…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.74,0:03:30.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们碰了仓库里的东西吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.51,0:03:34.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  砚台…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.42,0:03:36.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砚台？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.14,0:03:49.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.20,0:03:50.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  我在这边  银古
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.31,0:03:54.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.99,0:03:58.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太大意了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.02,0:04:02.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来为了不让村里的人看到而藏得很隐蔽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.94,0:04:05.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,患者有什么反应？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.91,0:04:10.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很衰弱  给他喝热水暖身子也没用
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.68,0:04:13.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.34,0:04:16.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从熟识的收藏家那里买来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.99,0:04:18.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外观很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.54,0:04:21.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说是某种虫的化石做成的砚台
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.37,0:04:24.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫的化石？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.37,0:04:27.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能有那种东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.70,0:04:31.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们好像连尸骸都不会留下的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.43,0:04:36.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种来路不明的东西以后还是少买
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.77,0:04:37.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.14,0:04:43.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了  你收集的可都是异世界的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.54,0:04:48.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.61,0:04:57.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是化石
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.48,0:05:00.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看到活着的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.16,0:05:04.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是那些患者到底做了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.52,0:05:08.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们对砚台做了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.07,0:05:11.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们试着磨墨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.00,0:05:15.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？你拿着那个做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.44,0:05:19.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么  只不过是砚台嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.01,0:05:22.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  一定是特别的砚台
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.18,0:05:24.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  那边有水耶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.15,0:05:26.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试着磨磨看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.82,0:05:32.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是别磨了  医生会生气的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.23,0:05:34.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一会啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.56,0:05:41.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有…什么很冷的东西出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.20,0:05:45.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我也有感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.74,0:05:51.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受到刺激就会再生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.47,0:05:53.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入人体后  导致体温下降
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.26,0:05:56.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光知道这些很难给这种虫定性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.67,0:05:59.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.43,0:06:03.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前的拥有者知道些什么吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.78,0:06:05.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他最多只会知道刚才那些
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.34,0:06:12.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像以前的持有者都因为用过砚台而死掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.30,0:06:16.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还活着的  只有砚台的制作者吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.27,0:06:19.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铭牌在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.30,0:06:21.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调查一下的话就知道住在哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.80,0:06:23.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.55,0:06:25.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西就先放我这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.81,0:06:28.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.80,0:06:29.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.41,0:06:52.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是难找啊  应该就在附近
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.75,0:06:57.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.34,0:07:00.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过她已经不做砚台了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.14,0:07:03.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.42,0:07:04.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.02,0:07:06.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.21,0:07:10.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然手艺很好  但是家里没有其他人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.42,0:07:30.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.20,0:07:34.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是你做的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.58,0:07:40.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面确实印有我的铭牌
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.92,0:07:44.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…有问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.52,0:07:48.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  有人因为这个砚台而痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.00,0:07:53.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你把知道的都告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.08,0:08:03.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一天终于来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.53,0:08:10.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在找这个砚台…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.96,0:08:17.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据我所知  有三个人使用过这个砚台
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.26,0:08:23.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说他们都在一个月内死去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.08,0:08:30.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是  身为制砚名匠的父亲病倒不久的事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.88,0:08:35.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一个未婚夫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.77,0:08:39.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他住在山那边的村里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.68,0:08:41.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和父亲有生意上的来往
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.41,0:08:48.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和他的双亲都一致反对我继承父业
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.73,0:08:52.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnyouyuan}鏨{\r}  你还是要…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.88,0:08:55.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该明白我的心情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.94,0:08:58.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和父亲都很了解这里的石头
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.99,0:09:00.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.91,0:09:02.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一个人干不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.31,0:09:06.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上现在的订购量也下降了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.55,0:09:10.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会做出和父亲一样的砚台
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.55,0:09:12.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.52,0:09:17.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.71,0:09:25.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能做出让他也能承认的东西的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.21,0:09:26.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.16,0:09:30.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那之后我不断制作砚台
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.52,0:09:35.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  一直做不出什么好作品
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.07,0:09:40.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.61,0:09:42.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挖出了一块石头
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.46,0:09:44.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它有一种不可思议的魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.12,0:09:46.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸引着我全身心投入传作中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.10,0:09:50.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做出来的砚台
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.08,0:09:53.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堪称杰作
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.14,0:09:57.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形状很好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.25,0:10:00.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你试着来磨下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.57,0:10:20.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.64,0:10:21.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.09,0:10:25.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从砚台出来一些像烟的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.89,0:10:27.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  那里还有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.90,0:10:31.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.31,0:10:32.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.92,0:10:44.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墨渣也沉淀的很好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.97,0:10:48.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话就能安心让你继承了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.11,0:10:59.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸进那烟雾几日后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.28,0:11:01.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体也没什么不对劲
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.62,0:11:04.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只有我能看见…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.52,0:11:06.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他看这个砚台的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.18,0:11:08.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也许会重新考虑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.51,0:11:15.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.79,0:11:18.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这砚台能放我这里吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.62,0:11:20.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试着说服我的父母吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.82,0:11:22.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.00,0:11:27.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  如果有好消息我会给你写信的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.44,0:11:34.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  一个月后收到的信传达了他的死讯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.18,0:11:39.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从我把砚台寄放在他那里那天开始
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.77,0:11:41.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他开始喊冷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.00,0:11:46.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说得了体温持续下降的不可思议的怪病
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.56,0:11:52.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后那砚台  被称作是不吉利的东西卖到古玩店去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.78,0:12:01.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找那个古董商时已经转手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.86,0:12:04.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去了行踪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.74,0:12:10.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且在中介和古董商之间传出谣言
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.20,0:12:15.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「由于那个砚台的缘故  又有人死了」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.43,0:12:23.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后  我父亲也去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.87,0:12:26.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不再做砚台了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.54,0:12:28.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很想帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.33,0:12:32.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的也只是这些
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.08,0:12:37.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我已经抓住线索了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.65,0:12:38.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.09,0:12:41.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.74,0:12:44.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我赶时间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.60,0:12:45.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.57,0:12:49.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那个砚台卖给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.50,0:12:52.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想亲手毁掉它
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.00,0:12:55.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我的东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.70,0:12:58.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干脆你也一起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.19,0:13:19.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘记你收集的东西都是异世界的东西了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.75,0:13:24.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我也清楚…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.89,0:13:28.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很少看你愁眉苦脸呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.55,0:13:30.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.93,0:13:33.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还有心思拿我开心么…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.77,0:13:38.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  一定能帮上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.78,0:13:47.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木炭和…火炉？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.67,0:13:50.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锅  还有架子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.24,0:13:52.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.18,0:13:57.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个砚台里的是一种叫作「噬云」的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.78,0:14:00.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和积雨云的形状很像
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.04,0:14:02.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就如其名一样是云型
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.62,0:14:07.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是吸收空气中的水和冰晶变成雪或雹降下来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.75,0:14:09.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是为什么当时明明没有云
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.03,0:14:11.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能看到雹的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.91,0:14:16.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  这种虫不会自己移动  必须靠风的传播
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.66,0:14:19.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在没有云的季节就会萎缩
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.49,0:14:22.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉到地表冰冻自身进入假死状态
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.13,0:14:26.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集结成这种石头一样的形态
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.46,0:14:29.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得花上万年的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.63,0:14:32.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你把它做成砚台使它们重见天日
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.07,0:14:36.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并浇上水后使它们复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.71,0:14:41.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  我们现在怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.92,0:14:43.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnyouyuan}鏨{\r}小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.13,0:14:47.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你是在山上制砚的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.02,0:14:50.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸了那烟而没事也许就是因为这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.02,0:14:55.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把患者带到这里最高的山峰上去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.71,0:15:13.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好  快给他喝热水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.05,0:15:13.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.17,0:15:16.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经变得温热了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.04,0:15:18.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先去把水热一热
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.04,0:15:19.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.23,0:15:32.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生  还要继续往上走吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.89,0:15:35.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经呼吸困难了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.24,0:15:38.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们一定也很辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.73,0:15:41.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银古
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.95,0:15:48.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.72,0:16:01.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家  快屏住呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.24,0:16:46.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这孩子的面色…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.11,0:16:51.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体不冷了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.17,0:16:57.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体温恢复了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.72,0:17:02.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于搞定…了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.20,0:17:04.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.48,0:17:09.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底…为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.39,0:17:13.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是气压
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.91,0:17:17.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「噬云」是云状的浮体生物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.53,0:17:21.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说应该和云的重量相近
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.99,0:17:24.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来到高处的话就能让它们出来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.63,0:17:27.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本来就住在高处
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.15,0:17:31.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸进去的烟会慢慢漏出来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.68,0:17:33.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你制砚时经常翻越山岭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.06,0:17:36.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时你体内的「噬云」就完全出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.78,0:17:40.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.85,0:17:41.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.22,0:17:51.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.98,0:17:56.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.40,0:18:11.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归根结底
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.50,0:18:13.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为人们对这种危险的东西的好奇惹出来的麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.47,0:18:16.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会负起一切责任把它毁掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.24,0:18:21.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是对付它的办法也不知道  也没办法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.78,0:18:23.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太没戒心了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.43,0:18:25.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能说那边的东西全都是安全的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.81,0:18:27.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那和你没关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.30,0:18:30.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  银古
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.49,0:18:31.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也说两句啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.15,0:18:33.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要破坏砚台的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.53,0:18:36.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就得杀死其中的虫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.18,0:18:39.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊  就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.29,0:18:42.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  虫可是没有罪的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.90,0:18:48.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  这么漂亮的一个砚台毁掉岂不可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.92,0:18:52.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说它对你来说不就像自己的孩子一样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.99,0:18:54.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.73,0:18:56.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法释怀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.25,0:19:00.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为你把带有虫的砚台带到了这个世上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.16,0:19:06.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  把虫从砚台里放出来怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.81,0:19:08.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.08,0:19:11.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  这个是我的砚台
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.51,0:19:14.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次事件  化野
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.49,0:19:16.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有很大责任
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.99,0:19:18.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就当作为教训吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.05,0:19:22.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说  这个砚台也是一级品
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.21,0:19:24.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.15,0:20:27.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.44,0:20:29.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.39,0:20:34.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.16,0:20:35.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是冰雹
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.60,0:20:35.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.16,0:20:38.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明云都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.77,0:20:39.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底从哪里来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.66,0:20:56.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下子村里的屋顶的修理费就成大问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.30,0:21:00.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我赔你也行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.93,0:21:03.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会干一辈子还你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.86,0:21:06.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你怎么还
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.39,0:21:10.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续做砚台就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.79,0:21:12.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就能在这里立足
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.29,0:21:15.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.85,0:21:18.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先订一个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.33,0:21:21.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  就算里面有虫也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.02,0:21:24.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是不知悔改啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.32,0:21:39.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.23,0:21:46.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后也许要花一点时间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.47,0:21:53.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  这雹子几时才停啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.09,0:21:57.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该做饭了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.76,0:23:37.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)}沉睡之山


