[Script Info]
Title:oreimo
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00287ED7,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HC8000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正康体_GBK,40,&H0006BD82,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: NEXT,方正康体_GBK,42,&H0034C774,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: NEXT2,DFGPOP1-W12,40,&H004DD481,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,15,&H0019CA69,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HB4FFFFFF,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,10,20,7,1
Style: OPCN,方正准圆_GBK,17,&H0019CA69,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HB4FFFFFF,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,8,25,7,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00287ED7,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,5,1
Style: EDJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,16,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00585858,&HB4D7EDFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,15,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00585858,&HB4D7EDFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,15,25,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,15,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&H64FFFFFF,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正大标宋_GBK,15,&H003C3CB8,&HFF0000FF,&H50EAEAEA,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: INJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,14,&H0080F2F1,&HFF0000FF,&H00C06530,&H50B180C5,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,7,10,20,10,1
Style: INCN,方正准圆_GBK,15,&H0080F2F1,&HFF0000FF,&H00C06530,&H50B180C5,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,7,8,25,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:02:46.27,0:02:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.21,0:01:57.46,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(130,330)\fs38\fsp-6\fad(800,0)}我不可能和学妹留下一整个夏天的回忆
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.52,0:00:36.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた物語が　始まるの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.38,0:00:45.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}記憶の遠く走ってた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.07,0:00:52.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}きらめく影法師も忘れられなくて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.94,0:00:59.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}ずっと　君の目線の先に気付かずに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.87,0:01:04.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}勝手な理想だけ膨らんじゃって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.14,0:01:07.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}前見えないの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.19,0:01:14.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}想いはやっぱり　透明だけど重くて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:21.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}少しずつ　溶かしてくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.62,0:01:24.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた手を繋ごう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.92,0:01:28.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}私とまた夢を見よう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.47,0:01:32.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}傷だらけでも今を抱いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.43,0:01:35.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}はじまりにしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.78,0:01:39.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた声交わそう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.23,0:01:42.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}私とまた笑い合おう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.72,0:01:48.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}蕾のままだった　明日を咲かせるの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.93,0:01:52.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君の近くで
Comment: 0,0:00:04.00,0:00:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.52,0:00:36.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我与你之间又有全新的  故事开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.38,0:00:45.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}在记忆的彼方徘徊不定
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.07,0:00:52.78,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}那闪烁的人影也一直无法忘怀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.94,0:00:59.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}从来  对于你的视线我毫不在意
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.87,0:01:04.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}只是执着于那偏执的理想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.14,0:01:07.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}看不见前方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.19,0:01:14.41,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我的思念一如坚冰  透明却又厚重
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:21.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}如今却逐渐  因你而融化
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.62,0:01:24.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一次牵手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.92,0:01:28.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一起做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.47,0:01:32.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}即使满身疮痍也要拥抱现在
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.43,0:01:35.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}然后再一次启程
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.78,0:01:39.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一次交流
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.23,0:01:42.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一起欢笑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.72,0:01:48.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我的明天一如  花蕾含苞待放
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.93,0:01:52.58,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}就在你的身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.64,0:22:10.62,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}気付いてる？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.94,0:22:20.36,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}彷徨う孤独　闇の狭間で
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.84,0:22:26.95,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}契約重ね　繋ぐココロ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.64,0:22:34.15,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}光と影の交鎖点では
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.57,0:22:40.11,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}貴方と踊るさだめなの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.28,0:22:47.01,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}白い羽　広げたら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.09,0:22:54.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}闇を抜け　飛び立つの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.39,0:23:02.41,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}この気持ち　捧げたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.60,0:23:08.84,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}全ては　運命の記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.96,0:23:16.19,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}胸の奥　騒ぐのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.40,0:23:23.90,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}解って　刹那さを
Comment: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.64,0:22:10.62,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你是否察觉？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.94,0:22:20.36,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}晦暗的裂隙中　彷徨的孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.84,0:22:26.95,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}我们互结契约　心心相连
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.64,0:22:34.15,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}在光与影的十字交锁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.57,0:22:40.11,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你我的轮舞已然天定
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.28,0:22:47.01,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}雪白之翼　终将展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.09,0:22:54.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}穿越幽暗之空　我将飞向彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.39,0:23:02.41,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}这份心意　你是否明了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.60,0:23:08.84,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}一切都是　命运的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.96,0:23:16.19,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}吾心深处　怦然的焦躁
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.40,0:23:23.90,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}刹那幽思　你可知晓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.61,0:01:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.32,0:02:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.43,0:02:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.20,0:02:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.47,0:02:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把和我拍的大头贴贴到冰箱上了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.26,0:02:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.31,0:02:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.74,0:02:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是被来家里玩的朋友看到怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.24,0:02:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会被误解是兄控的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.24,0:02:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是故意找茬吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.76,0:02:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.26,0:02:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想和你关系再进一步
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.69,0:02:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.90,0:02:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是被车撞了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.06,0:02:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.20,0:02:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是吹的什么风
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.42,0:02:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你太没用了  所以我才帮你的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.43,0:02:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.18,0:02:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是 真是感謝…好痛！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.09,0:02:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是男人吧 给我忍忍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.44,0:02:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但痛就是痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.06,0:02:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  这个伤是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.87,0:02:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟你没关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.74,0:03:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.82,0:03:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.85,0:03:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.01,0:03:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始和黑猫交往了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.66,0:03:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.01,0:03:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  你之前说的我很珍惜的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.96,0:03:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是说黑猫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.41,0:03:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  完成
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.55,0:03:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.88,0:03:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.94,0:03:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从黑暗转职到光明
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.69,0:03:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看样子是赶上了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.14,0:03:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今晚起  我成了神圣的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.96,0:03:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但却无法从黑暗中逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.21,0:03:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.93,0:03:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑠璃姐  浴室空着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.24,0:03:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.80,0:03:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在做裁缝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.43,0:04:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的cosplay服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.65,0:04:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.00,0:04:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是注入了能让男人入迷魔力的圣天使的羽衣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.38,0:04:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是很清楚 不过预感不怎么好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.34,0:04:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个超现实主义的画面是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.30,0:04:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.92,0:04:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…黑猫？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.87,0:04:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.15,0:04:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.39,0:04:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣天使神猫
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.65,0:04:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是由黑暗眷属转生成的白色天使
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.81,0:04:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是黑猫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.34,0:04:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说了不是呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.34,0:04:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能问你一件事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.13,0:05:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.27,0:05:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那身打扮是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.59,0:05:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣天使的羽衣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.11,0:05:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么还有翅膀呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.21,0:05:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从堕天圣向圣天使转职时
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.68,0:05:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,象征物被实体化了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.30,0:05:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法交流啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.90,0:05:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑠璃姐  没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.20,0:05:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去去就来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.33,0:05:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑠璃姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.08,0:05:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翅膀！翅膀还是再考虑一下怎么弄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.74,0:05:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 绝对会碍事的  还是别戴翅膀了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.50,0:05:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类少女啊  我就实现你的愿望吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.42,0:05:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去换一副小点的翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.60,0:05:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有备用品啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.50,0:05:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没有被带去辅导教育吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.05,0:06:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我也担心会不会太大胆了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.72,0:06:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你说我适合白色
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.11,0:06:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  很合适哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.89,0:06:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比之前更妖媚了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.03,0:06:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.81,0:06:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为参考
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.13,0:06:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说看哪里让你觉得妖媚了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.82,0:06:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起昨天  胸部明显更大了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.68,0:06:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.88,0:06:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去哪儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.85,0:06:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.49,0:06:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是特价！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.74,0:06:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在笑什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.63,0:06:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.25,0:06:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要那个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.30,0:06:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  但是我现在不会买的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.14,0:06:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据我的心眼的判断
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.90,0:06:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再过一个月  折扣应该会更低一点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.74,0:06:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我买给你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.13,0:07:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.74,0:07:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有理由让你买给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.44,0:07:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为开始交往的纪念什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.95,0:07:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的没和女生交往过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.44,0:07:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你挺老练的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.68,0:07:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和桐乃一起出去的时候被好好调教了一番呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.37,0:07:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是妹控呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.09,0:07:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烦～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.76,0:07:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是算了  你的好意我心领了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.95,0:07:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不用客气哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.90,0:07:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有其他更想要的东西的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.59,0:07:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你的储蓄已经用完了  那就可惜了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.74,0:07:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.35,0:07:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是构思出MASCHERA原案的人画的漫画
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.03,0:07:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然设定有部分不同
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.13,0:07:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过说这是原作也不过分
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.56,0:07:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来教你我喜欢玩的游戏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.84,0:08:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.13,0:08:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.62,0:08:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要牵个手吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.90,0:08:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你你你你你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.93,0:08:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不行的话就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.90,0:08:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你今天一直很兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.48,0:08:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道你很期待和我的约会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.00,0:08:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想再进一步  再做点什么不是更好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.32,0:08:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  不行的话就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.61,0:08:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.33,0:08:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就牵手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.76,0:08:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这就是命运的话！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.76,0:08:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这么夸张的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.02,0:08:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.76,0:08:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别发出奇怪的声音啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.46,0:08:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你那么粗鲁…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.06,0:08:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别…别说那么奇怪的话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.46,0:09:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好软啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.15,0:09:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且太害羞了  好想死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.88,0:09:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是开玩笑 真的要喷鼻血了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.93,0:09:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.66,0:09:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去下洗手间  等我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.62,0:09:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牵着手走路还是等再练习一下再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.60,0:09:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.50,0:09:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.44,0:09:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…学长
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.26,0:09:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天…那个…不觉得无聊吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.79,0:09:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没那回事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.80,0:09:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.70,0:09:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  突然这么问
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.22,0:09:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为即使和我在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.51,0:10:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也无法有什么快乐的交谈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.14,0:10:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也没和男生交往过
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.94,0:10:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有后悔和我交往吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.66,0:10:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没后悔哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.86,0:10:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这半天一起玩得很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.09,0:10:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你告诉了我很多你的事  我也很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.51,0:10:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.40,0:10:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长很温柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.90,0:10:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天仪式的目标算是达成了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.73,0:10:30.98,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\fad(100,100)}（让学长了解我）
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.97,0:10:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.54,0:10:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…后面还写着什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.04,0:10:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不愿意的话就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.61,0:10:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我也想让你知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.67,0:10:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.12,0:10:49.83,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\fad(500,500)}（理想世界）
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.72,0:10:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和桐乃？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.30,0:10:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这就是我宁愿赌上自己的一切也想要实现的理想世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.52,0:10:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.99,0:11:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看不明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.20,0:11:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.19,0:11:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我实现理想的道路还很遥远呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.73,0:11:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.87,0:11:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这幅画上我和桐乃看起来很幸福的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.15,0:11:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想实现的话我来帮忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.95,0:11:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是我能做到的事  我全都会做的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.66,0:11:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.71,0:11:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  因为我是你的男朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.73,0:11:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  接下去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.54,0:11:30.08,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\fad(0,0)}（把学长带去我家）
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.07,0:11:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你随便坐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.70,0:11:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去给你倒茶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.15,0:11:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Thank you
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.89,0:11:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妹妹也喜欢梅露露啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.42,0:11:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.82,0:11:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在在家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.29,0:12:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人都出去玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.05,0:12:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都想见见她们  真是遗憾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.08,0:12:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那伯父伯母呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.65,0:12:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.95,0:12:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说家里只有我们两个了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.09,0:12:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.33,0:12:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎么样  和平时没什么两样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.62,0:12:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也对哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.47,0:12:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.68,0:12:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.41,0:12:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有东西想和你一起看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.96,0:13:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能先等我一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.20,0:13:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.53,0:13:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是去厕所也太久了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.52,0:13:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这难道  难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.80,0:13:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要淡定  冷静下来  事情还不一定
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.26,0:13:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定不是的  虽然我也不是没期待过
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.10,0:13:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想要的是更加健康的…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.68,0:13:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.78,0:13:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  有一双不认识的鞋子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.48,0:13:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  真的诶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.20,0:14:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑠璃姐  有客人来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.23,0:14:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.82,0:14:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.08,0:14:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  被打扰啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.86,0:14:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男…男…是瑠璃姐的男朋友啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.46,0:14:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厉害  原来真的有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.45,0:14:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就觉得她最近有些奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.32,0:14:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为是脑内男友或者是二次元男友之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.72,0:14:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到居然是真人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.77,0:14:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也突然说「给我在外面玩到太阳落山」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.72,0:14:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.47,0:14:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫高坂京介
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.71,0:14:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和你们姐姐参加同一社团活动的朋友  多多指教啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.41,0:14:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.89,0:14:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是总是在电话里和姐姐吵架的bitch姐姐的哥哥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.77,0:14:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错那说的就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.80,0:14:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以叫你bitch哥哥吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.90,0:14:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以啊  换个别的叫法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.93,0:14:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊~？  那…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.27,0:14:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.29,0:15:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥哥~
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.15,0:15:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就先叫你高坂君了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.11,0:15:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就先这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.79,0:15:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫日向  五更日向
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.95,0:15:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是小妹珠希
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.85,0:15:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多多关照啦  大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.05,0:15:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是要请多多关照  那个…可以叫你们珠希和日向吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.79,0:15:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.49,0:15:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.37,0:15:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高坂君
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.28,0:15:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑠璃姐…  姐姐呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.29,0:15:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…  她说要我等一下然后就走了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.73,0:15:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.58,0:15:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人她好像在洗澡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.23,0:15:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦？  瑠璃姐在洗澡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.57,0:15:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还真奇怪啊  哈哈哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.29,0:15:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岔开话题水平好臭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.10,0:15:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要你管…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.77,0:15:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  高坂君会和瑠璃姐结婚吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.37,0:15:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会问到这个  太跳跃了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.25,0:16:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为之前瑠璃姐说过哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.50,0:16:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「再怎么說我也是有结下连理的对象的」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.99,0:16:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连理就是指…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.70,0:16:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲亲对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.81,0:16:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何故喧哗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.20,0:16:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么情况…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.46,0:16:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你看到的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.80,0:16:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个为什么回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.54,0:16:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为外面热嘛  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.04,0:16:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.45,0:16:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗言差不多都说完了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.53,0:16:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个问题想问瑠璃姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.39,0:16:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚洗完澡就是说接下来要和高坂君结连理对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.98,0:16:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿  因为我们碍事了所以才生气的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.93,0:16:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.37,0:16:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么男朋友来了却要去洗澡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.04,0:16:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为太紧张出汗了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.80,0:16:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  怎么感觉在找借口呢  另外为什么会紧张呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.65,0:16:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.57,0:17:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为？  什么什么  说说看  说说看嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.18,0:17:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑猫？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.38,0:17:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了学长  我要再失陪一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.33,0:17:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.20,0:17:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在此时  我不得不对妹妹施以管教了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.08,0:17:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您走好…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.90,0:17:32.90,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\fad(500,100)}（到学长家去玩）
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.20,0:17:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.78,0:17:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢大哥哥！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.33,0:17:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这里  再往左一点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.66,0:17:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  技术不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.79,0:18:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再激烈一点  ♀啊♀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.89,0:18:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.82,0:18:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.75,0:18:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候回来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.56,0:18:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.18,0:18:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一同：玩游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.33,0:18:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.41,0:18:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为是在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.30,0:18:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么都无所谓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.98,0:18:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是误会成在○○××了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.59,0:18:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都回来了怎么不早些进来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.48,0:18:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  我才没那么不知趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.58,0:18:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才笨呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.82,0:18:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.50,0:18:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是瞻前顾后不像你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.48,0:18:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和以前一样一起玩不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.94,0:18:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事怎么可能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.36,0:18:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我话先说在前头
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.58,0:18:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要把你排除在外的话我一开始就不会来这里玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.39,0:18:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.80,0:18:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是你的什么人？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.63,0:18:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋…朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.32,0:18:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.07,0:19:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了一个新游戏  你能来玩一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.21,0:19:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.81,0:19:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.30,0:19:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.36,0:19:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高坂君为什么要叫瑠璃姐黑猫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.83,0:19:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是她在网上的称呼  也就是网名
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.78,0:19:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们是在线下聚会上认识的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.95,0:19:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么成为情侣之后还要用网名称呼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.70,0:19:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接叫「瑠璃」不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.63,0:19:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总感觉有点害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.48,0:19:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…哈？  你们真的是高中生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.70,0:19:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很烦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.20,0:19:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.11,0:19:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就像辉夜公主一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.57,0:19:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.31,0:19:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人超级漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.80,0:20:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.81,0:20:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.04,0:20:12.04,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\fad(500,100)}（和学长一起看焰火）
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.38,0:20:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧  黑猫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.68,0:20:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.96,0:20:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑猫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.63,0:21:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.18,0:21:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.84,0:21:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来夏天就结束了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.68,0:21:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  暑假也没剩下几天了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.93,0:21:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一起度过的这个夏天…如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.70,0:21:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很开心  和你一起度过的这个夏天
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.40,0:21:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定永世不忘
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.44,0:21:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.38,0:21:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.02,0:21:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比之前更加喜欢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.11,0:21:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  京介
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.14,0:21:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.66,0:21:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.41,0:22:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.46,0:22:04.97,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\fad(0,0)}（和学长分手）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.18,0:23:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妹妹不可能这么可爱！
