[Script Info]
Title:oreimo
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00287ED7,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HC8000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正康体_GBK,40,&H0006BD82,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: NEXT,方正康体_GBK,42,&H0034C774,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: NEXT2,DFGPOP1-W12,40,&H004DD481,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,15,&H0019CA69,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HB4FFFFFF,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,10,20,7,1
Style: OPCN,方正准圆_GBK,17,&H0019CA69,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HB4FFFFFF,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,8,25,7,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00287ED7,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,5,1
Style: EDJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,16,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00585858,&HB4D7EDFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,15,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00585858,&HB4D7EDFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,15,25,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,15,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&H64FFFFFF,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正大标宋_GBK,15,&H003C3CB8,&HFF0000FF,&H50EAEAEA,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: INJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,14,&H0080F2F1,&HFF0000FF,&H00C06530,&H50B180C5,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,7,10,20,10,1
Style: INCN,方正准圆_GBK,15,&H0080F2F1,&HFF0000FF,&H00C06530,&H50B180C5,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,7,8,25,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.66,0:00:46.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた物語が始まるの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.52,0:00:56.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an9}記憶の遠く　走ってた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.21,0:01:04.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an9}きらめく影法師も忘れられなくて　ずっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.86,0:01:09.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an7}君の目線の先に　気付かずに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.01,0:01:14.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an7}勝手な理想だけ膨らんじゃって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.28,0:01:17.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an7}前見えないの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.33,0:01:24.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an9}想いは　やっぱり　透明だけど重くて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.82,0:01:31.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}少しずつ　溶かしてくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.76,0:01:34.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた手を繋ごう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.06,0:01:38.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}私とまた夢を見よう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.61,0:01:42.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}傷だらけでも今を抱いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.57,0:01:45.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}はじまりにしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.92,0:01:49.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた声交わそう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.37,0:01:52.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}私とまた笑い合おう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.86,0:01:56.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}蕾のままだった明日を
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.34,0:02:02.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}咲かせるの　君の近くで
Comment: 0,0:00:25.00,0:00:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.66,0:00:46.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我与你之间又有全新的  故事开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.52,0:00:56.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an1}在记忆的彼方徘徊不定
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.21,0:01:04.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an1}那闪烁的人影也一直无法忘怀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.86,0:01:09.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an3}对于你的视线我毫不在意
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.01,0:01:14.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an3}只是执着于那偏执的理想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.28,0:01:17.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an3}看不见前方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.33,0:01:24.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an1}我的思念一如坚冰  透明却又厚重
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.82,0:01:31.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}如今却逐渐  因你而融化
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.76,0:01:34.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一次牵手  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.06,0:01:38.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一起做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.61,0:01:42.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}即使满身疮痍也要拥抱现在
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.57,0:01:45.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}然后再一次启程
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.92,0:01:49.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一次交流
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.37,0:01:52.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一起欢笑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.86,0:01:56.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我的明天一如  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.34,0:02:02.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}含苞待放的花蕾  就在你的身边
Comment: 0,0:02:46.27,0:02:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.48,0:02:07.48,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(130,356)\fs38\fsp-6\fs30\fad(1000,0)}我不可能做我妹妹的男朋友我的妹妹也不可能有男朋友
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.44,0:23:50.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}誰も彼も口々に言う
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.89,0:23:59.37,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}「可愛い」って言葉はわかるけど
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.43,0:24:06.74,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}部屋の隅に隠したディスク
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.96,0:24:13.34,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}「可愛い」じゃ足りない　そうでしょ？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.54,0:24:20.98,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}胸の痛み　このままでいいわ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.20,0:24:27.11,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}叫ばせて  {\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs18}lalala…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.41,0:24:31.53,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}大人の（アダルト）ゲームで{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs18}revolution  
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.72,0:24:35.27,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}妹は神様よ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.44,0:24:42.62,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}出会わなくても生きていける——わけない
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.87,0:24:47.51,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}あたしを待ってる　{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs18}Brand-new  sky
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.66,0:24:51.08,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}両腕で抱きしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.25,0:24:57.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好きなら好きとありのままに
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.90,0:25:00.21,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}やっぱり秘密
Comment: 0,0:02:09.00,0:02:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.44,0:23:50.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}不管是他还是别人  都会异口同声
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.89,0:23:59.37,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}「可爱」这个形容词实在太好理解
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.43,0:24:06.74,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}在房间的角落里  你藏着我的CD
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.96,0:24:13.34,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}「可爱」对你还不够  我没猜错
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.54,0:24:20.98,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}心中的阵痛  那就是你活该
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.20,0:24:27.11,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}大声喊出来  lalala…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.41,0:24:31.53,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}用成人的游戏来Revolution
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.72,0:24:35.27,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}妹妹大人就是你的神
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.44,0:24:42.62,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}就算见不到你  也能生活下去——怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.87,0:24:47.51,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}一直在等待我的  Brand-new  sky
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.66,0:24:51.08,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}张开双臂紧紧拥抱它
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.25,0:24:57.71,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}如果喜欢我就请一直保持…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.90,0:25:00.21,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}果然还是保密
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.94,0:00:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.74,0:00:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来做我的男朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.38,0:00:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你  原来喜欢我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.28,0:00:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会！像你这种人  我怎么会喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.50,0:00:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是想让你假装做我的男朋友一小段时间而已
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.85,0:00:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就说清楚啊  说法真让别人误会
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.62,0:00:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你是妹控才会乱误会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.97,0:00:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.58,0:00:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须假装成我的男朋友和我去见一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.95,0:02:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.42,0:02:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望让桐乃当我的专属模特
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.84,0:02:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的话  想把她带到欧洲的总公司去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.90,0:02:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可她却说「我有男朋友  所以…不想去外国！」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.09,0:02:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今再去外国这种事情  怎么好意思开口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.99,0:02:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确  我假装成男朋友是最妥当的拒绝方式了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.94,0:02:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我就是个…妹控！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.82,0:02:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以京介同学  请和桐乃分手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.43,0:02:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.07,0:02:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,50万如何
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.75,0:02:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.25,0:03:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是钱的问题  因为我…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.95,0:03:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱着桐乃！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.98,0:03:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.50,0:03:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情必须说清楚才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.73,0:03:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是这样  你也有点怎么说呢  太过了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.67,0:03:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑且我知道桐乃是有男朋友的了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.23,0:03:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.22,0:03:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我还没有放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.70,0:03:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃明天有空吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.02,0:03:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  明天我们有约会
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.46,0:03:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧  My  honey
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.90,0:03:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在害羞吗  My  honey
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.27,0:03:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不觉得害羞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.58,0:03:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在美咲小姐面前说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.06,0:04:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久…久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.52,0:04:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没等多久啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.64,0:04:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…今天就叫你京介了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.81,0:04:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样比较像恋人间的称呼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.17,0:04:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随…随便你  走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.75,0:04:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.62,0:04:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在吗  美咲小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.51,0:04:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  但我能感觉到视线
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.21,0:04:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的来了吗  今天不是有时装秀吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.11,0:04:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放着那边不管却来这里  根本不知道她在想些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.66,0:04:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是换个立场考虑的话 也许是件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.97,0:04:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她看到我们今天一天约会的样子的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.57,0:04:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会放弃的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.57,0:04:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么牵强的说法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.99,0:04:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你说要约会才变成现在这样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.65,0:04:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这么做了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.27,0:04:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  从现在开始
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.96,0:04:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京…京介
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.71,0:04:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.17,0:05:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.36,0:05:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然老套了点  去看电影吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.68,0:05:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那根本就是工口游戏的选项吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.00,0:05:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能  怎么会暴露的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.47,0:05:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我借你的游戏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.99,0:05:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小京  桐乃？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.17,0:05:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.57,0:05:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  京介
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.56,0:05:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才绝对是引起奇怪的误会了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.43,0:05:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.65,0:05:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她那表情真夸张
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.50,0:05:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\3c&HFF80FF&}决不让任何人阻止我们  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.50,0:05:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\3c&HFF80FF&}宇宙最强的妹妹们  在此诞生！ \N Little  Sisters
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.42,0:05:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.00,0:06:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主角们都是群萝莉  超可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.49,0:06:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定这片会火呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.74,0:06:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过能预测到这一点的我也很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.01,0:06:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.00,0:06:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你太吵了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.03,0:06:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许现在也正被监视着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.14,0:06:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.27,0:06:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.78,0:06:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才好像看到了很像的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.75,0:06:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就找个店进去确认一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.57,0:06:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好也肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.76,0:06:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别转来转去的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.75,0:06:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定就在你后面看着你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.10,0:06:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  她打算跟到最后吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.12,0:06:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  那不是桐乃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.49,0:06:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加…加奈子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.95,0:06:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  约会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.13,0:06:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃果然是有男朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.25,0:06:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这笨蛋居然忘记了我的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.05,0:06:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是啊  不要和大家说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.04,0:06:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加奈加奈  洗手间现在空着哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.05,0:07:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  阿尔！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.88,0:07:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不对…是布里吉特
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.83,0:07:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.73,0:07:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布里吉特和新垣小姐是同一个事务所的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.34,0:07:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看过照片的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.21,0:07:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.53,0:07:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近因为工作  经常和这家伙在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.20,0:07:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉就变得这么亲近了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.52,0:07:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.36,0:07:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.07,0:07:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位是情侣吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.48,0:07:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底喜欢对方的哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.79,0:07:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子我也很有兴趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.14,0:07:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃到底喜欢这个老土家伙的哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.31,0:07:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温柔吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.37,0:07:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  很值得信赖  之类？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.26,0:07:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.23,0:07:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太得意了  这只是演戏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.41,0:08:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.97,0:08:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这家伙似乎很喜欢我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.11,0:08:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点我也喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.50,0:08:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.16,0:08:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢你女朋友的哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.94,0:08:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  我喜欢你无论何时都竭尽全力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.85,0:08:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对各种事情都抱有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.56,0:08:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢上之后又都能竭尽全力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.42,0:08:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这点很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.15,0:08:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很感谢你  别看我这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.39,0:08:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你  我的人生也增添了不少乐趣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.47,0:08:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦  把手拿开吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.35,0:08:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}好厉害  真好  真好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.66,0:08:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  总觉得不怎么像情侣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.70,0:08:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.20,0:08:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么又不高兴啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.24,0:09:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粘着你是我不好  但也没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.30,0:09:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.42,0:09:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没忘记吧  我们也许是被监视着的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.66,0:09:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.90,0:09:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还跟着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.37,0:09:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.10,0:09:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法  就在这里让我们激烈地展示下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.96,0:09:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之间的深爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.88,0:09:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个要怎么拍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.89,0:09:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那里放钱  你没拍过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.15,0:09:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生首次大头贴居然是和妹妹拍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.39,0:09:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要回想起来就会喘不过气昏倒的感觉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.01,0:09:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦  我选镜框了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.13,0:09:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偏偏还选心型的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.93,0:09:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都到这一步了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.42,0:09:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要做就只能做得更彻底了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.19,0:09:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的眼神已经呆滞不动了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.78,0:09:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  要拍了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.78,0:09:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  牵手牵手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.53,0:09:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.37,0:10:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.27,0:10:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的零钱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.63,0:10:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,零钱掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.98,0:10:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你们在做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.39,0:10:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候变得这么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.04,0:10:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在正面临一个巨大的误会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.66,0:10:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么啊  正有人看着我们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.59,0:10:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙日后再和她说也不迟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.16,0:10:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在正在约会中  所以先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.13,0:10:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？…哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.95,0:10:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  京介
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.17,0:10:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.91,0:11:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.44,0:11:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.41,0:11:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲小姐说暂时是放弃我了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.26,0:11:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  总觉得解决得太轻松了点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.49,0:11:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么不满吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.89,0:11:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是我去国外比较好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.01,0:11:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪有那么说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.06,0:11:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之能解决就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.61,0:11:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.98,0:11:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊  今天的约会真是烂透了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.75,0:11:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能再认真点取悦你的女朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.43,0:11:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是很高兴吗  看了电影后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.22,0:11:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是因为电影好看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.60,0:11:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我想和你聊电影的内容
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.66,0:11:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却用可怕的声音说「你真啰嗦」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.81,0:11:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是超伤我的心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.86,0:11:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还不是因为你宅属性全开说个不停
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.67,0:11:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你不能温柔点阻止我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.91,0:11:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些话啊  你别对着哥哥  去对着你的男朋友说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.34,0:12:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想再演你的男朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.38,0:12:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你干什…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.85,0:12:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你傻吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.00,0:12:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经够了  下次我就拜托真的男朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.96,0:12:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的男朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.08,0:12:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到游研也有暑假活动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.17,0:12:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来这样好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.01,0:12:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加夏Comiket
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.88,0:12:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是学校的社团  不用申请许可吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.72,0:12:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说些什么吧  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.17,0:12:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  让亲妹妹叫你「京介」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.50,0:12:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还卿卿我我的妹控变态先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.07,0:13:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了那是桐乃她…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.64,0:13:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伪装约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.22,0:13:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真像你喜欢的妹系工口游戏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.20,0:13:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尽玩妹系是因为那都是桐乃塞给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.78,0:13:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀？  是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.30,0:13:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得那全是借口  你自己都已经乐在其中了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.43,0:13:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  你觉得桐乃会有男朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.84,0:13:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除你之外？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.69,0:13:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逗我玩了  我是认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.49,0:13:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她说得好像真有一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.73,0:13:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我在想会不会真有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.22,0:13:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当有趣的假设呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.16,0:13:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女人一定对恋人也会很忘我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.94,0:13:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和她一直以来一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.72,0:13:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想也是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.28,0:13:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比现在更压缩娱乐的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.02,0:13:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙织可能会觉得寂寞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.40,0:13:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也一样会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.52,0:14:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  沙织和你一定会觉得寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.36,0:14:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.50,0:14:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…  
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.27,0:14:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会感到高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.56,0:14:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.06,0:14:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.30,0:14:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.58,0:14:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊  关于夏Comiket
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.61,0:14:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.73,0:14:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑猫在第三天会作为社团参加
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.70,0:14:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我在想要不要像去年一样大家一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.59,0:14:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.15,0:14:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我也和沙织说了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.98,0:14:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说机会难得  我们要不要出个本子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.13,0:14:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本子？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.19,0:14:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过因为是她的社团  所以题材是Maschera
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.80,0:15:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Maschera？  怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.62,0:15:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你挡路了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.46,0:15:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.43,0:15:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  你就为了说那个才坐这等我的？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.24,0:15:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心  你是忠犬八公吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.92,0:15:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.37,0:15:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你有关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.56,0:15:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很痛啊  你干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.47,0:15:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.29,0:15:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放手啊  干什么这么认真
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.31,0:15:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.34,0:15:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  有男朋友了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.26,0:15:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超痛的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.21,0:16:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我不对
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.73,0:16:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本是想跟你和好的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.89,0:16:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  随你去吧  一切都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.87,0:16:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算啥？  妹妹交到男朋友嫉妒了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.69,0:16:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.22,0:16:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然超认真地瞪着妹妹说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「你真的有男朋友了吗」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.84,0:16:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.71,0:16:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  你到底有男朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.12,0:16:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有还是没有？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.37,0:16:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.22,0:16:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏Comiket出本子的事你去和黑色的说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.23,0:16:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我帮忙做也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.98,0:16:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是算了  我自己去说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.82,0:16:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊  真是搞不懂你在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.43,0:16:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也弄不懂你在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.77,0:17:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次我介绍给你吧  我的「男朋友」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.21,0:17:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.56,0:17:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都还没开始你少给我提不起劲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.91,0:17:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的夏Comiket可是早就开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.25,0:17:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天也和游研一起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.78,0:17:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以还没有从疲劳恢复过来？  真像个大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.21,0:17:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了要走了  沙织说已经先入场了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.22,0:17:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先等下  黑猫来短信说就在这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.30,0:17:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从刚才就在背后了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.85,0:17:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是  什么Cosplay来着？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.12,0:17:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是Cosplay  便装…是便装啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.83,0:17:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  因为和平时太不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.12,0:17:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样  不错诶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.17,0:18:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.37,0:18:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯  很合适
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.82,0:18:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就不算黑猫  是白猫了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.82,0:18:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是在夸我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.71,0:18:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是  上周我给你挑的衣服嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.01,0:18:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候…谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.31,0:18:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是桐乃挑的啊  果然你很厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.91,0:18:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧  我就觉得她穿这一类型的衣服绝对合适
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.35,0:18:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  原来是今天穿的衣服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.65,0:18:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧  沙织在等我们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.08,0:18:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}现在开始实施入场限行  请排成五列在原地稍候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.50,0:18:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}请不要留出空隙尽量向前
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.88,0:18:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\3c&H400080&}神圣黑猫骑士团
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.65,0:18:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锵锵~
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.86,0:18:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的做成本子了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.36,0:18:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你冷静点啊  又不是第一次出书了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.56,0:18:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个和这个完全不一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.44,0:19:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这个可是大家一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.22,0:19:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之就是不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.02,0:19:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能拜读一下吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.74,0:19:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.59,0:19:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实在下是第一次参加制作同人志
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.01,0:19:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己做出来的本子还真是好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.12,0:19:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑猫氏的漫画  桐乃乃氏的小说  在下的插画…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}妹妹的冒险  埼玉灭亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}作者  KIRIRIN  是假名哦  你们知道是谁吗  知道了就强悍喽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}我是KIRIRIN  是个美少女初中生哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}非常感谢大家购买这个本子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}虽然里面都是些业余的家伙们制作的作品
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}但是不要紧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}接下来就由我这个专业的超级专家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}来给大家带来快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}综上所述呢——
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}我来到Maschera的世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}东京
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}这东京是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}天上好多云真阴暗www
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}建筑也全毁了ww
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}大好机会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}现在的话千叶可以胜过东京了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}首都迁到房总半岛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}现在正是和埼玉一决胜负的时机
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}赶紧到埼玉去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}寻找妹妹们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}不管琦玉有多么…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}我也不会输
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.27,0:19:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}只要那里有妹妹…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}好厉害！琦玉人都有这种能力啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}在风的指引下  我们继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}为了把从埼玉——不对是魔界救起的妹妹们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}带回到安全的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}可爱的妹妹们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}已经超过了十二人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}破纪录了  我家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}或许应该改名叫妹妹之家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}回到千叶之后大家一起在雪上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}画大大的妹妹图吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}待续
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.67,0:19:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦  做出来的效果还是相当不错的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.68,0:19:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱做什么就做什么  这就是同人志的乐趣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.86,0:19:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}第82届Comic  Circle  Market（C82）现在开幕
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.73,0:20:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一册都没有卖出去  怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.10,0:20:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次都是差不多这样  你冷静点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.85,0:20:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  我来Cos一下漆黑招揽客人怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.98,0:20:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是傻吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.08,0:20:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的小说不也被无视了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.34,0:20:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位  快看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.42,0:20:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我一册
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.37,0:20:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非  非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.48,0:20:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.13,0:21:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才卖出去一册  你们也高兴过头了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.89,0:21:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个由你拿着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.25,0:21:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.62,0:21:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么特别的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.12,0:21:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下记得放进收银盒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.48,0:21:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.10,0:21:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  恭喜恭喜  全部售罄了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.08,0:22:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之是可喜可贺呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.74,0:22:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也高兴下嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.04,0:22:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别一副「我都来参加了应该卖得更好一点」的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.31,0:22:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不是这个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.28,0:22:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到  居然可以卖光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.45,0:22:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.33,0:22:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还剩九成以上没卖出去  我的冬Comiket就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.43,0:22:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.84,0:22:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天卖了这么多  我很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.15,0:22:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了大家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.88,0:22:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}神圣黑猫骑士团5
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.88,0:22:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}已经全部售罄！！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.88,0:22:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}非常感谢大家的支持
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.88,0:22:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}预定参加下一次的冬Comiket
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.88,0:22:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\1c&H000000&\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs11}黑猫社团
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.02,0:22:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在下眼睛里进东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.69,0:22:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再一起制作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.69,0:23:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了  我要去企业展台
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.44,0:23:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星尘小魔女梅露露  要开始了哟
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.33,0:23:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勉强赶上了  果然大屏幕就是好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.23,0:23:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能赶上真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.48,0:23:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.01,0:23:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅露露~
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.98,0:23:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.06,0:23:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是桐乃小姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.95,0:23:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  怎么会在这里

Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.87,0:25:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妹妹不可能带男朋友回家
