[Script Info]
Title:oreimo
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00287ED7,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HC8000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正康体_GBK,40,&H0006BD82,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: NEXT,方正康体_GBK,42,&H0034C774,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: NEXT2,DFGPOP1-W12,40,&H004DD481,&HFF0000FF,&HFF7B0A25,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,15,&H0019CA69,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HB4FFFFFF,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,10,20,7,1
Style: OPCN,方正准圆_GBK,17,&H0019CA69,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HB4FFFFFF,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,8,25,7,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00287ED7,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,5,1
Style: EDJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,16,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00585858,&HB4D7EDFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,15,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00585858,&HB4D7EDFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,15,25,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,15,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&H64FFFFFF,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正大标宋_GBK,15,&H003C3CB8,&HFF0000FF,&H50EAEAEA,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: INJP,ＦＡ 丸ゴシックＭ,14,&H0080F2F1,&HFF0000FF,&H00C06530,&H50B180C5,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,7,10,20,10,1
Style: INCN,方正准圆_GBK,15,&H0080F2F1,&HFF0000FF,&H00C06530,&H50B180C5,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,7,8,25,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.66,0:00:51.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた物語が始まるの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.52,0:01:01.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an9}記憶の遠く　走ってた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.21,0:01:09.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an9}きらめく影法師も忘れられなくて　ずっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.86,0:01:14.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an7}君の目線の先に　気付かずに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.01,0:01:19.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an7}勝手な理想だけ膨らんじゃって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.28,0:01:22.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an7}前見えないの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.33,0:01:29.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an9}想いは　やっぱり　透明だけど重くて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.82,0:01:36.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}少しずつ　溶かしてくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.76,0:01:39.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた手を繋ごう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.06,0:01:43.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}私とまた夢を見よう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.61,0:01:47.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}傷だらけでも今を抱いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.57,0:01:50.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}はじまりにしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.92,0:01:54.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}君とまた声交わそう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.37,0:01:57.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}私とまた笑い合おう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.86,0:02:01.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}蕾のままだった明日を
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.34,0:02:07.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}咲かせるの　君の近くで
Comment: 0,0:00:30.00,0:00:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.66,0:00:51.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我与你之间又有全新的  故事开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.52,0:01:01.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an1}在记忆的彼方徘徊不定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.21,0:01:09.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an1}那闪烁的人影也一直无法忘怀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.86,0:01:14.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an3}对于你的视线我毫不在意
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.01,0:01:19.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an3}只是执着于那偏执的理想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.28,0:01:22.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an3}看不见前方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.33,0:01:29.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2\an1}我的思念一如坚冰  透明却又厚重
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.82,0:01:36.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}如今却逐渐  因你而融化
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.76,0:01:39.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一次牵手  
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.06,0:01:43.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一起做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.61,0:01:47.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}即使满身疮痍也要拥抱现在
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.57,0:01:50.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}然后再一次启程
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.92,0:01:54.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一次交流
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.37,0:01:57.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}好想和你再一起欢笑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.86,0:02:01.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我的明天一如  
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.34,0:02:07.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}含苞待放的花蕾  就在你的身边
Comment: 0,0:02:46.27,0:02:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.20,0:02:12.48,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(170,310)\fad(800,0)\fs30}我的妹妹的劲敌不可能来日本
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.55,0:22:10.32,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}私のこの気持ち届け！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.56,0:22:29.00,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}前を歩くあいつの背中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.43,0:22:35.06,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}大きすぎて眩しすぎて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.41,0:22:41.07,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}目を合わすとケンカばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.38,0:22:46.76,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}どうしてこうなったビミョーな関係
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.94,0:22:53.48,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}時は流れて人は大人になっていく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.62,0:23:00.48,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}でもこの気持ちはずっとずっと変わらないから
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.71,0:23:07.02,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}神様、どうか私をね素直にしてお願い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:12.88,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}とめどないこの気持ち少しでもいい伝えたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.11,0:23:18.96,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}ああそしていつの日か二人並んで歩いて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.07,0:23:24.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}そっと手を差し出して触れるあいつの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.05,0:23:31.12,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}驚いた顔見てふと笑うんだ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.55,0:22:10.32,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我的这一份心愿  能否传达
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.56,0:22:29.00,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}大步向前走  我跟在你身后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.43,0:22:35.06,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}背影很宽大  又那么地耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.41,0:22:41.07,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}每次眼对眼  争吵不可免
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.38,0:22:46.76,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}不知何时起  关系便如此奇妙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.94,0:22:53.48,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}光阴流转  我们逐渐长大
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.62,0:23:00.48,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}只是这一份心愿  一直都未曾改变
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.71,0:23:07.02,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}神啊您听我说  请您给我更大勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:12.88,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}这份感情无法压抑  一点也好  让他知道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.11,0:23:18.96,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}然后但愿有一天  我们能并肩而行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.07,0:23:24.57,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}我一伸出手  就能握住他
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.05,0:23:31.12,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\be2}看着他一脸惊讶  我不禁笑满颜
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.09,0:00:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.06,0:00:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工口游戏什么时候进化到这种地步了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.45,0:00:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  我不是让你穿好衣服再出去嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.83,0:02:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.85,0:02:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我留学时认识的朋友马上就要来日本了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.80,0:02:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以让她寄宿在我们家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.42,0:02:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个朋友是女生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.15,0:02:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.42,0:02:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么不好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.88,0:02:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧  孩子他爸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.28,0:02:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是  如果对方父母也都同意的话就没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.78,0:02:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  谢谢爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.75,0:02:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在看什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.31,0:02:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有意见就直说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.39,0:02:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没意见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.25,0:02:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在想你的朋友如果是个可爱的女孩子就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.14,0:02:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝莉控
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.18,0:02:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝莉控？你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.38,0:03:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃  你那位朋友是个怎么样的人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.79,0:03:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字叫做莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.04,0:03:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  就是她
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.59,0:03:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.56,0:03:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  很可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.07,0:03:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  她不就是你曾经赢过一次的那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.25,0:03:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  是在那边的室友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.53,0:03:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关系非常要好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.09,0:03:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是呢  就像妹妹一样？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.36,0:03:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.46,0:03:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你敢对她下手  我真的会杀了你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.14,0:03:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会下手啊  笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.92,0:03:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚出去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.34,0:03:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  刚才那可是不可抗力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.81,0:03:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少废话  快给我滚出去  变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.99,0:03:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也别回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.49,0:04:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这萝莉控！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.83,0:04:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我说话的时候你在看哪…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.96,0:04:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  你打算保持那身打扮到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.28,0:04:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.28,0:04:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要那么生气呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.19,0:04:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然要生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.18,0:04:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  是你说「我从机场跑过来的  出了好多汗」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.21,0:04:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才变成现在这样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.86,0:04:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是说一起泡的不是桐乃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.43,0:04:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话…话是这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.40,0:04:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之快点把衣服穿起来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.66,0:04:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我错了  桐乃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.47,0:04:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.87,0:04:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  你怎么还在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.93,0:04:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我消失行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.53,0:04:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说我在道歉呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.81,0:04:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了那是意外啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.98,0:04:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会为了这种无聊的事一次次出去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.63,0:04:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无聊的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.24,0:04:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你对我做了什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.23,0:04:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.71,0:04:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今看了你的裸体我也不觉得有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.28,0:05:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是兄妹  你怎么还那么自我意识过剩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.27,0:05:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下恐怕要大闹一场了  这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.51,0:05:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.43,0:05:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没看到！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.45,0:05:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃的小裤裤好紧身啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.09,0:05:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿那样的不觉得凉飕飕的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.98,0:05:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这臭小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.01,0:05:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打不到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.30,0:05:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,着陆～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.95,0:05:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.65,0:05:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.61,0:05:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我适可而止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.85,0:05:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  桐乃  不行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.83,0:05:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也太无防备了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.74,0:05:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是作弄别人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.98,0:05:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底想干什么呐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.90,0:05:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为桐乃明明是在生我的气
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.65,0:05:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却一直在和哥哥吵架
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.56,0:06:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.07,0:06:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.51,0:06:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次生你的气都会渐渐变得和傻瓜一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.62,0:06:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.95,0:06:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  这里有变态萝莉控  我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.06,0:06:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.03,0:06:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯什么嗯  我既不是变态也不是萝莉控
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.82,0:06:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头发什么的我会帮你弄好的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.11,0:06:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去我房间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.69,0:06:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  好麻烦呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.40,0:06:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,My  name  is  Ria
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.21,0:06:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间要给你们添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.62,0:06:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是高坂京介
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.31,0:06:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是桐乃的哥哥  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.41,0:06:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.55,0:06:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚一直都很想见你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.26,0:06:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以叫你京介大哥哥吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.95,0:06:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.44,0:06:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…一直想见我？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.13,0:06:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我觉得你一定是个很棒的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.36,0:06:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和想象的不一样很失望吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.89,0:07:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  和我想象中的一样哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.45,0:07:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥哥  超喜欢你！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.97,0:07:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么刚才的情况会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.71,0:07:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.27,0:07:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.25,0:07:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么不好  京介大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.80,0:07:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  你在干…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.43,0:07:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊  你这萝莉控！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.39,0:07:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我不是萝莉控！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.54,0:07:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么容我再次介绍下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.67,0:07:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的室友  莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.75,0:07:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后这是我的爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.91,0:07:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,How…How  do  you  do？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.28,0:07:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Welcome  Japan
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.03,0:07:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教呢  大叔！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.32,0:07:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后这是我妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.96,0:07:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.12,0:07:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真美味
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.35,0:07:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯母真是料理的天才
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.75,0:07:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.51,0:08:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可爱呢  让我想起了桐乃小时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.76,0:08:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有  我可没那么粘人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.64,0:08:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  别乱动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.96,0:08:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  桐乃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.95,0:08:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.07,0:08:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和想象中的稍微有些不同呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.02,0:08:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.77,0:08:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有好好做一个姐姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.08,0:08:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥哥  一起来洗澡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.35,0:08:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.36,0:08:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快挡起来！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.31,0:08:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少给我围一下浴巾或穿个泳衣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.69,0:08:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.69,0:08:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么啊  你这萝莉控
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.69,0:08:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要一点警戒心都没有就去接近那个萝莉控啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.96,0:08:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很糟糕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.24,0:08:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他基本上就是个变态
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.11,0:09:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京介大哥哥是个好人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.52,0:09:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像桐乃说的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.57,0:09:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有说过那种话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.21,0:09:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.20,0:09:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.82,0:09:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚想出去玩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.72,0:09:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带我观光日本吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.04,0:09:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.13,0:09:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就乖乖睡觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.12,0:09:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋叶原～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.63,0:09:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近你来这里太频繁了点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.22,0:09:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到东京名胜的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.95,0:09:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多其他地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.13,0:09:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？  说到在日本观光的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.45,0:09:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是先来秋叶原吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.40,0:09:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是你的偏见
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.70,0:09:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是传说中的秋叶原啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.25,0:09:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都很想来看一次呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.10,0:09:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意外地很中意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.78,0:09:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  在国外秋叶原可是很有人气的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.82,0:09:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊  你在这里打算干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.19,0:10:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道一起去买工口游戏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.93,0:10:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为这里只卖工口游戏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.20,0:10:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要去的就是普通卖手办  扭蛋和漫画的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.09,0:10:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.53,0:10:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃  京介大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.93,0:10:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个打扮很奇怪的人在哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.12,0:10:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}请您不要这样  我现在正在工作…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.46,0:10:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个笨蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.93,0:10:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}喂  快住手啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.25,0:10:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好痛好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.91,0:10:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  打扰你工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.22,0:10:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的对不起  这个笨蛋给您添麻烦了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.13,0:10:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人关系真好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.02,0:10:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵…吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.63,0:10:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说这么恶心的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.99,0:10:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛痛  抓头发犯规  犯规啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.40,0:10:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已经…不是你们的同伴了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.54,0:10:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是暗黑小魔女梅露露！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.69,0:10:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  太帅气了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.09,0:11:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作画和音乐都充满了爱啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.79,0:11:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是桐乃一直说的那个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.35,0:11:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  莉亚也趁在日本的时候一起看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.39,0:11:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对会喜欢的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.38,0:11:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  看上去很有趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.19,0:11:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边没有播放日本的动画吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.46,0:11:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想看也不是看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.46,0:11:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}一  二…要上了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.34,0:11:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底宿舍里根本没有电视机哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.81,0:11:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的只有训练一件事可以做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.40,0:11:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是每天都很无聊吗  莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.39,0:11:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有  每天都能做喜欢做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.77,0:11:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是超开心的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.03,0:11:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和莉亚说什么都是没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.38,0:11:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙除了跑步以外真的什么都不在乎了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.42,0:11:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  相比较都不在乎了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.76,0:11:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  我就知道会这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.78,0:11:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Planet  Burst！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.36,0:11:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊  我还是去预订蓝光吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.04,0:12:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是已经预订过了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.28,0:12:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多预订几份要你管啊  
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.33,0:12:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一卷可是会抽选活动预约券的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.71,0:12:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  这家伙在美国也是这…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.93,0:12:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.13,0:12:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.24,0:12:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  京介大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.03,0:12:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\3c&HFFFFFF&\1c&H000000&}此处向前为同人志专区
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.40,0:12:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别随便玩消失啊  我们会担心的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.85,0:12:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  抱歉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.74,0:12:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到什么想要的书了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.37,0:12:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为觉得这女孩有点像莉亚所以看了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.26,0:12:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\1c&HC080FF&\3c&HFFFFFF&}XXX的大人的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.39,0:12:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？咦…？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.38,0:12:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  这本书不可以啊  千万别翻开…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.62,0:12:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥哥  这本书怎么…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.44,0:13:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是你这种小鬼看的书
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.94,0:13:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看你把莉亚领到什么地方来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.78,0:13:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我领过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.78,0:13:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个萝莉控  实在太恶心了  去死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.70,0:13:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是萝莉控！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.87,0:13:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  这个才比较像你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.71,0:13:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.90,0:13:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.87,0:13:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.14,0:13:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.13,0:13:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  虽然你说除了跑步之外都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.92,0:13:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就是因为这样我才想带你来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.82,0:13:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让莉亚看看我珍爱的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.10,0:14:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不全是为了你  而是我自己也想这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.56,0:14:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了  桐乃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.78,0:14:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也真的很享受啊  桐乃真是爱操心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.63,0:14:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然莉亚只要能跑步就不需要其他了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.09,0:14:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不是不想要哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.38,0:14:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友也好  娱乐也好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.14,0:14:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.22,0:14:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.36,0:14:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来比赛吧  赛跑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.91,0:14:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃也是一开始就这么打算的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.94,0:15:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿那么方便活动的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.83,0:15:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那双鞋也是训练时候穿的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.06,0:15:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也多少感觉到莉亚可能会这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.12,0:15:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  你来日本是为了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.47,0:15:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是为了报仇了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.82,0:15:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那次只是碰巧状态好…  这么说你也不会听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.41,0:15:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚怎么会碰巧输掉呢  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.57,0:15:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候桐乃确实比莉亚跑得还快  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.93,0:15:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明前一天还不值一提  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.73,0:15:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想弄明白  才一天时间究竟发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.47,0:15:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么让桐乃的脚步变快了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.38,0:15:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明赢了莉亚  为什么却又回国了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.75,0:15:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.75,0:15:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天桐乃给我看的东西就是答案吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.51,0:16:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边的我并不是真的我  所以我才回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.55,0:16:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够保持真我的地方  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.23,0:16:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后我还是没能舍弃我珍爱的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.98,0:16:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社团活动  朋友  家人还有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.48,0:16:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了这一切  我才是我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.11,0:16:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要保持真正的我  然后赢给你们看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.47,0:16:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始咯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.51,0:16:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ready
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.51,0:16:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Go
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.53,0:16:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超快
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.27,0:16:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌「天才」这个词
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.29,0:16:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我曾经认为是天才的人  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.12,0:17:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果只是个比一般人努力得多的凡人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.15,0:17:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我觉得如果把那家伙长年累月流下的汗水  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.68,0:17:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,积累起来的努力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.14,0:17:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归结成「天才」这一个词  实际上是极度失礼的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.73,0:17:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是拥有「天才」这一因子的人如今就摆在我眼前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.18,0:17:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单比跑步这一项的话  我的妹妹无论如何也不可能赢莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.34,0:17:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我这个外行也能看出来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.39,0:17:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不可能不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.76,0:17:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃正在被远比自己优秀的对手逼到死角
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.26,0:17:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像曾经的我  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.47,0:17:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个在所有事情上都输给妹妹抬不起头的我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.77,0:17:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她没有像我一样逃避  而是那样努力应战
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.71,0:17:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直面对手  毫不气馁地不断挣扎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.24,0:18:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么能…不为她加油
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.09,0:18:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃  加油啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.02,0:18:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊  还能追的上  别放弃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.03,0:18:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超她  超过她  桐乃！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.05,0:18:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超越她吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.98,0:18:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.03,0:18:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是萝莉控  是妹控啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.29,0:18:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要赢啊  桐乃！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.03,0:18:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃  是莉亚赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.86,0:18:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啊  你不用每次都说出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.10,0:18:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不懂照顾一下失败者吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.09,0:18:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不呢  赢了就是赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.04,0:19:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复仇成功  看到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.99,0:19:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小鬼  气人  太气人了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.92,0:19:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太气人了  太气人了…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.08,0:19:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  虽然我最喜欢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.41,0:19:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在我要说  现在的你是世界第一烦人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.66,0:19:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然莉亚也最喜欢桐乃了  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.21,0:19:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但恕我直言  莉亚就是为了看这个表情才来的日本
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.75,0:19:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了  现实中的妹妹根本不是什么好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.34,0:19:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹只有二次元的好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.87,0:19:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没资格说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.11,0:19:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.09,0:19:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你真的只是为了复仇才来的日本啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.00,0:19:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？  大哥哥真是笨蛋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.69,0:19:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚是来调查是什么让桐乃加速的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.61,0:19:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然已经大概预测到了  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.69,0:20:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是桐乃最喜欢的大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.04,0:20:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.50,0:20:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为桐乃搞得那么萎靡不振都是因为见不到超喜欢的大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.19,0:20:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下子变快也是因为大哥哥来洛杉矶了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.12,0:20:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙  怎么产生这种误会了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.67,0:20:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.91,0:20:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听好了  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.16,0:20:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会没有状态都是因为和你一个房间没办法玩工口游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.59,0:20:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有就是见不到黑猫和绫濑那些朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.65,0:20:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她复活也是因为我让她玩了工口游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.41,0:20:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,证据就是她自己说的「玩了下工口游戏终于有干劲了」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.38,0:20:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然细想一下是很过分的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.58,0:20:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她能赢你全是工口游戏之力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.04,0:20:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说也不懂吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.75,0:20:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.63,0:20:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉亚  你说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.93,0:20:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐乃就是见到了她超喜欢的我才复活的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.87,0:21:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.43,0:21:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那如果我也变得超喜欢大哥哥的话  也会跑得更快吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.63,0:21:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能啊  别贴上来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.68,0:21:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京介大哥哥  超喜欢的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.98,0:21:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲  亲…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.20,0:21:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经纪人来接你了哟…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.90,0:21:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要我说几遍同样的话啊  这个萝莉控
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.74,0:21:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了就让我当个萝莉控吧  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.36,0:21:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ByeBye
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.57,0:21:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她走了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.99,0:21:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  可能有点寂寞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.52,0:21:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝莉控
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.48,0:21:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是那种意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.21,0:21:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对了  你是妹控啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.85,0:21:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  妹妹什么的一个就够受了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.38,0:21:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我有事要拜托你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.68,0:21:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.82,0:21:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…这个…有点难说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.91,0:22:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  做我的男朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.75,0:23:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不可能做我妹妹的男朋友我的妹妹也不可能有男朋友  
