[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-12-20 03:14:33
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:CASO_Tsubasa
Original Script:CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwen,方正隶变_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&H004080FF,&H00000000,&H3C000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,0,3,1,2,30,30,15,134
Style: jinggao,方正水柱_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,8,5,5,13,134
Style: op,MS Gothic,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H80000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,1,8,10,10,13,134
Style: opzw,方正黑体_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H80000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,1,2,10,10,12,134
Style: ed,MS Gothic,22,&H00A8333A,&H80000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,4,0,8,10,10,13,134
Style: edzw,方正黑体_GBK,25,&H00A8333A,&H80000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,4,0,2,10,10,12,134
Style: yingwen,Monotype Corsiva,31,&H00FFFFFF,&H004080FF,&H00000000,&H3C000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,0,2,2,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.85,0:00:09.42,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}果て無き夢求める座標なき世界で…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:27.26,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}重なる想い　心突き刺す鼓動
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.81,0:00:34.30,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}静かに続く　ためらいもない詩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.81,0:00:42.02,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}遠く空の彼方から混ざり合った僕らの影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.20,0:00:49.53,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}必然と気まぐれの中　記された記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.03,0:00:53.67,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}すれ違った時間の渦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.78,0:01:01.58,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}朽ち果てても君の声を信じて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.90,0:01:09.70,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}果て無き夢求める座標なき未来で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:17.02,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕が輝無くしても　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.50,0:01:24.17,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君が灯してくれた煌めく胸の炎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.27,0:01:33.00,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}翼に変わる　希望の破片
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.85,0:00:09.42,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在没有向导的世界追寻无尽的梦境…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:27.26,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}重叠的愿望　刺痛着内心跳动
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.81,0:00:34.30,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}持续的寂静　毫无犹豫的诗篇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.81,0:00:42.02,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}遥远天空的另一边合而为一的彼此身影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.20,0:00:49.53,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在必然和偶然之中　刻下了记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.03,0:00:53.67,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}交错的时空旋涡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.78,0:01:01.58,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}纵然已经腐朽也坚信着你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.90,0:01:09.70,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在没有向导的世界追寻无尽的梦境
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:17.02,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}即使不知何时我会丧失自己的光辉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.50,0:01:24.17,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你点燃了胸中的辉煌火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.27,0:01:33.00,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}将希望的碎片化作羽翼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.50,0:23:09.90,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねえこの街が夕闇に染まるときは
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.80,0:23:17.03,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}小さな種を落とすだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.20,0:23:28.86,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}踏み固められた土を「道」だと呼ぶのならば
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.90,0:23:37.72,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}目を閉じることでも「愛」かな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.26,0:23:48.60,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}この星が平らなら　ふたり出会えてなかった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.70,0:23:56.87,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}お互いを遠ざけるように　走っていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.10,0:24:07.30,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}スピードを緩めずに　今はどんなに離れても
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.40,0:24:18.81,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}めぐる軌跡の途中に　また向かい合うのだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.01,0:24:26.30,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}向かい合うのだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.50,0:23:09.90,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}当这条街道被夜幕笼罩之时
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.80,0:23:17.03,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}便会落下那小小的希望之种
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.20,0:23:28.86,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}双脚踏实的土地便被称作「道路」的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.90,0:23:37.72,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那闭上眼睛就是「爱」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.26,0:23:48.60,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果这星球平坦无际　两个人便会无法相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.70,0:23:56.87,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}曾像互相越走越远一般奔走过
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.10,0:24:07.30,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}追寻的速度未曾放慢　如今无论相隔多远
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.40,0:24:18.81,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在巡回的轨迹之中　彼此终究还会再度相逢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.01,0:24:26.30,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}终究还会再度相逢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.50,0:02:25.40,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}本字幕仅限试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版，\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，华盟字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.50,0:02:29.40,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}翻译：丽丽、狗咪；校对、时间：zipwinmax；后期：猫猫拳；繁化：黑羽侖人。
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.66,0:01:52.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去了翅膀的鸟儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.14,0:01:56.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法在像思绪一样广阔的天空中飞来飞去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.30,0:02:01.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我相信着
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.02,0:02:11.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在只要活下去  就能孕育出更多美好的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.04,0:02:21.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无瑕的流浪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.35,0:02:36.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为她应该已经没有什么大碍了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.97,0:02:39.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我打算到城南那边去一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.51,0:02:42.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？那请小心了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.04,0:02:43.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.71,0:02:49.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该出发了 小狼君
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.96,0:02:50.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.68,0:02:58.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去去就回来  小樱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.51,0:03:02.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已经开始有觉醒的征兆了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.66,0:03:04.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.35,0:03:10.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人的内心深处  隐藏着一股深信的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.14,0:03:14.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那是一颗崇高的心的话  慢慢就会…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.27,0:05:03.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小伙子  第一次见到章鱼烧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.65,0:05:06.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来这个叫章鱼烧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.21,0:05:07.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,章鱼烧  章鱼烧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.21,0:05:08.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}这个要怎么吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.21,0:05:11.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}放进嘴里嚼就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.81,0:05:12.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}你在耍我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.71,0:05:15.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}岂敢岂敢  客官请尝尝看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.03,0:05:14.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都想问你一个问题  现在可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.81,0:05:16.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么问题？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.10,0:05:21.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱她  到底是个什么样的女孩？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.74,0:05:23.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和小樱她从小一起长大的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.31,0:05:26.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是以前我们国家的王族的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.61,0:05:27.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问的不是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.86,0:05:33.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想问的是她的本质
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.52,0:05:35.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本质？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.28,0:05:40.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像黑磷遇到的那样  就是生命的本质
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.68,0:05:40.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}谁吃了就是谁赢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.48,0:05:41.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}别都吃了啊  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.49,0:05:43.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是关于在以前的世界遇到的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.91,0:05:48.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了另外一个世界之后  过着和以前完全不一样的生活的这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.56,0:05:49.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.93,0:05:51.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听了那人讲的话之后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.93,0:05:55.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就经常会去考虑有关人的本质的一些事情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.36,0:05:59.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如对事物的考虑方法  胸襟之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.73,0:06:03.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及给周围的人带来的影响等
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.98,0:06:06.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是属于人的本质的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.40,0:06:09.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使生活在不同的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.20,0:06:11.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也总觉得和以前完全一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.53,0:06:19.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  这只是我的感觉而已呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.58,0:06:23.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱的…本质…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.60,0:06:25.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来大家都在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.75,0:06:30.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  由于我的疏忽  小樱她…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.54,0:06:32.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.17,0:06:54.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱不见了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.67,0:06:58.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我稍微走开了一下她就…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.96,0:07:00.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱可以起来了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.89,0:07:01.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.51,0:07:04.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找她
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.28,0:07:07.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找的话  去哪里呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.00,0:07:14.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…但我不能扔下她不管
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.17,0:07:18.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.75,0:07:23.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是没办法的事呢  小樱毕竟失去了记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.84,0:07:27.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  再被奇怪的人盯上了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.25,0:07:28.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可会出事的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.97,0:07:31.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像上次黑磷遇到的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.87,0:07:33.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是黑磷啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.31,0:07:34.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑磷  黑磷…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.03,0:07:37.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.35,0:07:44.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回去看看  说不定小樱已经回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.42,0:07:46.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.22,0:08:00.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱  你到底在哪里…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.93,0:08:12.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  绝对没错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.73,0:08:16.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是之前和那些家伙在一起的小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.08,0:08:18.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那赶快动手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.36,0:08:19.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.70,0:08:23.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不动手？如果抓住那个女孩的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.72,0:08:27.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前的那臭小子和黑小子就得乖乖听我们的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.34,0:08:33.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然  可我不是说过不要做一些粗暴的行为嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.79,0:08:37.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  在这个时候就要…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.27,0:08:42.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐  你好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.88,0:08:43.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.53,0:08:52.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  她没反应呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.32,0:08:58.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  这个女孩是从外国来的  我们的话她听不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.06,0:09:06.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要来吃铁板烧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.26,0:09:08.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}稍等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.66,0:09:11.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}好好  排骨一份  久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.56,0:09:10.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.70,0:09:14.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么看的话  我都不好意思做了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.43,0:09:21.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前很少见吧  铁板烧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.07,0:09:23.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.36,0:09:27.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐  你的名字是？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.11,0:09:31.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字叫什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.93,0:09:35.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.65,0:09:42.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老…老大  她刚才不是在讲我们的语言吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.63,0:09:44.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好像是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.90,0:09:47.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.34,0:09:55.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.54,0:09:58.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  两位客人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.32,0:10:06.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位客人不会是在动这个女孩的坏脑筋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.78,0:10:07.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.68,0:10:10.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么这么说？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.09,0:10:15.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说过有关两位的一些不太好的谣传呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.39,0:10:22.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃  真的很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.30,0:10:30.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到小樱了没有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.56,0:10:32.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有下落啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.84,0:10:34.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也没有找到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.39,0:10:39.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  对了  这个给黑炭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.24,0:10:43.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个个头挺大的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.07,0:10:48.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.35,0:10:51.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就行…了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.39,0:10:53.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可真够乱来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.22,0:10:55.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法伊先生  黑钢先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.21,0:10:59.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们找到小樱没有？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.65,0:11:01.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到处都找遍了  但还是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.37,0:11:04.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样…吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.36,0:11:07.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.36,0:11:09.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞪眼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.40,0:11:15.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？小樱她…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.67,0:11:17.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  她和他们在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.46,0:11:20.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和之前的那个闹事集团？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.49,0:11:22.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我看的非常清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.11,0:11:25.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.31,0:11:31.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有办法
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.09,0:11:34.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,办法…吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.23,0:11:46.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.22,0:11:49.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是我们的藏身之所了  用不着说明的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.85,0:11:52.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少在那里废话  快干
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.98,0:11:59.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个女孩到我们手里的话  那两个臭小子就得听我们的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.94,0:12:03.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再去收拾笙悟他们的队伍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.17,0:12:23.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.68,0:12:25.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.80,0:12:27.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的手下到哪里去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.42,0:12:33.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.74,0:12:38.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已对老大你失败的样子失去了信心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.43,0:12:41.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不想再留在队里了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.56,0:12:47.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都决定要走  所以请不要找我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.55,0:12:49.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全体成员一同
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.91,0:12:54.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.99,0:12:57.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从建立到现在已经25年了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.75,0:13:03.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,历尽千辛万苦才终于把队伍搞到这个声势
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.48,0:13:13.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.17,0:13:17.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没怎么样  都是你那些朋友给害的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.28,0:13:27.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为你们  我的队伍才…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.44,0:13:34.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的队伍…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.63,0:13:38.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能哭
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.94,0:13:43.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能哭
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.16,0:13:56.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我输了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.53,0:14:03.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的能顺利找到吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.03,0:14:08.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我的巧断只有4级  是最低的等级
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.27,0:14:11.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有能找出人的所在位置的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.27,0:14:16.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们所在的位置  也是这样找的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.39,0:14:21.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  厉害的巧断只会跟着内心坚强的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.29,0:14:28.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像笙悟跟小狼那样能用自己的心去操纵巧断的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.03,0:14:34.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以象我这种弱小的人只能操纵弱小的巧断
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.99,0:14:37.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正义君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.24,0:14:42.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但像我这样的人也有能做得到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.20,0:14:45.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请相信我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.49,0:14:48.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.94,0:14:52.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.76,0:15:04.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.97,0:15:09.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起吃铁板烧  还安慰我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.27,0:15:17.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还笑得这么甜  却是我们骗了她并把她带到这里的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.89,0:15:22.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像感到有罪恶感了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.58,0:15:26.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  如果能早点遇到那副笑脸的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.02,0:15:30.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我现在就不会走上歪路了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.44,0:15:33.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我已经决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.25,0:15:36.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么决定？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.50,0:15:46.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要跟我说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.36,0:15:59.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天决定把整个队伍都解散掉  从头再开始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.28,0:16:00.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.14,0:16:04.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些地盘就交给你了  让你经营去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.85,0:16:08.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底发生了什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.79,0:16:14.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我不会说  那个孩子的消息我也不会对任何人说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.65,0:16:16.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.20,0:16:24.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.97,0:16:26.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  不…不得了了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.57,0:16:28.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.90,0:16:31.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱到那里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.54,0:16:38.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.26,0:16:43.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我稍微一不留神她就不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.87,0:16:46.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就发现她攀到那里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.80,0:16:49.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底怎么搞的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.70,0:16:53.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  就是那个孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.72,0:17:06.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笙悟  拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.31,0:17:08.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.19,0:17:24.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.89,0:17:29.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的这么喜欢高的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.47,0:17:30.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.86,0:17:36.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我带你去看漂亮的风景吧  来我这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.39,0:17:47.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好抓紧了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.15,0:17:47.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.51,0:17:59.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次给笙悟那小子占大便宜了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.30,0:18:05.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是最好不过的  保重啊  小樱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.38,0:18:17.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笙悟你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.42,0:18:30.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.91,0:18:37.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羽毛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.33,0:18:42.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的…羽毛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.63,0:18:50.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得要去找了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.69,0:19:10.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被称为翅膀的东西就是人类回忆的实体
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.54,0:19:15.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算失去一切也不会立刻消失
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.33,0:19:25.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这就像快烧尽的蜡烛一样  只能发出最后一瞬间的光辉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.03,0:20:19.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.65,0:20:26.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.75,0:20:46.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接得好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.27,0:20:54.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  看来没受伤呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.65,0:20:56.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱  快醒醒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.20,0:21:10.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…真正的羽毛…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.36,0:21:11.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她自己说的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.06,0:21:13.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笙悟
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.47,0:21:17.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是你的朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.40,0:21:21.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱  小樱她到底说了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.29,0:21:25.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说要找属于自己的羽毛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.63,0:21:28.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羽毛…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.49,0:21:33.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你的胜负  就留到下次见面时吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.89,0:21:55.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许小樱在无意识中
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.28,0:22:01.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己找回了自己的记忆也不一定呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.87,0:22:02.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.84,0:22:06.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.94,0:22:07.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡太久了！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.08,0:22:11.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿作了个梦  梦到自己瞪眼了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.70,0:22:16.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次不要做梦了  要真的能哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.54,0:22:17.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.85,0:22:21.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  那个叫笙悟的说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.98,0:22:28.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了小樱  那些恶徒洗心革面了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.66,0:22:30.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.46,0:22:35.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能洗净恶人心中的恶念的那份温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.13,0:22:38.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许这就是小樱的本质
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.25,0:22:40.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会是这样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.13,0:22:42.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.18,0:22:50.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱  下次你一定会找到属于你的羽毛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.66,0:24:35.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了被救坏人捉去的可爱的摩可拿
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.04,0:24:38.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼他们去了阪神城
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.49,0:24:43.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在那里等待着他们的\N是跟摩可拿一样可爱的坏首领
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.01,0:24:47.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？到底谁要跟坏首领战斗呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.91,0:24:49.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就请继续期待吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.59,0:24:50.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼·年代记
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.85,0:24:53.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第五话  魔术师的对决
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.39,0:24:56.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回会因为「My 巧断」而激动不已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.34,0:21:47.05,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Far in the night,I can see it in every scene of the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.27,0:21:49.81,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}A tiny feather of love.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.07,0:22:00.63,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}I gotta go destiny never finds the way for me,my love.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.92,0:22:10.35,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Even in the night I see your face,in the dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.98,0:22:15.38,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}So I never lose my way to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.73,0:22:18.65,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}I never close my heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.85,0:22:25.05,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}The light is always there.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.46,0:22:34.77,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Time goes by,we can never stay the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.98,0:22:40.21,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Now we come so far from love memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.42,0:22:45.68,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Though your smile has gone,we will never be apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.90,0:22:51.52,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}In our hearts we are one,for love melody.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.72,0:22:59.00,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}The future arrives with your love.


