[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-12-20 03:29:00
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:CASO_Tsubasa
Original Script:CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwen,方正隶变_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&H004080FF,&H00000000,&H3C000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,0,3,1,2,30,30,15,134
Style: jinggao,方正水柱_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,8,5,5,13,134
Style: op,MS Gothic,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H80000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,1,8,10,10,13,134
Style: opzw,方正黑体_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H80000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,2,1,2,10,10,12,134
Style: ed,MS Gothic,22,&H00A8333A,&H80000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,4,0,8,10,10,13,134
Style: edzw,方正黑体_GBK,25,&H00A8333A,&H80000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H50000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,0,4,0,2,10,10,12,134
Style: yingwen,Monotype Corsiva,31,&H00FFFFFF,&H004080FF,&H00000000,&H3C000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,0,2,1,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.85,0:00:09.42,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}果て無き夢求める座標なき世界で…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:27.26,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}重なる想い　心突き刺す鼓動
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.81,0:00:34.30,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}静かに続く　ためらいもない詩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.81,0:00:42.02,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}遠く空の彼方から混ざり合った僕らの影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.20,0:00:49.53,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}必然と気まぐれの中　記された記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.03,0:00:53.67,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}すれ違った時間の渦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.78,0:01:01.58,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}朽ち果てても君の声を信じて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.90,0:01:09.70,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}果て無き夢求める座標なき未来で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:17.02,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕が輝無くしても　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.50,0:01:24.17,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君が灯してくれた煌めく胸の炎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.27,0:01:33.00,op,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}翼に変わる　希望の破片
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.85,0:00:09.42,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在没有向导的世界追寻无尽的梦境…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:27.26,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}重叠的愿望　刺痛着内心跳动
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.81,0:00:34.30,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}持续的寂静　毫无犹豫的诗篇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.81,0:00:42.02,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}遥远天空的另一边合而为一的彼此身影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.20,0:00:49.53,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在必然和偶然之中　刻下了记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.03,0:00:53.67,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}交错的时空旋涡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.78,0:01:01.58,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}纵然已经腐朽也坚信着你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.90,0:01:09.70,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在没有向导的世界追寻无尽的梦境
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:17.02,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}即使不知何时我会丧失自己的光辉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.50,0:01:24.17,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你点燃了胸中的辉煌火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.27,0:01:33.00,opzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}将希望的碎片化作羽翼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.50,0:23:09.90,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねえこの街が夕闇に染まるときは
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.80,0:23:17.03,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}小さな種を落とすだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.20,0:23:28.86,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}踏み固められた土を「道」だと呼ぶのならば
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.90,0:23:37.72,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}目を閉じることでも「愛」かな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.26,0:23:48.60,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}この星が平らなら　ふたり出会えてなかった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.70,0:23:56.87,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}お互いを遠ざけるように　走っていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.10,0:24:07.30,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}スピードを緩めずに　今はどんなに離れても
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.40,0:24:18.81,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}めぐる軌跡の途中に　また向かい合うのだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.01,0:24:26.30,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}向かい合うのだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.50,0:23:09.90,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}当这条街道被夜幕笼罩之时
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.80,0:23:17.03,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}便会落下那小小的希望之种
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.20,0:23:28.86,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}双脚踏实的土地便被称作「道路」的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.90,0:23:37.72,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那闭上眼睛就是「爱」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.26,0:23:48.60,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果这星球平坦无际　两个人便会无法相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.70,0:23:56.87,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}曾像互相越走越远一般奔走过
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.10,0:24:07.30,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}追寻的速度未曾放慢　如今无论相隔多远
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.40,0:24:18.81,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在巡回的轨迹之中　彼此终究还会再度相逢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.01,0:24:26.30,edzw,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1000)}终究还会再度相逢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.00,0:02:28.90,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}本字幕仅限试看之用，如您喜欢本作品，请支持正版，\N若因私自散布传播造成法律及相关一切问题，华盟字幕社概不负责。
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.00,0:02:32.90,jinggao,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}翻译、后期：zipwinmax；校对：苍空翔；时间：林扬茹对不起；繁化：黑羽侖人。
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.16,0:08:22.97,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Far in the night,I can see it in every scene of the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.10,0:08:25.84,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}A tiny feather of love.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.07,0:08:36.52,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}I gotta go destiny never finds the way for me,my love.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.94,0:08:46.52,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Even in the night I see your face,in the dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.86,0:08:52.57,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}So I never lose my way to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.92,0:08:55.53,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}I never close my heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.70,0:09:02.20,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}The light is always there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.25,0:09:08.71,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Time goes by,we can never stay the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.05,0:09:14.19,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Now we come so far from love memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.48,0:09:19.67,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Though your smile has gone,we will never be apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.93,0:09:25.49,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}In our hearts we are one,for love melody.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.71,0:09:30.22,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}The future arrives...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.33,0:09:34.62,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Time goes by,we can never stay the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.88,0:09:40.04,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Now we come so far from love memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.38,0:09:45.72,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Though your smile has gone,we will never be apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.86,0:09:51.35,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}In our hearts we are one,for love melody.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.58,0:09:57.83,yingwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}The future still shines...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.84,0:02:24.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破魔之刀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.09,0:02:11.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那是火焰  我这是水
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.95,0:02:19.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样分胜负才有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.23,0:02:33.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很多队伍都是由坏人组成的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.70,0:02:38.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只有以笙悟为首的队伍决不会向弱者出手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.22,0:02:39.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一支好的队伍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.69,0:02:41.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是当首领的笙悟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.67,0:02:44.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都很崇拜他
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.21,0:02:46.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.10,0:02:56.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是叫小狼对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.51,0:03:01.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很欣赏你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.73,0:03:03.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笙悟  警察来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.52,0:03:05.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正上演精彩的部分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.06,0:03:07.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.17,0:03:07.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.84,0:03:08.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FOWOOO！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.54,0:03:12.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期待下次见面的时候咯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.46,0:03:23.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.32,0:03:40.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.77,0:03:42.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体逐渐变暖和了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.29,0:03:44.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可以暂时安心了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.26,0:03:46.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.37,0:03:49.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的暴风  好像把它弄晕了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.73,0:03:51.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用太担心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.31,0:03:53.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是晕过去而已啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.36,0:03:55.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁在担心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.23,0:03:56.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.62,0:03:59.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外一个才让人担心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.15,0:04:06.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有介绍  真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.03,0:04:07.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.00,0:04:09.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你的巧断吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.88,0:04:10.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.86,0:04:12.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都有可能嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.72,0:04:15.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然见面了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.46,0:04:17.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.33,0:04:21.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是  有洙川空汰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.13,0:04:25.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  这边的是我心爱的爱人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.37,0:04:26.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是岚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.13,0:04:41.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼君啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.09,0:04:43.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很帅气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.81,0:04:48.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱人以前也是个巫女
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.41,0:04:53.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  她的巫女打扮可是很神圣庄严的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.50,0:04:55.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在和我结婚了  就隐退了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.08,0:04:57.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵力可是还存在的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.14,0:05:00.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才可以预知你们到达这个世界的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.89,0:05:05.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我和爱人经营的分租公寓
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.78,0:05:08.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是空房间哦  你们就住下好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.11,0:05:11.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话  真是帮上大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.60,0:05:16.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  为什么要对我们这么好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.18,0:05:18.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我欠侑子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.88,0:05:23.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是欠次元的魔女一个人情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.45,0:05:25.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们待在这个世界的期间里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.38,0:05:26.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就由我来照顾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.49,0:05:28.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.24,0:05:31.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有人敢对我的小甜心出手的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.75,0:05:33.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定不会饶了他哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.12,0:05:35.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切  你干嘛只对我说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.04,0:05:37.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说笑啊说笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.47,0:05:38.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说笑说笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.83,0:05:40.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是认真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.22,0:05:41.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要一直针对我！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.02,0:05:43.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先去泡茶了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.61,0:05:55.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸色好像好了很多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.83,0:05:57.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了那片羽毛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.29,0:06:00.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  接下来要怎么去找呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.21,0:06:02.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这女孩的羽毛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.91,0:06:03.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.29,0:06:05.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.03,0:06:06.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.04,0:06:10.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿能感到羽毛的波动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.44,0:06:13.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  感到有羽毛在附近的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.59,0:06:15.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会这样「瞪眼」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.69,0:06:19.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿刚才也是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.94,0:06:24.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是指感觉到小狼君衣服上的那片吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.94,0:06:25.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是指另外一片
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.77,0:06:29.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狼在战斗的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.13,0:06:33.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里还有另外一片羽毛存在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.23,0:06:34.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.88,0:06:37.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞪眼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.21,0:06:41.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是叫小狼对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.58,0:06:46.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很欣赏你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.92,0:06:47.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笙悟
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.83,0:06:52.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话似乎的确存在呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.32,0:06:53.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到羽毛在周围的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.16,0:06:55.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能告诉我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.19,0:06:57.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.56,0:06:58.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我可没有关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.11,0:07:02.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是要回自己的世界去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.59,0:07:05.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的目的只有这个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.75,0:07:12.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插手管你们的事或是出手帮忙我都没兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.35,0:07:12.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.27,0:07:15.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.77,0:07:18.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会注意不给您添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.75,0:07:23.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是老实啊  小狼君
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.01,0:07:24.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.84,0:07:26.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.51,0:07:27.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.61,0:07:28.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要帮他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.00,0:07:29.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.24,0:07:31.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.84,0:07:32.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.09,0:07:35.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说不要回到原先的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.36,0:07:38.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是最重要的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.40,0:07:39.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.08,0:07:42.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不会危害到性命的话我就帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.03,0:07:44.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我也没其它的事可做
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.03,0:07:46.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.48,0:07:47.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.50,0:07:48.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找到羽毛之前
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.04,0:07:50.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会前往下一个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.37,0:07:52.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也谢谢摩可拿你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.08,0:07:53.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.40,0:09:05.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了  小狼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.78,0:09:37.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  无论如何
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.57,0:09:40.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都不会停止无谓的杀生是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.56,0:09:42.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想变得更强而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.25,0:09:45.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更强  更强  比任何人都要强
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.53,0:09:48.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是为此而战
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.87,0:09:53.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别人是生是死  那和我无关
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.71,0:09:58.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  没有办法了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.61,0:10:05.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在要把你送去异界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.21,0:10:07.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.70,0:10:14.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定会遇到很多很多的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.46,0:10:19.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样  你才会知道强劲的真正意义
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.57,0:10:23.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  虽然离别是很痛苦的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.54,0:10:26.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我还是要目送你离开啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.42,0:10:28.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切！是你强迫我的啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.37,0:10:32.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一件事  我来为你施上法术吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.10,0:10:36.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.84,0:10:39.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是「咒」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.62,0:10:40.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「咒」？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.54,0:10:59.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「咒」是为了让你不再继续无谓的杀生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.87,0:11:01.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.06,0:11:07.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你每杀一个人  你的强劲就会减弱一点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.99,0:11:11.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里？知世公主？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.90,0:11:32.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是梦？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.40,0:11:35.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.75,0:11:45.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  很适合你们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.77,0:11:48.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种打扮即使走在街上也没关系啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.58,0:11:51.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我们出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.70,0:11:54.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱就由我来照料好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.14,0:11:56.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.51,0:12:03.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面是中午的饭钱  三人要一起吃好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.08,0:12:05.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.50,0:12:08.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  为什么给这个小子拿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.42,0:12:10.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他看上去是最可靠的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.06,0:12:12.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.30,0:12:18.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着吧  小樱  我一定会找到羽毛的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.82,0:12:36.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.83,0:12:38.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿感觉不到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.38,0:12:39.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.93,0:12:42.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天就能感觉到羽毛的波动
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.28,0:12:43.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天却感觉不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.23,0:12:46.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么一回事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.07,0:12:48.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑碰你怎么想？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.55,0:12:50.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许你用奇怪的名字叫我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.32,0:12:51.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑大大好恐怖呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.72,0:12:52.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.74,0:13:03.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.74,0:13:04.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.18,0:13:07.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙  绝对错不了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.25,0:13:10.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑碰啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.44,0:13:11.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么那家伙会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.02,0:13:14.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这种事怎么都好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.23,0:13:17.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是「咒」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.35,0:13:22.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住那家伙  让她把那种奇怪的术给我解开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.42,0:13:42.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑钢先生现在到哪里去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.77,0:13:44.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑碰真会给人添麻烦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.62,0:13:48.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边正忙着寻找羽毛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.60,0:13:51.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.61,0:13:58.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像感觉到黑炭所处的位置了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.99,0:14:06.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里有很香的味道飘出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.90,0:14:10.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的话  的确是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.23,0:14:12.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩可拿的肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.39,0:14:14.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.97,0:14:19.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问是几位呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.61,0:14:21.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  三位
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.58,0:14:25.00,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  两位和一只…吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.11,0:14:26.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么这边请
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.60,0:14:28.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国王陛下  为什么会在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.99,0:14:31.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦？国王陛下？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.12,0:14:34.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的店员会帮忙煎好的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.29,0:14:36.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请保持原样等我们过来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.71,0:14:38.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小哥  要一份排骨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.39,0:14:38.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.18,0:14:41.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排骨一份
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.43,0:14:44.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国王陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.73,0:14:46.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是说你以前世界的国王陛下吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.87,0:14:47.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.74,0:14:50.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  旁边叫排骨一份的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.66,0:14:53.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是以前世界的神官吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.77,0:14:54.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.67,0:15:02.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了吧  小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.06,0:15:03.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.40,0:15:05.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱没受伤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.93,0:15:06.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.78,0:15:08.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在问你我妹妹是不是没事！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.78,0:15:19.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  那些羽毛是…公主的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.14,0:15:22.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记…记忆？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.07,0:15:27.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主从出生开始  一直到现在的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.90,0:15:29.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.30,0:15:32.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  那些飞走的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.35,0:15:37.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个世界上已经…不存在了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.10,0:15:38.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.22,0:15:40.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.45,0:15:45.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.46,0:15:49.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妹妹就拜托给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.71,0:15:52.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.61,0:16:00.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  这里决不允许你们踏过一步！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.82,0:16:05.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来的话就请自己动手了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.34,0:16:08.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次元的魔女不是说过了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.37,0:16:14.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到异世界去旅行  是比想像中还要辛苦的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.42,0:16:17.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有各式各样的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.49,0:16:20.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认识的人  在以前的世界遇见过的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.91,0:16:24.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可能正在另一个世界过着截然不同的人生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.16,0:16:26.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同一个样子的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.06,0:16:29.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在不同的世界里或许会相遇无数次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.35,0:16:34.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个人  和小狼君的国家里的那两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.86,0:16:37.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然样子相同  但其实还是不一样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.77,0:16:40.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过「根源」是相同的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.58,0:16:41.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「根源」？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.15,0:16:43.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命的源头
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.98,0:16:46.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性格啊  内心啊  诸如此类的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.19,0:16:49.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是指灵魂吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.21,0:16:51.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.94,0:16:54.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的话  黑钢先生他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.44,0:16:56.94,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也应该是碰见了他原来的世界里的某个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.32,0:17:06.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  去哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.95,0:17:09.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.32,0:17:12.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.24,0:17:16.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特地跑到我们的地盘来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.52,0:17:19.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,省得我们去找你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.43,0:17:22.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你们这些家伙没兴趣  快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.66,0:17:25.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的确没有想找我们  可我们却有事找你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.01,0:17:27.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.00,0:17:34.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以你为诱饵  要挟那个可恶的小鬼加入我们的队伍
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.86,0:17:38.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天虽然失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.98,0:17:41.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我的巧断可是一级的！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.42,0:17:44.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  不想受伤的话就乖乖跟我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.12,0:17:52.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.87,0:17:55.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的巧断可以把身体的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.19,0:17:57.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成像刀刃一样尖锐的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.04,0:17:59.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这一招叫做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.67,0:18:01.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蟹锅旋回
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.88,0:18:12.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就攻过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.96,0:18:14.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.30,0:18:17.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我有剑的话  就能把他们都收拾掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.36,0:18:25.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.54,0:18:29.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的巧断可以把壳上的刺转化为武器
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.31,0:18:30.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这一招叫做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.81,0:18:31.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蟹动落
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.84,0:18:32.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.24,0:18:47.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.91,0:18:49.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以那种东西就想打倒我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.09,0:18:55.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会死
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.23,0:19:01.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我回到原来的世界之前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.40,0:19:07.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到遇到那个家伙之前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.00,0:19:16.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  那家伙的巧断是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.50,0:19:20.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…曾在梦中见过
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.85,0:19:27.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.73,0:19:35.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要让我使用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.81,0:19:42.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你也想大干一场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.26,0:19:48.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种愿望的话  就满足你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.80,0:19:51.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破魔·龙王刃
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.66,0:20:04.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作…作战变更…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.63,0:20:06.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  黑黑的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.32,0:20:09.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也很不错的  加入我们怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.46,0:20:11.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.23,0:20:17.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让我服从的  从来就只有一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.63,0:20:20.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知世
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.89,0:20:47.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天到底发生了什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.35,0:20:50.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讲给我们听听吧  黑磷
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.78,0:20:52.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.79,0:20:54.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑磷根本没有在听嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.11,0:20:57.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  看上去是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.09,0:21:24.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.49,0:21:26.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.09,0:21:28.74,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…睡觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.81,0:21:30.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.66,0:21:33.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  睡觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.87,0:21:38.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  就这样好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.65,0:21:44.63,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安了  小樱
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.83,0:24:34.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好不好  大事不好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.82,0:24:36.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小樱突然不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.57,0:24:38.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找羽毛的时候不见了的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.76,0:24:40.86,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都找遍了仍然找不到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.05,0:24:43.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望不会被坏人给带走了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.54,0:24:46.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？小樱是换了衣服后才出去的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.46,0:24:48.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将会发生什么事呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.24,0:24:49.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就请继续期待吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.05,0:24:51.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼·年代记
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.41,0:24:53.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第四话  无瑕的流浪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.08,0:24:56.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回的小樱会让人期待不已


