[Script Info]
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080
Aegisub Video Aspect Ratio: c1.777778

[Aegisub Project Garbage]
Audio File: ../做种/[Moozzi2] Nande Koko ni Sensei ga! - 13 Unaired [ Uncensored Ver. ] (BD 1920x1080 x.264 Flac).mkv
Video File: ../做种/[Moozzi2] Nande Koko ni Sensei ga! - 13 Unaired [ Uncensored Ver. ] (BD 1920x1080 x.264 Flac).mkv
Video AR Mode: 4
Video AR Value: 1.777778
Video Zoom Percent: 0.500000
Active Line: 2
Video Position: 15718

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial,30.00,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0.00,0.00,1,3.00,3.00,2,15,15,15,1
Style: Sub-CN,方正准圆_GBK,65.00,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H1ED36F04,&H78000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0.00,0.00,1,1.50,0.00,2,20,20,10,1
Style: Sub-JP,A-OTF Shin Maru Go Pr6N M,50.00,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H1ED36F04,&H78000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0.00,0.00,1,2.25,0.00,2,30,30,18,1
Style: staff,方正兰亭圆_GBK_中,55.00,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H1ED36F04,&H78000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0.00,0.00,1,2.25,0.00,2,20,20,20,1
Style: OPJP,SeuratCapiePro-EB,60.00,&H008000E0,&H000000FF,&H00A23BE8,&H00E6E6E6,0,0,0,0,100,100,9.00,0.00,1,5.50,0.00,2,30,30,30,1
Style: OPJP1,SeuratCapiePro-EB,60.00,&H008000E0,&H000000FF,&H00FFEAFF,&H00E6E6E6,0,0,0,0,100,100,9.00,0.00,1,2.80,0.00,2,30,30,30,1
Style: EDCN,腾祥嘉丽准粗圆GB18030,54.00,&H00EEF3EC,&H000000FF,&H00BD3AE9,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,9.00,0.00,1,3.00,0.00,8,30,30,30,1
Style: OPCN,腾祥嘉丽粗圆GB18030,60.00,&H008000E0,&H000000FF,&H1EA23BE8,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0.00,0.00,1,5.50,0.00,2,20,20,12,1
Style: OPCN1,腾祥嘉丽粗圆GB18030,60.00,&H008000E0,&H000000FF,&H1EFFEAFF,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0.00,0.00,1,2.80,0.00,2,20,20,12,1
Style: EDJP,SeuratCapiePro-B,54.00,&H00EEF3EC,&H000000FF,&H00BD3AE9,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,9.00,0.00,1,4.00,0.00,2,30,30,30,1
Style: ps,方正兰亭圆_GBK,60.00,&H008000E0,&H000000FF,&H00A23BE8,&H00E6E6E6,-1,0,0,0,100,100,9.00,0.00,1,5.50,0.00,2,30,30,30,1
Style: ps1,方正兰亭圆_GBK,60.00,&H008000E0,&H000000FF,&H00FFEAFF,&H00E6E6E6,-1,0,0,0,100,100,9.00,0.00,1,2.80,0.00,2,30,30,30,1
Style: ps2,@方正兰亭圆_GBK_中,55.00,&H00020C1A,&H000000FF,&H00647D90,&H00E6E6E6,-1,0,0,0,100,100,9.00,0.00,1,1.50,0.00,2,30,30,30,1
Style: ps3,方正兰亭圆_GBK_特,100.00,&H009DE1EA,&H000000FF,&H00F208E4,&H00E6E6E6,-1,0,0,0,100,100,9.00,0.00,1,14.00,0.00,2,30,30,30,1
Style: Default_AGE2_,方正准圆_GBK,24.00,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H10000010,&H70000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0.75,0.00,1,3.00,0.00,2,8,8,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,staff,,0,0,0,,*********************staff*********************
Comment: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:43.23,OPJP,,0,0,0,,*********************OPJP*********************
Comment: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:43.23,OPCN,,0,0,0,,*********************OPCN*********************
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,EDJP,,0,0,0,,*********************EDJP*********************
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,EDCN,,0,0,0,,*********************EDCN*********************
Comment: 0,0:11:21.68,0:11:29.75,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,*********************正片*********************
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.92,0:01:12.84,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}この胸に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.84,0:01:14.05,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}My Darling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.05,0:01:16.01,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}太ももに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.01,0:01:17.18,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}My Body
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.18,0:01:19.10,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}ね　お尻に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.10,0:01:20.26,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}My Feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.26,0:01:23.39,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}触れてみたいのでしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.39,0:01:25.27,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}どう 惚けても
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.27,0:01:26.48,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}You Fake It
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.48,0:01:28.35,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}もう 無駄だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.35,0:01:30.06,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}You Fall in Love Me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.44,0:01:31.57,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}ちゃんと顔に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.57,0:01:33.19,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}If I want you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.40,0:01:34.61,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}書いてあるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.61,0:01:35.53,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}Together
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.90,0:01:41.66,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}あなたは夢の 中で私に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.04,0:01:47.33,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}どんなことして 見上げてるのかしら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.33,0:01:49.83,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}ああ～Yes I love You
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.83,0:01:52.63,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}偶然が　重なって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.63,0:01:57.30,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}何故かあなたに 惹かれちゃてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.30,0:01:59.26,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}Oh　Baby Baby  Touch Me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.26,0:02:01.97,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}運命が交差して
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.97,0:02:06.60,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}二人がいつか 結ばれたら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.60,0:02:08.14,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}抱きしめてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.14,0:02:10.98,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}すべてあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.44,0:02:17.24,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}彼氏になったらね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.53,0:02:20.24,OPJP,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}Darling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.92,0:01:12.84,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}この胸に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.84,0:01:14.05,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}My Darling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.05,0:01:16.01,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}太ももに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.01,0:01:17.18,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}My Body
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.18,0:01:19.10,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}ね　お尻に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.10,0:01:20.26,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}My Feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.26,0:01:23.39,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}触れてみたいのでしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.39,0:01:25.27,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}どう 惚けても
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.27,0:01:26.48,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}You Fake It
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.48,0:01:28.35,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}もう 無駄だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.35,0:01:30.06,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}You Fall in Love Me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.44,0:01:31.57,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}ちゃんと顔に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.57,0:01:33.19,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}If I want you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.40,0:01:34.61,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}書いてあるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.61,0:01:35.53,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,1060)}{\an3}Together
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.90,0:01:41.66,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}あなたは夢の 中で私に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.04,0:01:47.33,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}どんなことして 見上げてるのかしら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.33,0:01:49.83,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}ああ～Yes I love You
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.83,0:01:52.63,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}偶然が　重なって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.63,0:01:57.30,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}何故かあなたに 惹かれちゃてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.30,0:01:59.26,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}Oh　Baby Baby  Touch Me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.26,0:02:01.97,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}運命が交差して
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.97,0:02:06.60,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}二人がいつか 結ばれたら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.60,0:02:08.14,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}抱きしめてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.14,0:02:10.98,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}すべてあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.44,0:02:17.24,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}彼氏になったらね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.53,0:02:20.24,OPJP1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,1055)}Darling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.92,0:01:12.84,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}我这丰胸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.84,0:01:14.05,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.05,0:01:16.01,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}我这美腿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.01,0:01:17.18,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}我的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.18,0:01:19.10,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}我这翘臀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.10,0:01:20.26,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}我的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.26,0:01:23.39,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}想要触碰吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.39,0:01:25.27,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}再怎么装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.27,0:01:26.48,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.48,0:01:28.35,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}都没有用哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.35,0:01:30.06,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}爱恋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.44,0:01:31.57,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}全都在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.57,0:01:33.19,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}渴望
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.40,0:01:34.61,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}写得很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.61,0:01:35.53,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}共度
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.90,0:01:41.66,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}你在梦中对我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.04,0:01:47.33,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}做了什么 而偷偷地笑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.33,0:01:49.83,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}啊 ～是的 我爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.83,0:01:52.63,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}种种偶然 重合于此
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.63,0:01:57.30,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}为何我会 倾心于你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.30,0:01:59.26,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}宝贝 宝贝 请触碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.26,0:02:01.97,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}二人命运 互相交错
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.97,0:02:06.60,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}我们何时 喜结连理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.60,0:02:08.14,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}就请抱紧我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.14,0:02:10.98,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}把我的一切都献给你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.44,0:02:17.24,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}待成为我另一半的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.53,0:02:20.24,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}亲爱的~
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.92,0:01:12.84,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}我这丰胸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.84,0:01:14.05,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.05,0:01:16.01,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}我这美腿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.01,0:01:17.18,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}我的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.18,0:01:19.10,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}我这翘臀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.10,0:01:20.26,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}我的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.26,0:01:23.39,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}想要触碰吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.39,0:01:25.27,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}再怎么装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.27,0:01:26.48,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.48,0:01:28.35,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}都没有用哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.35,0:01:30.06,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}爱恋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.44,0:01:31.57,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}全都在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.57,0:01:33.19,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}渴望
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.40,0:01:34.61,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}写得很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.61,0:01:35.53,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(1900,80)}{\an3}共度
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.90,0:01:41.66,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}你在梦中对我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.04,0:01:47.33,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}做了什么 而偷偷地笑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.33,0:01:49.83,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}啊 ～是的 我爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.83,0:01:52.63,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}种种偶然 重合于此
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.63,0:01:57.30,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}为何我会 倾心于你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.30,0:01:59.26,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}宝贝 宝贝 请触碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.26,0:02:01.97,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}二人命运 互相交错
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.97,0:02:06.60,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}我们何时 喜结连理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.60,0:02:08.14,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}就请抱紧我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.14,0:02:10.98,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}把我的一切都献给你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.44,0:02:17.24,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}待成为我另一半的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.53,0:02:20.24,OPCN1,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,80)}亲爱的~
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.64,0:11:15.90,EDJP,,0,0,0,,小さな思いでも どんどん膨らんで
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.36,0:11:21.99,EDJP,,0,0,0,,頼りない背中 気つけば目で追っていた
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.99,0:11:32.42,EDJP,,0,0,0,,教科書にはない本当の 君の気持ちが知りたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.42,0:11:34.84,EDJP,,0,0,0,,教えて　きゅん　きゅん　きゅん　きゅん　
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.84,0:11:38.30,EDJP,,0,0,0,,あの時よりもずっとむちゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.30,0:11:43.84,EDJP,,0,0,0,,チャイム鳴っても　止まらない　大好き
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.84,0:11:46.22,EDJP,,0,0,0,,ときめき　だん　だん　だん　だん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.22,0:11:49.64,EDJP,,0,0,0,,早とちりする　恋はかな　
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.64,0:11:57.69,EDJP,,0,0,0,,いつも夢見ちゃう 君からの りんご色のメモリーズ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.64,0:11:15.90,EDCN,,0,0,0,,小小的思念 渐渐地膨胀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.36,0:11:21.99,EDCN,,0,0,0,,那不可靠的后背 不禁注视着你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.99,0:11:32.42,EDCN,,0,0,0,,我想知道你真正的心意 而不是教科书里的词条
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.42,0:11:34.84,EDCN,,0,0,0,,告诉我吧 紧张好紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.84,0:11:38.30,EDCN,,0,0,0,,比起当初更加恋慕你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.30,0:11:43.84,EDCN,,0,0,0,,就算铃声响起 也无法停止 对你的喜爱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.84,0:11:46.22,EDCN,,0,0,0,,心跳不止 渐渐不断地
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.22,0:11:49.64,EDCN,,0,0,0,,变得胡思乱想 这是恋爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.64,0:11:57.69,EDCN,,0,0,0,,梦想得到来自于你的 苹果色回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.95,0:02:27.96,ps,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(1646,882)}第十三节课
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.95,0:02:27.96,ps1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(1646,882)}第十三节课
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.35,0:00:04.48,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,空气果然不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.61,0:00:06.90,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,来了真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.23,0:00:10.76,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,小高 有卖温泉馒头的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.76,0:00:13.75,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,现在吃的话晚饭就吃不下了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.75,0:00:15.49,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,光姐忍一忍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.03,0:00:20.80,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,感觉田中带着女朋友还是很违和呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.80,0:00:23.58,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,别废话 马上就让你适应
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.96,0:00:27.59,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,也帮我拿行李 你不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.92,0:00:29.42,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,完全没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.05,0:00:33.30,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我们赶快去酒店登记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.76,0:00:36.34,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,现在看起来可能要下雨了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.68,0:00:37.60,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.51,0:00:42.89,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,到了四月 我们毕业后一起去了慰劳旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.77,0:00:45.44,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,本应这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.10,0:00:48.77,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,各位客人 你们好像没预订啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:51.78,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,为什么会发生这样的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.49,0:02:25.91,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,怎么会 佐藤 我明明预约了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.91,0:02:27.76,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,冷静一下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.76,0:02:30.38,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,请问 今天还有空房间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.17,0:02:34.80,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是的 双人房的话还有两间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.38,0:02:37.64,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,双人房两间是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.64,0:02:39.47,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,多出了一半人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.13,0:02:42.39,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我们去网吧也行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.80,0:02:44.70,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,可以和小高通宵打游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.70,0:02:45.97,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,还是睡觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.39,0:02:48.02,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我们也去其他地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.60,0:02:49.23,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.64,0:02:51.53,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我反正去哪都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.53,0:02:52.20,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.20,0:02:54.36,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,因为是我的错 我们应该出去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.36,0:02:56.44,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,那么 大家明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.69,0:03:00.84,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,别放在心上 我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.84,0:03:02.84,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,通宵打网游吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.84,0:03:05.83,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,明天还要观光 让我稍微睡一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.45,0:03:11.71,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这位客人 你要住吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.17,0:03:15.77,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,既然这样我们就接受大家的好意吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.77,0:03:17.13,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.13,0:03:20.06,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,你有目的地吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.06,0:03:23.09,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,没事 我查了一下预定了其他的旅馆
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.93,0:03:24.76,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,真有你的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.35,0:03:28.39,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,那边的旅馆 从房间里能看见外面的星星
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.14,0:03:30.70,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,想看星星
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.70,0:03:32.07,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.07,0:03:34.52,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,观察星空也是旅游的目的之一
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.02,0:03:37.07,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,但是今天的天气看星星就
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.69,0:03:38.94,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,下起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.44,0:03:40.53,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,总之我们快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.95,0:03:43.03,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,在鹿儿岛也下雨了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.91,0:03:45.78,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,田中肯定是雨男
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.74,0:03:47.97,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.97,0:03:48.83,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.91,0:03:52.67,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我可能也是雨女
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.21,0:03:54.79,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我们一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.84,0:04:01.44,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,太可爱了 鼓起勇气告白真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.44,0:04:03.97,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我一定要保护好她的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.55,0:04:07.16,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不能因为是晚上就各种胡来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.16,0:04:08.47,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,可能会让她失望
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.89,0:04:12.29,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不过至今为止的经历已经让我升级了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.29,0:04:13.74,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,肯定靠平常心就能
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.74,0:04:14.69,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,找到旅馆了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.06,0:04:17.61,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,爱情旅馆
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.02,0:04:20.40,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,平常心可能没用了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.95,0:04:25.97,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.97,0:04:28.41,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不好 这家伙好硬
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.87,0:04:30.95,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这样怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.62,0:04:36.25,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,好的击破了 就这样一直玩到早上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.83,0:04:37.96,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,还要玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.38,0:04:40.61,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,而且你为什么穿这么少
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.61,0:04:43.47,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这样更舒服哦 而且这里除了你没有别人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.80,0:04:46.47,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,差不多该睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.89,0:04:48.45,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,怎么回事小高
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.45,0:04:50.39,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,一直说睡觉睡觉的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.81,0:04:54.14,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,难不成「睡觉」是这个意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.52,0:04:56.50,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,田中他们说的毕业旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.50,0:04:58.40,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,想让自己在那个方面也毕业吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.15,0:05:00.09,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.09,0:05:01.84,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,第一次在网吧什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.84,0:05:03.36,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,至少要在旅馆里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.49,0:05:06.07,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,光姐怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.78,0:05:07.37,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.74,0:05:10.38,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不知道田中他们找到旅馆了没有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.38,0:05:12.25,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,他们两个应该没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.75,0:05:13.44,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.44,0:05:15.43,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,在这里被小高出手的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.43,0:05:16.54,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,会抵抗不了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.54,0:05:17.33,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,小高
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.04,0:05:19.54,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不行了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.17,0:05:23.17,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我去洗澡了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.17,0:05:24.76,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,光姐 衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.43,0:05:29.39,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,雨中的露天浴池 真有意趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.85,0:05:31.72,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,可是真的没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.06,0:05:36.16,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,把其他人晾在外面只有我自己享受
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.16,0:05:38.60,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不要再消沉了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.98,0:05:40.73,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,大家一定都很开心的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.40,0:05:43.36,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,你真的是这么想吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.86,0:05:46.99,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,嗯 因为都和喜欢的人在一起嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.53,0:05:48.78,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,加奈不也是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.32,0:05:52.37,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,那倒也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.25,0:05:57.50,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,但是加奈又恢复了精神 真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.83,0:06:00.21,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,佐藤君很担心你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.75,0:06:01.88,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,佐藤吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.59,0:06:07.32,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,进来了 这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.32,0:06:09.90,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,难道我被千鹤引诱了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.90,0:06:13.81,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,怎么办太突然了我还没做好心理准备
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.81,0:06:15.60,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,因为我还是个处男啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.93,0:06:19.91,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,但是 如果退缩的话 会被笑话是处男的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.91,0:06:22.36,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,在这里我一定要坚决一点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.98,0:06:26.22,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,对于我这种经验丰富的人来说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.22,0:06:27.65,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这里还算不错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.03,0:06:30.49,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,从房间里看星星原来就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.16,0:06:35.45,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,在主页明明写着能看见真的星星似的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.16,0:06:37.50,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,最讨厌虚伪了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.50,0:06:39.08,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.08,0:06:42.35,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,其实我是没有经验吓得发抖的处男
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.35,0:06:46.74,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我会努力的 今晚请好好指导我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.74,0:06:48.09,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,你怎么突然
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.38,0:06:51.39,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,要是冷的话就先去洗澡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.22,0:06:56.15,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是 那我现在就去洗澡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.15,0:06:58.10,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我会把全身每一块皮肤都洗干净
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.73,0:07:00.60,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,为什么慌慌张张的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.85,0:07:08.11,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an7\bord4\fs45\3c&H000000&}馆内指南
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.85,0:07:08.11,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an7\bord4\fs45\3c&H000000&}浪漫的能看见星空的旅馆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.85,0:07:08.11,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an7\bord4\fs45\3c&H000000&}本店立志成为日本最浪漫的爱情旅馆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.56,0:07:05.48,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这 这里是爱情旅馆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.98,0:07:08.03,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,原来如此 怪不得他那么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.74,0:07:12.74,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,该怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.41,0:07:17.75,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,热水真不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.54,0:07:19.54,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,你回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.00,0:07:22.21,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,露天浴池很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.83,0:07:25.38,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,嗯 非常舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.80,0:07:27.92,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,得感谢大家的谦让啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.38,0:07:29.64,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.64,0:07:31.98,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,也让佐藤担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.98,0:07:32.72,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,没有没有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.60,0:07:37.05,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,刚才是什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.05,0:07:39.79,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,隔壁应该是铃木他们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.79,0:07:41.64,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs60}怎么样 舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.85,0:07:44.73,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs60}铃木君的真舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.27,0:07:47.11,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs60}和这边一起刺激的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.57,0:07:49.98,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs60}用手弄那两个地方的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.98,0:07:50.99,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,铃木
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.36,0:07:52.86,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,什么时候技术那么好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.99,0:07:52.82,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs60}我还要~
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.16,0:07:54.77,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs60}好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.77,0:07:56.91,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,松风老师和铃木玩真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.62,0:08:00.34,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这个力度怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.34,0:08:03.05,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,嗯 真舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.05,0:08:04.17,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,那 接下来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.25,0:08:06.61,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,那里不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.61,0:08:08.25,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.21,0:08:10.51,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,怎么办 佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.05,0:08:12.68,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,佐…佐藤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.81,0:08:24.40,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,加奈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.23,0:08:26.15,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,一郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.20,0:08:39.04,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.04,0:08:41.58,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,为什么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.08,0:08:45.42,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,本来想回应田中的期待
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.79,0:08:46.92,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我也进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.88,0:08:49.59,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,能看见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.59,0:08:50.59,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.96,0:08:53.26,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我也因为没经验而不安
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.92,0:08:55.55,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,因为是保健老师
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.89,0:08:57.59,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,多少还是能教你一点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.59,0:08:59.35,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这难道是保健课吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.10,0:09:02.60,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,然后在说明体位的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.18,0:09:04.44,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这是骑乘位
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.81,0:09:07.52,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,第一次的话用正常位比较合适
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.94,0:09:08.84,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,换姿势吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.84,0:09:10.40,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,触碰到他的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.53,0:09:14.15,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,出来太多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.61,0:09:15.91,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.49,0:09:18.45,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.87,0:09:19.83,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.16,0:09:23.41,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我才应该道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.79,0:09:30.47,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,我太差劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.47,0:09:31.88,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,太逊了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.26,0:09:36.40,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,安定下来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.40,0:09:37.27,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.27,0:09:38.63,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,但是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.63,0:09:40.18,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这么不中用的男朋友…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.55,0:09:41.26,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.72,0:09:43.39,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不管什么样的田中君我都喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.68,0:09:45.48,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.32,0:09:54.19,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,而且失败的话 再来一次就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.69,0:09:55.66,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.66,0:09:57.28,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,下次不要出错了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.70,0:09:59.37,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.74,0:10:05.83,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,立花老师还没来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.21,0:10:08.58,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,快到约好的早餐时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.92,0:10:10.16,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.16,0:10:11.63,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,好像来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.17,0:10:14.93,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,对不起 我们迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.93,0:10:16.31,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.31,0:10:17.76,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,怎么感觉你们很开心嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.76,0:10:21.97,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,不会再让你说我和女朋友在一起有违和感了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.51,0:10:23.65,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是吧千鹤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.65,0:10:24.77,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,有违和感
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.02,0:10:28.64,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,怎么了前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.02,0:10:30.86,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,刚才还很幸福的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.27,0:10:32.31,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,你有没有听啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.82,0:10:33.82,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,你认为怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.57,0:10:36.44,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,咦 立花老师
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.86,0:10:38.60,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,摇摇晃晃的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.60,0:10:39.70,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是受伤了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.03,0:10:41.62,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,感觉还在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.24,0:10:43.80,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,违和感很强
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.80,0:10:45.09,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.09,0:10:45.95,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.00,0:10:48.08,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,那 那是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.17,0:10:50.76,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,恭喜你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.76,0:10:52.07,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.07,0:10:53.75,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,比起这个先听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.75,0:10:55.56,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,昨天小高啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.56,0:10:58.09,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,光姐那个不许说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.64,0:11:11.06,Sub-CN,,0,0,0,,
