[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:千夏字幕
Original Script:千夏字幕組
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,汉仪秀英体简,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0093550F,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.90,0:00:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.63,0:00:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学生会最大的谜团即将被揭晓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.28,0:00:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.45,0:00:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不会告诉向日葵的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.48,0:00:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就知道了 我也是学生会的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.60,0:00:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下地狱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.06,0:00:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么反而你生气啊



