[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:千夏字幕
Original Script:千夏字幕組
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,汉仪秀英体简,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0093550F,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.66,0:00:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我必须要和向日葵一起做预告
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.84,0:00:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.93,0:00:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们两个平时很少单独和其他人交流啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.95,0:00:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底该说些什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.26,0:00:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然觉得有点悲剧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.92,0:00:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.25,0:00:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(＿TдT)