[Script Info]
Title:oreimo
Original Script:澄空学园&华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00287ED7,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.53,0:00:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妹妹们  过来集合
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.08,0:00:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.72,0:00:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事啊  瑠璃姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.37,0:00:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据我夜观星象  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.70,0:00:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个明天可以通过沐浴日光获得新生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.01,0:00:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们必须去外面玩耍  天黑之前不准回家
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.49,0:00:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  不要嘛  好热的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.43,0:00:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人您呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.25,0:00:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于夜之一族来说太阳乃是大敌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.68,0:00:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就留在府邸凝视这片永恒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.47,0:00:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要午睡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欲知真相  请看下集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.66,0:00:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我不可能和学妹留下一整个夏天的回忆」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.62,0:00:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整个夏天的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.95,0:00:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道会是…
