[Script Info]
Title: Kara no Kyoukai Remix -Gate of seventh heaven-
Original Script: 未设定
Original Translation:bwfjc
Original Timing:bwfjc
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;EP
Style: Default,华文中宋,55,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00B36900,&HA0B36900,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: EP,华文中宋,50,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,7,30,30,10,1
Style: JP,Kozuka Mincho Pro H,50,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,7,30,30,10,1
Style: CH,华文中宋,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00B36900,&HA0B36900,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,7,30,30,10,1
Style: JP1,Kozuka Mincho Pro H,50,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,30,30,10,1
Style: CH1,华文中宋,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00B36900,&HA0B36900,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,30,30,10,1
Style: STAFF,华文中宋,53,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00B36900,&HA0B36900,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.00,0:01:30.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,字幕制作:bwfjc
Dialogue: 0,1:01:20.00,1:01:28.00,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制作仅供交流学习翻译技巧之用，请勿用于商业活动
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------<君が光に変えて行く>------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.90,0:02:44.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あたたかな風の中で
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.01,0:02:52.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰かが呼んでる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.19,0:02:59.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗闇を惜しむように
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.26,0:03:10.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜明けが始まる
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.55,0:03:18.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日はきっと
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.53,0:03:25.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綺麗な空に
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.47,0:03:40.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀色の虹がかかるでしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.26,0:03:46.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなに哀しい景色を
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.01,0:03:53.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君が光に変えて行く
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.20,0:04:01.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小さな涙の粒さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.35,0:04:08.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝石のように落ちてく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.77,0:04:18.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未来の中へ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.35,0:04:29.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心には秘密がある
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.22,0:04:36.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも触れたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.58,0:04:44.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,触れ合えば壊れて行く
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.22,0:04:51.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躊躇いは螺旋の中へ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.51,0:04:57.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,橋を渡った河の向こうまで
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.30,0:05:01.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日はきっと…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.93,0:05:04.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真昼の中で
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.04,0:05:11.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春は甘く深く香るのでしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.49,0:05:14.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢から醒めて
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.87,0:05:23.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人は何を探すの
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.88,0:05:51.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなに明るい世界へ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.43,0:05:58.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君が私を連れて行く
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.43,0:06:05.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眩しさにまだ立ち竦む
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.39,0:06:12.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背中をそっと抱きしめる
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.41,0:06:18.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信じることの儚さを
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.27,0:06:26.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君が光に変えて行く
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.28,0:06:33.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めた朝には涙が
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.18,0:06:40.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝石のように落ちてく
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.25,0:06:50.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未来の中へ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------<ARIA>----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.12,0:07:57.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ユメのカケラ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.09,0:08:03.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君がくれた
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.96,0:08:13.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明けない夜に潜む
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.61,0:08:20.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄り添う星
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.25,0:08:27.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一つ消えて
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.15,0:08:39.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜明けのARIAが響いた
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.31,0:08:44.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もうこの止まない雨の中で
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.93,0:08:50.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨日に怯えることもない
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.77,0:08:56.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今　君を無くした未来は
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.12,0:09:04.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始まったばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.45,0:09:10.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果てない闇の中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.06,0:09:16.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君がくれた篝火が
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.84,0:09:22.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伽藍のこの胸に
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.65,0:09:32.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生まれたいのちを照らしている…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.45,0:09:51.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消えたものと
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.27,0:09:57.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,変わらぬもの
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.73,0:10:06.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無惨な空が光る
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.29,0:10:14.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別れを告げ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.65,0:10:20.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微笑み合い
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.18,0:10:32.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂しい ARIAを重ねて…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.75,0:11:01.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ねぇ、人は何時まで独りで
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.56,0:11:06.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二人に焦がれて行くのだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.14,0:11:13.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだ　君の綺麗な未来は
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.56,0:11:21.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始まったばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.69,0:11:33.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,優しさを知らない
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.34,0:11:38.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君がくれた優しさが
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.16,0:11:44.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伽藍のこの胸に
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.85,0:11:51.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名も無き光を灯している
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.46,0:11:56.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤独の船を漕ぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.51,0:12:01.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,篝火は嘆き集う
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.25,0:12:08.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伽藍の世界には
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.18,0:12:19.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数多のARIAが響いている…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------<傷跡>----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.82,0:16:30.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静けさから歩き出す
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.07,0:16:35.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだ見ぬ愛の景色へ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.46,0:16:39.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この痛みを信じたいの
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.07,0:16:47.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.69,0:17:08.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方が触れた胸に優しい傷が一つ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.16,0:17:17.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隠していた涙が紅に零れ落ちて
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.06,0:17:26.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷たい肌の上にやっと灯した花びら
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.71,0:17:35.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私がここにいる　さいわいを歌うよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.76,0:17:39.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう夢も終わる
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.94,0:17:44.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星くずが消える頃
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.47,0:17:54.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ねえ、生きていると分かるほど抱きしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.91,0:18:03.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静けさから生まれて
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.30,0:18:07.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだぬくもりも知らず
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.71,0:18:12.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ただいのちに届きたいの
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.54,0:18:18.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.67,0:18:36.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なつかしいなつのあめ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.95,0:18:40.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私を見送ってね
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.16,0:18:45.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信じ合う始まりへ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.57,0:18:50.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣きながら行けるように
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.31,0:18:54.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よろこびもかなしみも
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.63,0:18:58.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刻みつけたい深く
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.87,0:19:03.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貴方とここにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.56,0:19:08.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さいわいの名残に
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.59,0:19:17.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星くずが消える頃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.04,0:19:30.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初めて見る光の中で
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.85,0:19:51.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳で　くちづけで
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.17,0:19:56.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋した跡を下さい
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.63,0:20:05.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生きることに貫かれて泣いてみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.47,0:20:09.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静けさから歩き出す
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.99,0:20:14.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだ見ぬ遠い夜明けへ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.37,0:20:18.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ただ願いを叶えたいの
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.07,0:20:27.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------<Interlude#1>-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.09,0:23:26.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜明けへ急ぐ電車の窓にもたれて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.31,0:23:32.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落ちてくる星を集めて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.95,0:23:41.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢のパズルは欠片一つ足りなくて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.86,0:23:45.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同じようなものを
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.64,0:23:49.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,みんな探してるけど
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.43,0:23:54.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつ全部違うよね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.42,0:24:02.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君は何処へ行くの
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.45,0:24:16.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日になれば綺麗な空に
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.28,0:24:21.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀の虹が
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.24,0:24:25.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇を抜けて君の元へ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.10,0:24:33.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光を届けるだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.43,0:24:40.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君へと続く夜を
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.00,0:24:46.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕へと続く夜を
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.68,0:24:50.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遙かな道を
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.44,0:24:53.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃げて行く水
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.93,0:24:57.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,止まらない風
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.78,0:25:01.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜明けへ急ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.62,0:25:05.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,満ち潮の歌
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.48,0:25:12.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,橋を渡った河の向こうへ
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.13,0:25:20.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眩しい夏の真昼の中へ
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.17,0:25:28.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君は何処へ行くの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------<Sprinter>------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.58,0:26:39.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君と出会い
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.42,0:26:43.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叶わぬ夢を見た
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.58,0:26:56.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それはたった一秒で越える永遠
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.99,0:27:02.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm calling　君を
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.19,0:27:08.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守ってあげたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.87,0:27:21.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸ばした指も震えてるそのまま  抱きしめた
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.67,0:27:26.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕等に出来る事はただ、生きているんだと
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.26,0:27:28.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力尽きるまで
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.59,0:27:33.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成す術無く叫び続ける、それだけなんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.51,0:27:35.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君に届く？　僕が届く？
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.08,0:27:42.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絶望の甘さ打ち砕いて走り出すんだ　今すぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.99,0:27:45.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,螺旋の果てまで
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.36,0:27:56.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm calling　遠く足掻く僕の唄が
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.85,0:28:07.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君の頬を空に向けられたら
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.43,0:28:14.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独りじゃない…
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.39,0:28:26.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剝き出しの真実が　こんなカラクリの心にも
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.49,0:28:33.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,溢れ出すほど詰まっていたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.47,0:28:39.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光の早やさで消えて行く昨日へ手を振って
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.91,0:28:45.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何処までも明るい砂漠を
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.01,0:28:56.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今、僕等は時を蹴り走る
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.81,0:29:07.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風に向かい破れた旗を振り
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.47,0:29:21.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君のいない道を　僕は僕の為
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.36,0:29:28.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行くんだ…
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.75,0:29:33.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,螺旋の果てまで…
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.08,0:29:38.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君に会いたい
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.11,0:29:44.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君が恋しい
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.16,0:29:50.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君に会いたい
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.11,0:29:56.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君が愛しい
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.91,0:30:08.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm calling 僕がここに居た証は
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.83,0:30:20.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今もきっと君の瞳の中
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.85,0:30:32.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm calling 閉じる螺旋に逆らって
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.14,0:30:44.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哭いて叫んで消えて行く僕等は
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.94,0:30:52.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生きて、いるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.11,0:31:05.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此所に、にいるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------<fairytale>-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.01,0:39:43.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子供の頃に置いてきた
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.54,0:39:48.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢を思い出した
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.11,0:39:54.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若草色の哀しみを
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.85,0:40:00.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,細く甘く歌う
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.43,0:40:05.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,my fairy tale
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.10,0:40:11.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何も終わることのない
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.13,0:40:17.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠を知っていた
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.87,0:40:23.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう誰も語らない
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.19,0:40:31.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二人の物語
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.78,0:40:36.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キスを一つ残して
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.03,0:40:42.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君は何処へ行く
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.80,0:40:48.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灯火一つ抱いて
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.33,0:40:53.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,森に消えて行く
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.48,0:40:59.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,in the dark
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.87,0:41:05.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ずっと遠くへ歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.38,0:41:10.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懷かしい面影
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.04,0:41:16.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ずっと遠くが君の家
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.75,0:41:22.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辿り着けはしない
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.34,0:41:28.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,your fairy tale
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.37,0:41:57.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢に見た永遠は閉ざされたままで
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.32,0:42:02.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過ちは深く隠されたままで
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.64,0:42:07.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消えていく帰り道
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.62,0:42:14.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君がもう見えない
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.07,0:42:21.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…さよなら
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.95,0:42:27.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧の森を抜けて
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.35,0:42:32.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君は何処へ行く
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.91,0:42:38.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一つだけ手を振って
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.34,0:42:43.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日へ去って行く
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.13,0:42:49.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君を好きになって
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.80,0:42:55.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永遠は終わる
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.53,0:43:00.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生きて行く喜びと
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.03,0:43:06.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛みが始まる
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.20,0:43:12.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,in the light
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------<oblivious>-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.32,0:48:20.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当は空を飛べると知っていたから
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.67,0:48:27.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羽ばたくときが怖くて風を忘れた
Dialogue: 0,0:48:27.95,0:48:29.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,oblivious
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.71,0:48:31.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何処へ行くの
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.63,0:48:35.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遠くに見えるあの蜃気楼
Dialogue: 0,0:48:36.13,0:48:39.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつか怯えながら
Dialogue: 0,0:48:39.28,0:48:47.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二人の未来を映して
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.16,0:49:06.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よるべない心二つ寄り添う頃に
Dialogue: 0,0:49:06.80,0:49:13.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の悲しみがほら翼広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.00,0:49:15.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,oblivious
Dialogue: 0,0:49:15.74,0:49:17.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜の中で
Dialogue: 0,0:49:17.69,0:49:21.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真昼の影を夢見るように
Dialogue: 0,0:49:22.14,0:49:25.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと墜ちて行こう
Dialogue: 0,0:49:25.36,0:49:30.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光へ
Dialogue: 0,0:49:45.13,0:49:50.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつか　君と　二人
Dialogue: 0,0:49:50.62,0:49:59.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜を　朝を　昼を　星を　幻想を
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.05,0:50:07.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏を　冬を　時を　風を
Dialogue: 0,0:50:07.70,0:50:13.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水を　土を　空を
Dialogue: 0,0:50:13.41,0:50:20.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,we go further in the destiny…
Dialogue: 0,0:50:31.72,0:50:38.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当は空を飛べると知っていたから
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.41,0:50:48.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羽ばたくときが怖く風を忘れた
Dialogue: 0,0:50:38.57,0:50:44.30,JP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星を　幻想を 空を
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.06,0:50:50.81,JP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,we go further in the destiny…
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.19,0:50:53.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,oblivious
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.73,0:50:55.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,側にいてね
Dialogue: 0,0:50:55.59,0:50:59.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静かな恋がほら始まるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.07,0:51:03.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつか震えながら
Dialogue: 0,0:51:03.19,0:51:07.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二人の未来へ
Dialogue: 0,0:51:07.39,0:51:08.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,oblivious
Dialogue: 0,0:51:08.95,0:51:10.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何処へ行くの
Dialogue: 0,0:51:10.90,0:51:15.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遠くへ逃げてゆく水の中
Dialogue: 0,0:51:15.47,0:51:18.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何て綺麗な声で
Dialogue: 0,0:51:18.61,0:51:22.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二人の未来を
Dialogue: 0,0:51:22.48,0:51:28.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌って
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------Ⅱ杀人考察(前)---------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.10,0:01:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(475,660)\fs45}我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.10,0:01:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类 无法拯救任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.44,0:02:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此 至少明确地将死亡记录下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.93,0:02:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡搜集
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.73,0:02:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.82,0:02:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是那个时候的...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.66,0:02:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.88,0:03:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是穿得那么清凉啊 式
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.97,0:03:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.27,0:03:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀人犯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.87,0:03:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在暑假的最后一天 发生了杀人事件
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.91,0:03:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.85,0:03:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带了伞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.37,0:03:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给学长举行了告别会
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.56,0:03:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫白纯里绪的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.46,0:04:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑桐君 我是一个异常的人 你能理解吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.41,0:04:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾 我是杀人犯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.20,0:04:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式的杀人的定义 是指杀了我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.20,0:04:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(915,660)\fs45}织
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.15,0:04:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀死想要释放我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.34,0:04:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式 为了保护自己
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.20,0:04:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会想把所有试图打开「式」这个盒子的人都杀掉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.90,0:04:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(575,660)\fs45}式
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.90,0:04:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也是 我肯定会杀了你的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.45,0:05:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 我没有看到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.69,0:05:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式只是在那里而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.37,0:05:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到的仅此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.19,0:05:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.01,0:05:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何等 幸福的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.91,0:05:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情你做不出来的 绝对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.12,0:05:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫绝对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.52,0:05:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你了解我什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.22,0:06:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又相信我什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.43,0:06:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有根据
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.49,0:06:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 我想我会一直相信式的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.24,0:06:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 因为喜欢你 所以想一直相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.86,0:06:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑桐！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.38,0:06:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑桐！！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.65,0:07:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好想杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------Ⅳ伽蓝之洞--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.87,0:07:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在无人的街道中行走 是想让自己孤身一人？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.88,0:07:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抑或刚好相反 只是想自认自己很孤独？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.24,0:08:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有...尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.29,0:08:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 死...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.61,0:09:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.46,0:09:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.34,0:09:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.37,0:09:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在只是一具空壳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.39,0:09:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如洞穴般空虚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.39,0:09:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 无论对自己多么没有实感
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.74,0:09:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还是两仪式
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.68,0:09:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.15,0:09:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.53,0:09:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是医生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.61,0:09:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我的本行是魔法使
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.80,0:09:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,织君真的白白牺牲了吗 两仪式
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.11,0:09:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.83,0:09:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.05,0:10:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若能填补我心中的空洞 那就来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.19,0:10:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果 空穴只能用某些东西去填补
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.31,0:10:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是记忆 而是累积现在 形成新的自我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.19,0:10:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁也无法插手的「伽蓝制造」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.16,0:10:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别犹豫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.82,0:11:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是「活着的尸体」对吧 那么...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.53,0:11:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是什么 我都杀给你看!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.05,0:11:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.38,0:11:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一堆死尸烂肉 别挡在我的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.42,0:12:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你就逃不掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.16,0:12:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会杀死懦弱的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.64,0:12:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两仪式 绝对不会交给你这种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.45,0:12:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他 究竟为了交换什么 为了保护什么而消失的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.16,0:12:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失了的「织」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.78,0:12:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕是 为了守护自己的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.51,0:13:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那个幸福地活下去的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.19,0:13:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我留下的 却是如此深邃的孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.95,0:13:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道...我是谁吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.70,0:13:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.34,0:13:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你一直在等着我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.62,0:13:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你一直在...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.83,0:13:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守护着我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.85,0:13:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑桐干也
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.33,0:13:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像个法国诗人似的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.18,0:14:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴天真好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.81,0:14:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出院再好不过了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.92,0:14:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些东西 是不会失去的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-------------------Ⅲ痛觉残留----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.42,0:14:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将人的脑比作电视的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.39,0:14:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使我和你的脑里面有数个频道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.34,0:14:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的脑所看到的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.59,0:14:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是最高视听率的8频道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.24,0:14:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换句话说 就是名为常识的节目而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.86,0:14:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是最能和谐地活下去的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.99,0:14:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓超能力者 是超出这个常识的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.46,0:14:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,例如 调到4频道的话 凭意念就能移动物体
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.81,0:15:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 那不是8频道的常识
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.64,0:15:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两者的存在并不能调和
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.58,0:15:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我们这样称呼他们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.51,0:15:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“不适合存在者”
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.68,0:15:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我听来 你所说的那个“不适合存在者”
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.95,0:15:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有如同可以拧断人的胳膊般强大的歪曲能力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.33,0:15:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是左边还是右边 都能使之运转
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.19,0:15:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是第一起拥有两个频道并同时使用的个案
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.66,0:15:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 应该考虑两个频道以上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.19,0:15:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 如果那个不适合者确实存在的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.78,0:15:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好不要和她扯上关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.16,0:15:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？将不适合者变成适合者的方法？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.20,0:15:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能杀了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.20,0:15:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破坏异常的频道等于是破坏大脑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.26,0:16:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还没有破坏肉体而不破坏其机能这种技术
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.77,0:16:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的话 那才叫超能力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.93,0:16:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归根到底是12频道吗 啊哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.47,0:16:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们存在本身已经不相宜了 不能存在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.04,0:16:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是不能让他们存在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.00,0:16:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭曲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.85,0:16:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.33,0:16:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我...不得不这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.25,0:16:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我终于...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.41,0:16:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于...成为普通人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.61,0:16:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们终于见面了 浅上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.95,0:16:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两仪...式...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.98,0:17:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的你 我下得了手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.42,0:17:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知疼痛为何物这件事 我不想让任何人知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.09,0:17:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不能让别人认为藤乃是普通人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.18,0:17:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定会崩溃的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.20,0:17:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.90,0:17:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实...我不想杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.57,0:17:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 并非如此
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.89,0:17:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.38,0:17:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是同类
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.59,0:17:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别胡说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.26,0:17:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易才体会到痛觉 体会到活着的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.49,0:18:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤乃 把伤养好的话就不会感到疼了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.11,0:18:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说 并不明白那句话的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.91,0:18:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 我从来没有体会过痛苦的滋味
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.73,0:18:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.20,0:18:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了避免麻烦 在黑桐回来之前解决吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.49,0:18:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 橙子姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.97,0:18:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于浅上藤乃 她果然是得了无痛症
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.11,0:18:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是 她的体质原本是很普通的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.71,0:18:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.80,0:19:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切皆源于小小的误会
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.62,0:19:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如式所言 浅上藤乃已经没救了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.25,0:19:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于见面了 浅上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.60,0:19:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两仪...式...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.39,0:19:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是尝过鲜血滋味的野兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.96,0:19:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.42,0:19:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是乱来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.28,0:20:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭曲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.62,0:20:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭曲吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.00,0:20:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭曲吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.16,0:20:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 好痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.40,0:20:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 好痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.01,0:20:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛的话...说出来不就好了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.21,0:21:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.94,0:21:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我同情她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.73,0:21:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心灵的创伤无法治愈 无时无刻不腐蚀着她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.88,0:21:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对此我心里也不好过
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.49,0:21:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个老好人...但是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.28,0:21:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我可没有良知这种高尚品质
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.17,0:21:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放任我这种家伙没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.97,0:21:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 那没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.96,0:21:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式的罪 就由我背负好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.13,0:21:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.57,0:21:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前就这样一本正经的开玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.83,0:21:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话 对那一点 式真的是拿你没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.28,0:21:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.33,0:22:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想 一个女孩子我还是能背得动的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.16,0:22:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再告诉你一件事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.81,0:22:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也觉得自己在这次事件中背上了罪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.46,0:22:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可也令我明白了一点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.69,0:22:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己的所求
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.17,0:22:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然还很模糊 不太可靠
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.71,0:22:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也只能依靠它了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.37,0:22:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它并没有自己想像中那么糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.34,0:22:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那令我稍感欣慰
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.73,0:22:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点点 真的是有一点点 想杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.04,0:22:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今想来 那是她醒来之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.23,0:22:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次对我露出 真正的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------------Ⅰ俯瞰风景-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.62,0:23:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在意了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.42,0:23:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.33,0:23:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关联性？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.12,0:23:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 就是关联性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.50,0:23:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这与跳楼自杀是矛盾的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.25,0:23:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.67,0:23:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要到什么时候才会回来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.29,0:23:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家那小子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.91,0:24:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能飞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.59,0:24:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...不明白！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.49,0:24:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堕落吧 堕落吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.34,0:24:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊 式
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.94,0:24:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔？果然是式啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.33,0:24:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 堕落吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.81,0:25:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.03,0:25:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能带我走
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.56,0:25:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的结局 果然是俯瞰风景坠落而死才适合啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------------Ⅴ矛盾螺旋------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.38,0:25:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.67,0:25:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔术师荒耶宗莲
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.62,0:25:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弑式之人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.08,0:25:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何...要杀我？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.33,0:25:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为巫条雾绘和浅上藤乃都没有效果
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.29,0:25:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.26,0:25:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管你们都在死亡边缘
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.15,0:25:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她选择了死 你却选择了生
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.45,0:25:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管你们都在杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.10,0:26:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在享受杀人的欢愉 你却尊重互相厮杀
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.22,0:26:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.12,0:26:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们虽是你的同类
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.81,0:26:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却又是和两仪式截然相反的杀人鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.35,0:26:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们两人 是为你而准备的祭品
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.53,0:26:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.27,0:26:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两仪式 「无」才是你的混沌冲动 你的起源
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.99,0:26:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正视那片黑暗 然后忆起汝之真名
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.75,0:26:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.31,0:26:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫胭条巴
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.61,0:26:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是两仪式
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.36,0:26:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有睡觉的地方吧 暂时就睡这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.26,0:26:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚你不是说过没有锁嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.31,0:27:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就换了新的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.11,0:27:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了没有必要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.01,0:27:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有锁的家根本不是一个家
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.38,0:27:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能为我而死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.16,0:27:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.52,0:27:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只是个试验而已
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.00,0:27:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的生活本来就已经崩溃了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.58,0:27:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅一个月就开始互相厮杀 然后死去
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.93,0:27:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胭条 这栋公寓
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.68,0:28:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕是不断重复着居民的最后一天的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.36,0:28:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡的一天
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.19,0:28:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从根源一分为二的状态
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.39,0:28:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小川公寓正是太极图的具体体现
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.74,0:28:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,元凶
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.22,0:28:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 不惧 金刚 蛇蝎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.18,0:28:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心迷失于冥途之中哦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.60,0:28:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 苍崎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.37,0:29:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有目的的 魔术师的最终目标是根源之涡
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.23,0:29:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何 没有尽头的目的 永远得不到回报的群体
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.04,0:29:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世人称他们为「魔术师」
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.99,0:29:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死线 是物体的破绽
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.94,0:29:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看到它 即意味着理解了事物的真理
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.12,0:29:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.77,0:29:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根源里森罗万象
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.81,0:29:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定 式正在太极中做着梦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.53,0:29:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了不起呢 巴
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.61,0:29:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钥匙 是家人的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.16,0:29:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得不错吧 我也很满意
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.60,0:29:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这颗头颅还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.04,0:29:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.95,0:29:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人偶
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.77,0:29:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.04,0:30:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢两仪 这份心意是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.88,0:30:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾 在这里活过
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.11,0:30:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肃
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.68,0:32:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样看过去 不过是个和她岁数相符的妙龄少女罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.09,0:32:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你的结界 式得救了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.61,0:32:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次也是以失败告终呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.63,0:32:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何要如此逼迫自己
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.02,0:32:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何为了追求根源之涡而做到如此地步
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.49,0:32:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类 拯救不完
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.66,0:32:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是很遥远的事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.62,0:32:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能拯救全部的人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.06,0:32:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 该拿什么去拯救那些得不到救赎的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.77,0:33:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有答案
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.80,0:33:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 若能开启根源 终结世界
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.22,0:33:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记录并检视死亡 直到世界的终焉
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.45,0:33:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得不到回报之人 得不到救赎之人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.82,0:33:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若能全部从新审视
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.35,0:33:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无意义地死去之人便也有了意义
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.94,0:33:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何谓幸福 也能得出判别的标准
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.58,0:33:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底算是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.62,0:33:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都不是 只是想要一个结论而已
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.08,0:33:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些丑陋 肮脏 低贱而蒙昧的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.57,0:33:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若他们死绝之后只在历史上留下这些评价
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.55,0:33:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么这份丑陋才是人类的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.08,0:33:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也就能安心了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.66,0:33:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想为了自己而把所有卑微的人都消灭掉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.05,0:34:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 在还差一步的时候 我又受到了阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.16,0:34:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类真是喜欢垂死挣扎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.94,0:34:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胭条巴在这条螺旋中脱离出来 出乎你的意料吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.25,0:34:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不让抑止力发觉
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.24,0:34:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你布下了文明的结界
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.20,0:34:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但从那打起 就已经是错漏百出了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.67,0:34:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你输就输在区区一个巴对家人的爱之上
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.50,0:34:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你一件好消息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.75,0:34:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某个心理学家对集团潜意识下过定义
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.53,0:34:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人的意识的底层 都会到达同一个湖中
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.54,0:34:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中储藏着这个人世间的所有执念
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.68,0:34:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这在佛教 称之为阿赖耶识
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.29,0:34:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什...么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.23,0:34:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这世界的矛盾是何等的坏心肠啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.03,0:34:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你生来就和你所憎恨之物同名
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.39,0:35:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这副身体 已经到极限了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.34,0:35:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要重头再来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.74,0:35:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有制作备用的躯壳
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.74,0:35:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荒耶 所求为何
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.83,0:35:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真如
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.83,0:35:27.70,EP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,译注:真如乃佛教用语，意为世界的真理，本质
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.23,0:35:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荒耶 何处求之
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.10,0:35:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只在己身
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.82,0:35:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荒耶 所向何方
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.28,0:35:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明知故问
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.89,0:35:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这矛盾的世界——螺旋的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------Ⅵ忘却录音--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.18,0:36:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明记忆能像影像那样记录下来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.23,0:36:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何还会忘却
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.29,0:36:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任性地将之遗忘
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.92,0:36:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.53,0:36:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是记不起来而已
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.33,0:36:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定记得
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.75,0:36:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和不能记录的我不同
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.67,0:36:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会失去人们的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.60,0:36:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘却即等同与劣化
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.27,0:37:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回忆并不是失去的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.99,0:37:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是脱色的废弃物
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.18,0:37:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得这样很浪费吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.68,0:37:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家使永恒之物生锈
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.91,0:37:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用自己的手为永恒之物撒上使之沉淀的灰尘
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.70,0:37:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不永恒即是永恒
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.76,0:37:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么永恒不得不归还
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.76,0:37:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重现你的悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.92,0:37:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使你想要忘却
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.96,0:37:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记录却明确地被你录音了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.28,0:37:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永恒是由谁来决定的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.20,0:37:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.18,0:37:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我一直在寻找
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.48,0:38:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是兜了个大圈子呢 你的目的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.66,0:38:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢 我只是实现他人的愿望罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.19,0:38:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的事件说到底也是她们的愿望所致
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.44,0:38:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本身是没有目的的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.83,0:38:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是一种缘分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.90,0:38:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之所以来到这个国家 是应荒耶宗莲的请求
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.78,0:38:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将你忘却的两年前的记忆归还
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.67,0:38:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你也在追寻着失去的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.36,0:38:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看到你隐藏在话语之中的内心
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.32,0:38:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的任务仅此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.53,0:38:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是魔术师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.77,0:38:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我是操纵语言的魔术师
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.74,0:38:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人称「伪神之书」
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.74,0:38:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(685,660)\fs45}Godo Word
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.13,0:39:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能辨认曾见过的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.86,0:39:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以之后学到的知识 并不是记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.02,0:39:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是信息罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.45,0:39:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界不是影像 而是被替换成语言的信息而已
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.19,0:39:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也...不
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.46,0:39:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于我来说 外面的世界 从我十岁开始就已经停滞了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.23,0:39:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 橙子姐
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.93,0:39:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 看来安全到达了啊 秘密武器
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.29,0:39:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵苍崎橙子小姐的吩咐前来听候调遣
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.51,0:40:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事物因观测者的存在才意味着其自身的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.76,0:40:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 即使事物本身不变
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.18,0:40:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果观测者本身的印象不是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.04,0:40:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不是永恒的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.72,0:40:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新颜老去 美好不再
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.13,0:40:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事物本身没有变化
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.33,0:40:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是我们自身将事物的价值改变了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.20,0:40:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖精来了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.28,0:40:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.56,0:41:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖精夺走的 只是还记得的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.40,0:41:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去的记忆  谁也无法将忘却再生
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.15,0:41:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是 我是从什么时候开始喜欢干也的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.38,0:41:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全没有这段记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.70,0:41:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他虽然会用语言支配人的认识
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.67,0:41:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是再也没有其他的攻击手段
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.52,0:41:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里什么也没有...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.96,0:41:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赶时间 告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.80,0:41:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式君 所谓永恒 乃是无形之物
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.40,0:41:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.86,0:41:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑桐同学
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.65,0:41:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有任何期望
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.59,0:42:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是希望找到解决的手段
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.90,0:42:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未笑过
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.98,0:42:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看不到 前方
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.19,0:42:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重现你的悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.82,0:42:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使你想要忘却
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.99,0:42:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记忆却明确地被你录音了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.66,0:42:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.79,0:43:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纠缠不休
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.83,0:43:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.67,0:43:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.13,0:43:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.45,0:43:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲜花 不坐巴士了？
Dialogue: 0,0:43:46.87,0:43:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.66,0:43:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 我饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.78,0:44:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我梦见了小时候的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.71,0:44:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是哥哥和我都很熟悉的...重要的人去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.45,0:44:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.56,0:44:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他从未流过眼泪
Dialogue: 0,0:44:41.16,0:44:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全身上下都很普通 比谁都不愿意伤害别人
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.48,0:44:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明能和任何人相互理解
Dialogue: 0,0:44:47.33,0:44:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但却有着谁也发觉不到的 空虚的孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.25,0:45:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此时 对我来说 黑桐干也成为了我要珍惜的人
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.78,0:45:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能失去的人
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.84,0:45:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能理解能简单地把事物忘却的你们
Dialogue: 0,0:45:13.78,0:45:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界可以称之为永恒的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:45:16.74,0:45:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有人的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.72,0:45:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们错以为人生之后才是回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.66,0:45:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实人生是连接在回忆之后的
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.77,0:45:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人没有可以忘却的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:45:36.51,0:45:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使人格可以舍弃记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:45:39.20,0:45:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其本身并不想舍弃
Dialogue: 0,0:45:43.17,0:45:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们的愿望无论什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:45:47.06,0:45:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是忘却的录音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,------------------Ⅰ~Ⅵ Remix------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.18,0:48:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是乱来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.39,0:48:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:48:04.63,0:48:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:48:05.68,0:48:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:48:06.99,0:48:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.74,0:48:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:14.42,0:48:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.43,0:48:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑桐
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.17,0:48:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙上钩了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.38,0:48:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有过很想杀人的想法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:19.71,0:48:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他劳累之时...
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.81,0:48:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式的杀人定义...
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.44,0:48:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我在意你
Dialogue: 0,0:48:32.03,0:48:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近期内我们会再见的
Dialogue: 0,0:48:37.67,0:48:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈根达斯的草莓冰淇淋
Dialogue: 0,0:48:39.77,0:48:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的那份还在 给我处理掉
Dialogue: 0,0:48:43.22,0:48:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不该说「给我处理掉」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:45.52,0:48:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少把你的用词改改啊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:49.03,0:48:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是女孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.11,0:50:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:50:03.43,0:50:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你一直在等着我
Dialogue: 0,0:50:09.17,0:50:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你一直在守护着我
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.77,0:50:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点点 真的是有一点点 想杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:50:31.72,0:50:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万物皆有其破绽 人类自不必说
Dialogue: 0,0:50:36.46,0:50:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连大气 意志 乃至于时间都有
Dialogue: 0,0:50:40.74,0:50:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的眼睛 能看到事物的死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.66,0:50:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 只要是活着的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.22,0:50:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是神我也能杀给你看
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.16,0:50:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经看清你的戏法了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:55.32,0:50:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有我杀不死的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:50:59.74,0:51:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是最棒的
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.78,0:51:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果你在享受...
Dialogue: 0,0:51:02.45,0:51:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该现在就决定
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:53:13.34,0:53:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:53:37.44,0:53:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1995年4月
Dialogue: 0,0:53:41.61,0:53:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我遇上了她
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------Ⅶ杀人考察(后)---------------
Dialogue: 0,1:00:20.81,1:00:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次章预告
Dialogue: 0,1:00:26.02,1:00:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说 是谁杀了谁？
Dialogue: 0,1:00:29.32,1:00:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我需要她...需要杀人的两仪
Dialogue: 0,1:00:34.42,1:00:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你...因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,1:00:37.75,1:00:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两仪没有来到这边的世界
Dialogue: 0,1:00:43.85,1:00:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候 比起独自回家
Dialogue: 0,1:00:48.93,1:00:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我选择了和她在一起
Dialogue: 0,1:00:52.06,1:00:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,460)\fs45}从织消失的那个夜晚算起的三年后
Dialogue: 0,1:00:54.19,1:00:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 式 回来
Dialogue: 0,1:00:55.60,1:00:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,460)\fs45}1999年
Dialogue: 0,1:00:59.09,1:01:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,460)\fs45}——杀人鬼、再临
Dialogue: 0,1:00:58.00,1:01:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能杀了那个人
Dialogue: 0,1:01:00.87,1:01:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能杀...？
Dialogue: 0,1:01:03.32,1:01:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和干也你没有关系
Dialogue: 0,1:01:05.84,1:01:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式 你杀了学长的话 我不会原谅你的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------<君が光に変えて行く>------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.90,0:02:44.82,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暖风吹过
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.01,0:02:52.02,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼声渐闻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.19,0:02:59.01,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惜暗夜消逝
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.26,0:03:10.29,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黎明将至
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.55,0:03:18.24,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日必定
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.53,0:03:25.64,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在蔚蓝天空中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.47,0:03:40.11,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挂起银色长虹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.26,0:03:46.79,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,景色如此凄凉哀伤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.01,0:03:53.95,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君将化作光芒 一扫阴霾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.20,0:04:01.13,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连滴滴泪珠
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.35,0:04:08.37,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亦如同宝石般璀璨夺目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.77,0:04:18.34,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向未来洒落
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.35,0:04:29.92,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都有自己的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.22,0:04:36.91,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们依旧想一窥究竟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.58,0:04:44.02,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果使自己遍体鳞伤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.22,0:04:51.35,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踌躇不前 进退两难
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.51,0:04:57.72,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若能踏上桥头 渡过河流
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.30,0:05:01.81,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明日必定...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.93,0:05:04.86,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艳阳高照
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.04,0:05:11.33,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春意盎然
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.49,0:05:14.54,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如梦初醒
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.87,0:05:23.16,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一生何求
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.88,0:05:51.13,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界如此光明坦荡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.43,0:05:58.27,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君将紧携我手 导我前行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.43,0:06:05.23,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炫目光芒 我呆立不前
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.39,0:06:12.22,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君拥我入怀 软语温言
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.41,0:06:18.95,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信念如此虚幻无常
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.27,0:06:26.04,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君将化作光芒 一扫阴霾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.28,0:06:33.02,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清晨醒来的点点泪珠
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.18,0:06:40.06,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亦如同宝石般璀璨夺目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.25,0:06:50.20,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向未来洒落
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------<ARIA>----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.12,0:07:57.78,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦之碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.09,0:08:03.16,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君赠之
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.96,0:08:13.13,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隐入无尽长夜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.61,0:08:20.63,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两相偎依之星
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.25,0:08:27.61,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其一已逝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.15,0:08:39.00,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化作黎明的咏叹调
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.31,0:08:44.49,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无尽风雨之中
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.93,0:08:50.41,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不再惧怕昨日
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.77,0:08:56.27,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有你的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.12,0:09:04.85,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻刚刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.45,0:09:10.81,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无边黑暗之中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.06,0:09:16.63,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乃君赠之篝火
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.84,0:09:22.47,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照亮伽蓝之心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.65,0:09:32.72,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赐予新生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.45,0:09:51.51,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命易逝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.27,0:09:57.29,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世事难变
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.73,0:10:06.44,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无情天空 阳光普照
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.29,0:10:14.01,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与君离别
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.65,0:10:20.46,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相视一笑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.18,0:10:32.84,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前路寂寞多珍重
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.75,0:11:01.02,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此后一身孑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.56,0:11:06.87,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是愿两相依
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.14,0:11:13.17,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君之美好未来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.56,0:11:21.75,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻刚刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.69,0:11:33.10,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温柔不曾识
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.34,0:11:38.94,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸得君给与
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.16,0:11:44.63,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于伽蓝之心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.85,0:11:51.24,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点起无名灯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.46,0:11:56.33,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摇一叶孤舟
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.51,0:12:01.98,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,载篝火聚集之悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.25,0:12:08.00,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伽蓝之世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.18,0:12:19.03,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无尽咏叹响
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-----------------<伤迹>----------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.82,0:16:30.90,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从寂静中迈开脚步
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.07,0:16:35.33,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追寻着未曾见过的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.46,0:16:39.88,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使痛楚 亦愿相信
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.07,0:16:47.77,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,度过这长夜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.69,0:17:08.78,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你抚过我的胸口 留下一道温柔的伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.16,0:17:17.84,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隐藏已久的泪珠 带着点点猩红
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.06,0:17:26.46,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落在冰冷的肌肤上 化作朵朵鲜花
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.71,0:17:35.47,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里 歌唱幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.76,0:17:39.74,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦醒时分
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.94,0:17:44.13,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星辰陨落之时
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.47,0:17:54.57,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请紧抱我 让我感受生之喜悦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.91,0:18:03.13,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从寂静中诞生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.30,0:18:07.58,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未曾知晓温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.71,0:18:12.40,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只为寻找生之所在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.54,0:18:18.21,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,度过这长夜
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.67,0:18:36.64,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人怀念的夏日倾盆大雨
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.95,0:18:40.80,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛在为我送行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.16,0:18:45.30,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像希望我能带着泪水
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.57,0:18:50.15,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走向互相信任的开端般
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.31,0:18:54.18,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论喜悦 抑或悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.63,0:18:58.66,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都愿深深铭刻心中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.87,0:19:03.24,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与你在此
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.56,0:19:08.21,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下幸福的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.59,0:19:17.66,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星辰陨落之时
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.04,0:19:30.61,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见到的光芒中
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.85,0:19:51.97,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用眼神和一个吻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.17,0:19:56.43,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下爱过的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.63,0:20:05.31,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿为生命而痛哭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.47,0:20:09.81,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从寂静中迈开脚步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.99,0:20:14.22,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追寻着未曾见过的遥远黎明
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.37,0:20:18.95,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只为实现心中愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.07,0:20:27.58,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,度过这长夜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------<Interlude#1>-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.09,0:23:26.96,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠在向黎明急驶的列车窗边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.31,0:23:32.79,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收集着陨落的星辰
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.95,0:23:41.60,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦想拼图还差一块碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.86,0:23:45.44,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然大家都在寻找
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.64,0:23:49.21,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎一样的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.43,0:23:54.23,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但终究会渐渐错开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.42,0:24:02.53,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你又将去往何方
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.45,0:24:16.10,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了明天 蔚蓝天空中
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.28,0:24:21.99,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那银色长虹
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.24,0:24:25.96,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿过层层迷雾来到你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.10,0:24:33.14,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你带来光明
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.43,0:24:40.30,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将向你延伸的黑夜...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.00,0:24:46.49,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将向我延伸的黑夜...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.68,0:24:50.29,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将那遥远的道路...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.44,0:24:53.77,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汹涌澎湃的流水
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.93,0:24:57.46,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无休止的风
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.78,0:25:01.37,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向黎明急行
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.62,0:25:05.26,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涨潮之歌
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.48,0:25:12.93,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿过小桥 向着彼岸
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.13,0:25:20.03,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向着炫目的夏日白昼
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.17,0:25:28.05,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你又将去往何方
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------<Sprinter>------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.58,0:26:39.16,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与你相逢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.42,0:26:43.67,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如朝露昙花
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.58,0:26:56.81,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却刹那永恒
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.99,0:27:02.92,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm calling 呼唤你的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.19,0:27:08.71,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿将你守护
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.87,0:27:21.52,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纵使十指颤抖 亦要拥你入怀
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.67,0:27:26.09,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们所能做的 不过是竭尽全力地
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.26,0:27:28.45,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.59,0:27:33.37,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纵使无能为力 空余呐喊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.51,0:27:35.91,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可知？
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.08,0:27:42.83,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻 粉碎绝望 迈步前行
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.99,0:27:45.24,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到螺旋之尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.36,0:27:56.66,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm calling　我在远方挣扎的歌声
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.85,0:28:07.27,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让你为我仰望天空
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.43,0:28:14.54,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将不再孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.39,0:28:26.30,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残酷的真相 连这颗人偶的心
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.49,0:28:33.35,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亦无法承受
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.47,0:28:39.76,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向着光速逝去的昨日挥手
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.91,0:28:45.89,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在烈日当空的沙漠中
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.01,0:28:56.42,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们追赶着时间的脚步
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.81,0:29:07.98,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迎风挥舞 那残缺的旌旗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.47,0:29:21.05,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在没有你的路上 为了我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.36,0:29:28.09,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独自前行
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.75,0:29:33.93,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到螺旋的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.08,0:29:38.90,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想再见你一面
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.11,0:29:44.98,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经深恋着你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.16,0:29:50.91,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想再看你一眼
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.11,0:29:56.74,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经深爱着你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.91,0:30:08.00,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm calling 我曾在这的证据
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.83,0:30:20.04,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也一定残留在你的眼中
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.85,0:30:32.99,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm calling 逆转这封闭的螺旋
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.14,0:30:44.78,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使呐喊痛哭 即使行将消逝
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.94,0:30:52.88,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们仍然 活着
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.11,0:31:05.23,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们仍然 在此
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,--------------<fairytale>-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.01,0:39:43.35,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆起孩提之时
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.54,0:39:48.93,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾追寻的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.11,0:39:54.65,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻声甜蜜歌唱
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.85,0:40:00.10,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡绿色的哀伤
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.43,0:40:05.76,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,my fairy tale
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.10,0:40:17.59,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解并无所谓的永恒
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.87,0:40:31.02,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无人提起的二人故事
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.78,0:40:36.64,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下一个吻
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.03,0:40:42.67,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去向何方
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.80,0:40:48.16,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提上一盏灯
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.33,0:40:53.30,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失于森林
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.48,0:40:59.28,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,in the dark
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.87,0:41:05.17,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我渐行渐远
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.38,0:41:10.86,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀念的面孔
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.04,0:41:16.54,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你遥远的家
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.75,0:41:22.13,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我难以抵达
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.34,0:41:28.62,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,your fairy tale
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.37,0:41:57.17,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦想未曾实现
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.32,0:42:02.52,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过错未曾悔改
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.64,0:42:07.43,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行将消逝的归途
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.62,0:42:14.83,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却再也看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.07,0:42:21.20,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…别了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.95,0:42:27.20,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿越雾森
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.35,0:42:32.76,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去往何方
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.91,0:42:38.14,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挥手告别
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.34,0:42:43.94,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈向明天
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.13,0:42:49.51,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上你那一刻
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.80,0:42:55.28,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永恒宣告终结
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.53,0:43:00.64,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢喜与痛楚中
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.03,0:43:06.02,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.20,0:43:12.35,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,in the light
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---------------<oblivious>-----------------
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.32,0:48:20.17,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂得飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.67,0:48:27.81,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却因恐惧而忘记迎风展翅
Dialogue: 0,0:48:27.95,0:48:29.52,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,oblivious
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.71,0:48:31.45,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所向何方
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.63,0:48:35.99,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远远看到的海市蜃楼
Dialogue: 0,0:48:36.13,0:48:39.12,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天 颤抖着
Dialogue: 0,0:48:39.28,0:48:47.38,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,映照出我们的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.16,0:49:06.52,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两颗孤独的心偎依之时
Dialogue: 0,0:49:06.80,0:49:13.86,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的悲伤展翅高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.00,0:49:15.52,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,oblivious
Dialogue: 0,0:49:15.74,0:49:17.50,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛在黑夜之中
Dialogue: 0,0:49:17.69,0:49:21.96,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦见白天的阴影
Dialogue: 0,0:49:22.14,0:49:25.18,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必定坠向
Dialogue: 0,0:49:25.36,0:49:30.55,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:49:45.13,0:49:50.45,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天 与君二人
Dialogue: 0,0:49:50.62,0:49:59.87,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共鉴明月 共赏晨曦 共沐日光 共览星辰 共织幻想
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.05,0:50:07.52,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共游炎夏 共御寒冬 共度时光 共拂清风
Dialogue: 0,0:50:07.70,0:50:13.23,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共戏流水 共踏尘土 共翱蓝天
Dialogue: 0,0:50:13.41,0:50:20.40,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,we go further in the destiny…
Dialogue: 0,0:50:31.72,0:50:38.47,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂得飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.41,0:50:48.76,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却因恐惧而忘记迎风展翅
Dialogue: 0,0:50:38.57,0:50:44.30,CH1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共览星辰 共织幻想 共翱蓝天
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.06,0:50:50.81,CH1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,we go further in the destiny…
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.19,0:50:53.58,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,oblivious
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.73,0:50:55.43,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请陪伴着我
Dialogue: 0,0:50:55.59,0:50:59.93,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱情的种子已悄悄发芽
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.07,0:51:03.02,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终有一日
Dialogue: 0,0:51:03.19,0:51:07.23,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迎来二人的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:51:07.39,0:51:08.77,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,oblivious
Dialogue: 0,0:51:08.95,0:51:10.74,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所向何方
Dialogue: 0,0:51:10.90,0:51:15.29,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流水渐远
Dialogue: 0,0:51:15.47,0:51:18.42,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫋嫋之音
Dialogue: 0,0:51:18.61,0:51:22.30,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我们的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:51:22.48,0:51:28.63,CH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌唱


